[THEME SONG]
So
when you draw that sword
[heavy music]
the uncle disappears?
From this world, completely?
A tool of annihilation to end the goblin's immortality
[A TREMBLING BREATH]
That's the fate of the goblin bride
(Samshin)
You almost died once too
with your own hands
(Euntak)
move
[Kim Shin's groan]
[EUNTAK'S STRAINING GROAN]
[A TENSE SOUND EFFECT]
(Reaper)
When you draw the sword, that person
[SNIFFLES]
They'll scatter into dust and wind
[A LABORED BREATH]
In this world
or somewhere else forever
(Reaper)
This isn't your fault, other accomplices
If you think you are co-conspirators, that's unfair
What hasn't been said is Kim Shin himself
I've answered with utmost sincerity
Even now while telling this story
I'm on your side
Thank you for your words, take a rest
[WHIMPERING]
[EUNTAK CONTINUES TO WHIMPER]
[SNIFFLES]
Here too
It wasn't my house.
In this life,
It seems there's no home.
Let's go, buckwheat boy.
[ROUGH BREATHING]
Let's just go.
[SOBBING]
[BREATH SHOWING STRAIN]
[TENSE SOUND EFFECTS]
[FOOTSTEPS ECHO]
Excuse me.
It's been a while, want to have a drink?
I'm really angry right now.
Are you going to buy the drinks?
I don't have my card right now.
[AWKWARD LAUGHTER]
[SNICKERS]
[HEAVY MUSIC]
(Kim Shin)
Having lived for a hundred years, one day
On a day that was just right
It was my first love.
[HEAVY SOUND EFFECTS]
I hope to be able to confess
I ask for permission from the sky
I try to seek it
(Euntak)
What are the last words you want to leave?
(Kim Shin)
Every moment spent with you
was dazzling
Whether the day was good
Or not good
Or just right
Every day was good
And
No matter what happens
It’s not your fault
[EUNTAK SOBS]
Was that a farewell?
Ah, should I really just kill you?
[THE RAIN POURS DOWN]
[SOBBING]
(The Grim Reaper)
That day, other missing persons
were said to have walked
through someone's tears for a long time
[THE RAIN POURS DOWN]
As much as possible, from the goblin
to keep death at bay
[URGENT BREATHS]
(Kim Shin)
There's no child, they haven't come in
No calls either
It seems the kid has run away
(The Grim Reaper)
That...
There's no mat, no buckwheat pastries
[The door opens with a click]
That...
What are buckwheat pastries?
[Heavy music]
[Seagull cries]
It's not even at the beach
[THE DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
They said they didn't come to school
[A SIGH]
It's not near the library door where I first followed into Canada
It's not near the park where I was summoned for the second time
[A SIGH]
[TENSE SOUND EFFECT]
The ghost of Ji Eun-tak
[THE AWKWARD LAUGHTER OF THE GHOSTS]
[A SIGH]
(Kim Shin)
Where do you always go to buy chickens?
The chicken shop where Ji Eun-tak works part-time
Even the ghosts don't know Eun-tak's whereabouts.
[THE REAPER'S SIGH]
Do you carry this around?
(Grim Reaper)
I thought I might find it
Actually, I'm the culprit
I've told everything
What?
[A SIGH]
You can't be...
(Grim Reaper)
Yeah, I said that if I draw my sword, you die
I told everything
Are you crazy? How can you say that?
You told me to absolutely not say anything
But again, I'm
on the same side as the other missing person
What are you talking about? What do you mean we’re on the same side?
I don't want
you to die
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
(Grim Reaper)
There's no other meaning
I just thought it would be a bit boring
if you return to nothingness
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
You can be mad
How can I be mad, mad!
The one who held a ritual for my death
says not to die
There's no guarantee that I won't become a radish
(Kim Shin)
Really
(Grim Reaper)
It would be appreciated if you could
hold back on using that coupon...
[FADING FOOTSTEPS]
This
I really ended up forming a genuine friendship
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
[THE SOUND OF FOOTSTEPS ECHOES]
(Sunny)
Please don't contact me anymore.
Even if we run into each other by chance, don't greet me.
[SUNNY'S SIGH]
Happy New Year
Brother?
[TENSE MUSIC]
Why have you been staring at my store?
Could it be...
Are you looking for a part-time job?
That's not it.
I'm looking for this store's part-timer.
[SIGH]
Two thousand five hundred?
(Sunny)
Clothes, watch, shoes
From head to toe,
About two thousand five hundred worth of stuff.
What kind of relationship do you have with our
part-timer who earns six thousand thirty won?
Are you the one who made the kid cry?
Is that the one who caused
trouble while depending on others?
Did you cry?
[SIGH]
That's right, the angry breath of
[THE PERSON WHO FIRED MY PART-TIMER]
The fit is just right, I (Sunny) Are you possibly a
married man? Is that why you sent the kid away like that?
Marriage can be seen as temporary or with another bride,
So it
wouldn't be wrong to think that (Kim Shin)
Then let's see
again; it seems that complicated relationships
Are not just mine.
Hey, what is that...
(Sunny)
Hey, over there, brother!
[SIGH]
(Grim Reaper)
Couldn't find it?
Euntak didn't submit the documents, right?
For now, just upload the documents
What documents?
Other missing person's documents
I need to put it on the list
so they can at least see when they're going to die.
(Grim Reaper)
You're really trying to kill that kid,
why...
You need to know how and where they die
to deal with it whether you go or I go
(Grim Reaper)
What are you talking about?
Why would a missing person die?
I have no intention of that
[Heavy music]
[Kim Shin's sigh]
Seems like there's a bigger purpose
What on earth are we?
(Kim Shin)
How can there be a goblin and a grim reaper
both here
and still not save a single child
I'll upload the documents and come back, but
In the meantime, is there...
What if that happens?
Just go and come back
In a moment where life hangs in the balance,
you'll be able to feel it
What that child desperately seeks in that moment
If it's me
(Grim Reaper)
It's the other missing documents I mentioned earlier.
Please process it as quickly as possible.
It's urgent.
By tomorrow afternoon.
It's late.
Before midnight today.
(Lion)
Jieun-tak?
Isn't she that one?
The one your senior was looking for the list at the bus stop last time...
Who is she?
Goblin bride.
What? No, this person
(Lion)
Really?
Ah, so that's why the goblin teacher was
there at that time?
Holding a sandwich, eating it.
I realize while eating
'Ah, my flattery was excessive, shut up'
- Conduct
- Yes
(Woman)
Those people don't live here
They moved a long time ago
Oh my, really, I'm so annoyed
What kind of debt did they owe, every day
(Yuna)
Ah...
I'm sorry
[YUNA'S SIGH]
Where does this kid live
(Kim Shin)
Why are you looking for Jin-tak?
(Yuna)
The CSAT results came out
But Eun-tak hasn't been coming to school
I’m the class president, you know.
Who is this uncle?
How do you know Ji Eun-tak?
Well
(Kim Shin)
I'll pass this report card on, well
[Yoon A's awkward moan]
[AN ABSURD BREATH]
[A SURPRISED BREATH]
What is this...
(Kim Shin)
Is this enough to say I did well?
(Yoon A)
Yes?
Ah, yes
If it's this good, you can say you're good enough to go to school in Seoul
In the meantime, it's commendable
[YOON A'S FLUSTERED BREATH]
[The door opens with a click]
(The Grim Reaper)
I'm breaking up, they said my mom is sick...
[THE SOUND OF THE TV FLOWS OUT]
- What do you want me to do?
- I'm sorry in advance
I can't see anything right now
Can you bring this for me?
(Kim Shin)
Even the Grim Reaper must buy
socks with money
[A PUZZLED GROAN]
(News Anchor 1)
This is breaking news
Thick fog is engulfing the
body of high-rise buildings
[Heavy Music]
Only the tops of the buildings are towering above.
The unexpected fog feels like a sigh from the gods
and is even mysterious
(News anchor 2)
This is breaking news
This scene, reminiscent of a moment from a sci-fi movie
is from tonight's night sky over Seoul
Between the forest of urban buildings
the supermoon is ominously floating
Following the fog of the day,
the appearance of the supermoon, which is strangely red,
has left the citizens unable to hide their unease
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
(Three Gods)
Quickly draw that sword
Draw the sword and return to the void.
If you don't go back to nothing,
Eun-tak will die
(Kim Shin)
If I
make that choice
the excuse you prepared
will definitely be necessary
[THE WARNING SOUND OF THE ECG]
Father
[Mysterious sound effect]
[The ECG warning sound suddenly stops]
(Doctor 1)
8:15 PM
The patient has passed away
[Sobbing intensely]
Father!
(Man 1)
Father
[MAN 1 CONTINUES TO SOB]
(Lion)
Kim Ki-jung, 68 years old, cause of death, excessive bleeding
[Exciting Music]
(Lion)
Ah, it's
hot, ah, it's hot [A beeping sound
from an ECG machine is heard]
Ah,
it's hot, ah, it's hot Father (Lion)
Huh?
Ah, Father, the
[SCREAMS OF PEOPLE]
(Man 1) Oh, Father, have you come back to
life, right now? [The lion's astonished groan]
Blood is gushing like that... That, there's too much
bleeding, have you, have you, come back to life?
[THE LION'S URGENT BREATHING]
(Lion) Right in front of my eyes, you see
He suddenly sat up? Came back to life?
It's excessive bleeding, but the complexion looks good.
No, what kind of register goes up in flames...
Is this even possible?
Of course, if it's a goblin fire,
[THE GRIM REAPER CRINKLES A PLASTIC BAG]
I guess it was yours.
What is this?
A goblin's apology.
An apology?
[THE LION CRINKLES THE PLASTIC BAG]
It's socks?
[SIGH]
If you apologize in advance, is that all?
You cause the accident
and why does the poor grim reaper have to work overtime?
Dare to burn the register?
Since you live forever, do you see nothing?
(grim reaper)
I'm very sorry for your tragic fate,
but what are you going to do by disrupting human affairs like this?
You unreasonable goblin!
Just, let someone see it.
It would be good for God
and even better for Euntak.
If you end it like that, what do I become?
I shouldn't have said anything.
(grim reaper)
You just should have made sure the omitted people
got drawn out with a knife.
(Kim Shin)
True, that might have been better.
[SIGH]
In this world
(Chairman Yoo) There are strange beings
mixed in that cannot be explained with words.
Sometimes
They could be close by our side.
I think you might have
already known, right?
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
Mr. Yoo Jae-shin
- I'm sorry
- (Secretary Kim) Hehe
(Secretary Kim)
A man who doesn't age
I am aware of.
Really?
(Secretary Kim)
The passport I made
The places I arranged in Nice
The fact that you placed me next to Deokhwa
I thought it was because you wanted me
To recognize that existence on my own
[A FAINT MOAN]
About that existence
Have you ever leaked it anywhere?
No.
(Chairman Yoo)
The reason I picked you is that very existence.
[CHAIRMAN YOO'S LAUGHTER]
To the boy without dreams in the back alley,
I had him take the high school equivalency exam,
gave him a dream,
and helped him enter university.
Who do you think that faceless benefactor is?
Remember,
his real name is
written with the character for 'trust' in the Kim family name.
[CHAIRMAN YOO'S LAUGHTER]
(Deokhwa)
Hey, Mr. Kim Shin,
In the mist of the super moon, that's all uncle, right?
No, why would you look for a runaway high school girl on 'Isn't This a Wonderful World'?
I'm really scared that
NASA might come and take my uncle away
Did you drink?
I drank yesterday
(Deokhwa)
I'm all awake now
Anyway, if I find that girl,
what will my uncle give me?
Will he give me a card?
If I can't find her, how are you going to?
(Deokhwa)
She probably didn't go far; she has no money.
Wherever I go, it's Korea
Whatever I ride, it's the express bus
I have my own way, you know
[THE SOUND OF WINGS FLUTTERING ECHOES]
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
(Euntak)
Welcome
Oh, just a moment
- (Euntak) Hello
- (Customer 1) 177 centimeters
(Customer 2)
Hello
(Euntak)
Yes, just a moment
- (Euntak) Just a moment
- (Customer 3) Yes
[GENTLE MUSIC]
[TIRED GROANS]
(Duk-hwa)
I found that girl, she's at the ski resort right now
(Eun-tak)
What if
I say I won’t become a bride
what will happen then?
(Kim-shin)
Uh...
I can't pull this sword out
Only you can do this
You have to pull out this sword, I
I...
Get... prettier
You're not pretty right now
[KIM-SHIN'S LAUGHTER]
(Kim-shin)
You don’t understand, do you?
If I laugh in this situation
I’d be a crazy person
[SIGH]
Crazy person
Not today, today I just want to laugh with you
What if it snows for the first time?
First snow?
We need a broom
[I CHUCKLE]
Yeah, when it snows for the first time
[A SIGH]
There’s too much snow
Let’s go home
You can’t just do this alone
I don’t have a home
The places I thought were home
were all not my home
(Euntak)
I just kept them close
Some people because of insurance money
Some because they want to die
Now everyone knows, but me?
It is said to be a tool of annihilation that will end the goblin's immortality, me?
I missed the chance to speak
And I was glad to have missed the chance
[SOFT MUSIC]
If possible, until the moment of death
I was going to miss every opportunity
(Kim Shin)
But that shouldn't have been the case
The thousands of bloodstains on this sword
The weight of that one life
I shouldn't be the one to judge
So take out this sword
Please
[A SIGH]
No
I don't want to
I don't want to even if I die
(Hee-tak)
So don’t look for me
Don't look for me
Let's just act like we don't know each other, okay
Go far away from me
Just live a long life, Mr. Kim Shin
Do you understand?
Never show up again
If you appear in front of me again
Then I will really kill you
(Staff 1)
Welcome
[SOFT MUSIC]
[SIGH]
You did well on the exam
[SLIDES THE REPORT CARD IN]
[SIGH]
This is an excuse too
I was glad to have this excuse, at least.
Even like this
It's an excuse that I can come to see you
What should I do by coming to see me
What does it matter if I have an excuse
Are you suggesting we live together?
Are you suggesting we die together?
If I show up again
Did I say I'd kill you or not?
Alright, come here
I'll draw my sword
If that's your wish, I'll draw it for you
Come here, hurry up
[SNICKERS]
This gentleman until the end
Don't do it
Do it
It has to be done
[TREMBLING BREATH]
(Eun-tak)
[Sobbing]
Let go, let go
Let go, let go! I said let go
Let go
[SHE CONTINUES TO SOB]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC]
It was from that time
In that hotel, I was determined
I was going to do this from that time
Mister, do you love me?
If that's necessary, I'll go that far
I love you
(Eun-tak)
So
Did I love you?
No?
Not even that?
(Kim-shin)
I'm scared
It's so scary
So you keep
I hope you said it's necessary.
I wish you would do that too.
Such excuses like permission
I wish it would happen
With that excuse, I hope
I could keep on living
[TREMBLING BREATH]
With you
[I SOB]
[SIGH]
(Eun-tak)
Hello
Guest's personal errand, edge waxing
They asked for it to be done within an hour?
(Staff 2)
Why isn't Manager Kim coming?
I'm on a shift now, so they'll probably come
- Let's wait and see
- Okay
(Staff 2)
Ah, it's cold
[BREATH TREMBLING IN THE COLD]
[GROAN TREMBLING IN THE COLD]
[THE SOUND OF BREATH TREMBLING IN THE COLD]
[A SIGH]
[TENSE MUSIC]
[EUNTAK'S STARTLED BREATH]
[HEAVY MUSIC]
[THE DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES WITH A CLATTER]
(The Grim Reaper)
[Sighing]
Why are you alone?
Did you not meet the missing person?
I met them
But they said they won't come
What on earth is going on?
The list that seems to have come out waiting for the document submission
is the first time
(The Grim Reaper)
The list of the missing person has arrived
[TENSE MUSIC]
"Ji Euntak, 19 years old"
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
Is Eun-tak sure?
It's just a blank paper
(The Grim Reaper)
There is writing,
What the hell is this situation?
It's like someone is pushing to die,
It's not me,
and it can't be you either
It must be me
They say I have to die for him to live
(Kim Shin)
They say if I live, he will die
That's what our fates are
This was the punishment given to me
It was a greater purpose of God, this
Stop with the weak talk
Even if that's God's will,
my will is different.
(The Grim Reaper)
You will too
In one hour from now
[heavy music]
Sign, action, hurry
[MOBILE PHONE OPERATION SOUND]
(Samsin)
Death will keep approaching that child
It must have happened several times already?
It will be even more from now on
More often and harder
than the accidents that have happened until now
[TENSION-FILLED MUSIC]
[SHIVERING BREATH IN THE COLD]
[CALM MUSIC]
[BLOWING AIR FROM THE MOUTH]
[SHIVERING BREATH IN THE COLD]
(Euntak)
It's the first snow, sir.
But why is it snowing
for the first time already?
Wow, that's amazing!
(Kim Shin)
I hope you keep saying that you need me
I hope you tell me to go that far
I wish I had excuses like permission
I hope it happens
[SHIVERING BREATH]
(Eun Tak)
I need you
Let's go that far
I love you
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
(Doctor 2)
Ms. Ji Eun Tak, are you awake?
This is a hospital
You showed signs of hypothermia and
mild concussion
Fortunately, you are okay
If it had been a little later, it could have been serious.
[STRENUOUS GROANING]
How long have I been like this...
It has been a day and a half
Ah...
(Euntak)
Then how much is the hospitalization fee...
(Doctor 2)
Why worry about such things
But what about your relationship with
Chairman Yoo Shin-woo of Cheonwoo Group?
The chairman came in person
to take care of the hospitalization procedure.
The hospital was in chaos.
[AWKWARD GROANING]
You can be discharged if you wish
but
In my opinion,
it's better to take a little more rest...
I'm sorry, but more than that
Is there anyone who has matches or a lighter?
Yes?
[SHE SMILES SOFTLY]
[BLOWS AIR THROUGH HER LIPS]
[SOFT MUSIC]
(Euntak)
[Sobbing]
I thought you weren’t coming...
I thought you weren’t coming anymore...
[SHE PUFFS UP]
I came early and waited
Who came early? Who?
You should come when I blow out the candle
(Euntak)
You should have come there
You should be right in front of me
I tried to hold your hand when I came early
I don’t know, it’s fine
[EUNTAK’S SURPRISED BREATH]
[KIM SHIN'S SIGH]
Me too.
What is it?
You don't need to know
I know everything
Then that's good
(Euntak)
I
have something to confess
(Euntak)
I no longer
have anything to show for myself to you, uncle
You're tall and your clothes look expensive
Your eyes are incredibly beautiful
That's all I see
So I can't take off your ring anymore
Even if you smile, I won't be able to take it off
In my eyes
you are still incredibly handsome
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
Your face is pale and your lips are red
A man in black clothes
sometimes holds a black hat
[THE BELL JINGLES]
[THE FORTUNE TELLER'S STARTLED GROAN]
[SUNNY'S SURPRISED BREATH]
(Sunny)
Why, why?
Did we have an introduction?
That guy is the grim reaper
(Fortune Teller)
No, what did I say
I told you to be careful of the man in the black hat
Can you even make a living?
(Sunny)
Ah, are there any guests other than me?
This gentleman
If you’re careful of men
a single woman can't date
The grim reaper?
It should be somewhat plausible
You wouldn't even use a talisman
[SUNNY'S SIGH]
Then who is this man?
He's really tall, more like an older brother than me
He has a bit of a dinosaur vibe
and when I hear his voice, it feels like
I'm in the smallest café in the world?
Gong Yoo?
[A SIGH]
Are you there, then
(Fortune teller)
Did you bring back a sparkling object
from somewhere?
How did you know that?
Hurry up and throw it away.
An item whose original owner is unknown.
[Meaningful music]
Don't just bring it in carelessly.
What if something is contained there?
(Fortune Teller)
The original owner's resentment, sin, and longing.
Everything tends to settle in.
[SIGH]
What kind of resentment?
(Sunny)
Tsk, what sin could it be?
What kind of longing could be contained there?
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
Ha, by the way,
Manager Kim Woobin is still MIA.
(Grim Reaper)
I'm sorry, it was unintentional.
(Sunny)
People really have to contact first, and really
Right now?
[PLAYFUL MUSIC]
[ANNOYED SIGH]
(Sunny)
Are you busy?
Yes, I’m going crazy
(Sunny)
What are you doing now?
(Grim Reaper)
Solving patterns, trying to turn it off
I’m afraid it might make noise again
[SURPRISED BREATH SOUNDS]
[A SIGH]
[SUNNY’S TROUBLED BREATH SOUNDS]
(Sunny)
Why aren’t you contacting me again?
That’s
First
Because of the guilt of erasing your memory and
[SIGH]
(Grim Reaper)
Second
[CALM MUSIC]
[TEARS FALL SILENTLY]
(Grim Reaper)
Who on earth are you
to be this affected?
It's because
I feel like I'm in the wind.
I'm sorry.
(Grim Reaper)
I'm really confused about myself too
[Mobile phone notification sound]
[Sunny's surprised gasp]
A message has arrived.
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SURPRISED GASP]
(Sunny)
I miss you.
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
[SUNNY'S FRIGHTENED BREATH]
Me too.
Why am I like this again?
No, I didn't hear it
(Sunny)
I didn't hear it
I didn't hear it, didn't hear it
[SUNNY'S NERVOUS BREATHING]
♪ Glory glory hallelujah ♪
I know everything that's there! Come out
Is something so insignificant going to harm a person?!
Come out, no, get out, disappear!
If you don't, I'll sing again
♪ Glory glory hallelujah ♪
Why are you empty-handed?
Wasn't the stuff going home?
I was going to my part-time job?
(Euntak) Since it's the
Christmas season, it's a
relief we haven't been cut
given how high the pay is here.
Let’s wrap up our work
neatly and bring some beef
to celebrate our return. Until
when? Until when will you be here?
What do you mean until when?
The ski resort is open until
all the snow melts in February
(Euntak) You go
ahead, ah, February?
[MOBILE PHONE OPERATION SOUND]
Chairman Yoo's
[CALL CONNECTION SOUND]
Oh, Chairman Yoo, it's me.
I wish you would quickly cut
someone off using your connections.
If not, should I just melt all the snow at the ski resort quickly?
What should I do?
(Eun-tak)
I’m back
[THE DOOR SHUTS WITH A CLICK]
I’m sorry, you must have worried a lot, right?
I found a little, a lot of interest
It was Deok-hwa who discovered it
I brought it
(Eun-tak)
It’s the first time I have a place to come back to
so it feels strange
Now this feels like my real home
(Kim-shin)
Here we go again
Ah, if you ask, there’s always a story, huh?
Where would I say to come back because it's scary?
(Grim Reaper)
Just wear it
You have to go with me
(Euntak)
Where are you taking my uncle?
I'm a bit sensitive about that
(Kim Shin)
You said 'ours'
[SIGH]
(Grim Reaper)
I can hear everything
You're such a cringey goblin!
[AWKWARD GROAN]
(Grim Reaper)
It seems nice that you said 'ours'
[KIM SHIN'S COUGH]
[Entering the room with a click]
Hurry up! Leave the buckwheat pancakes behind!
[SHAKING LEGS]
[KIM SHIN SNAPS OPEN THE PEN]
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
But who do I submit this statement to?
(Kim Shin)
Do I submit it directly?
I won't go that far
We must have made it so we wouldn't have to deal with that stuff
(Kim Shin)
Isn't it a problem if the handwriting is different?
(Grim Reaper)
I'll just say I wrote it with my left hand, so just write it.
But it's nice
The owner of the chicken place you go to often
[AN EXCLAMATION]
Did you meet?
You didn't say anything unnecessary, did you?
It wasn't a conversation that had any purpose.
[As he puts the pen down forcefully]
Did you say it? That I'm a grim reaper?
You said it too.
When I draw my sword, it returns to nothingness.
[THE GRIM REAPER'S LAUGHTER]
Did you really say it? Really?
Wow, how did you, hey, you really...
[The door suddenly opens]
[The grim reaper's surprised gasp]
[Exciting music]
(Grim Reaper)
What do I do, what do I do, what do I do
What do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do
[Kim Shin's Surprised Moan]
Oh, oh, it's coming
in, it's coming in, it's coming in (Man 2)
I'm
really sorry, but I'm in a hurry, can I please use the...
[RESTROOM?
MAN 2'S STRAINED MOAN]
You're human, right?
It's not a spirit; humans can't
enter here [Kim Shin's Surprised
Exclamation]
(Man 2)
Oh, please,
[OH NO, WHAT SHOULD I DO? MAN 2'S URGENT MOAN]
Thank, thank you
Thank, thank you, th, th...
[MAN 2'S STRAINED MOAN]
Wow
[The door opens and closes with a clack]
There is no door that the earnestness of humans cannot open
Even when I see it, I cannot believe it
While believing in the invisible god
Why can't I believe in the visible earnestness of humans?
(Kim Shin)
That's the will of humans
The power to change one's own fate
In the teahouse of the deceased
It's a sign of the human realm
[A SIGH MIXED WITH IRRITATION]
How should I write this statement of reasons
(Grim Reaper)
Sit down
You write this too
You've brought misfortune upon us
(Kim Shin)
You can just make a good fortune at home
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
[A SIGH]
[CHEWING GUM NOISILY]
Do you have a boyfriend?
[A SIGH]
[EXHALING A BREATH]
[THE DOOR OPENS WITH A CLACK]
(Eun Tak)
My name is Ji Eun Tak
[Sunny’s Sigh]
When I was nine years old
I lost my parents and became orphaned...
[A SIGH]
If you have any questions, feel free to ask
For reference, I can meet all the conditions of the boss
[SOFT MUSIC]
Do you have plans later?
No.
Then from today, it's our first day, let's work.
Yes, I'll take care of it seamlessly.
[SUNNY SNICKERS]
(Euntak)
But how did you end up in a better place?
[Sighing]
Life is either all or nothing.
I released my apartment lease.
How did you know to come, without calling?
I guess I have my own secret method.
[Mysterious sound effect]
This is ridiculous.
(Kid 1)
Hey, are you a beggar?
How can a kid not have even a thousand won?
(Kid 2)
There are no older brothers either!
(Child 1) So, if you tell me to
bring it, we’re fine - (Child 1)
Oh, damn - (Child
2) Ah! Don’t hit me!
Energy wave!
[CHILD 1'S SNICKER]
(Child 1) I think
this kid is crazy,
[SAYING ENERGY WAVE, CHILD 1'S LAUGHTER]
You keep watching these
cartoons That’s why your
mom is running away
(Euntak) Hey! You guys come
here cowardly, you should
get hit too, come here!
[THE KIDS ARE MUMBLING]
[EUNTAK'S ANGRY BREATHING]
[CALM MUSIC]
(Euntak) Are you okay?
One day you’ll be able to
shoot, real energy wave.
Where is your
house? Is it close?
[SIGH]
(Euntak)
The results must be out
Ah, what to do
Ah, I don't know, damn
[MOUSE CLICK SOUND]
[TAPPING ON THE KEYBOARD]
[NERVOUS BREATHING]
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
(Euntak)
What to do
[EUNTAK'S SURPRISED BREATH]
Ah, what to do
Wow, ah, wow
[EUNTAK'S JOYFUL SCREAM]
Well then, now
Let's print out the tuition bill
(Administrative staff)
It’s not an error
Someone has paid for you.
When the confirmation call comes,
you said to make sure to pass on your name,
It's Kim Shin.
[THE DOOR SWINGS OPEN AND SHUT]
(Eun-tak)
Kim Shin, have you paid my tuition fee?
Goodness.
You asked me to keep it a secret, but in the end,
you told me to say that I paid it for you?
[*CLEARS THROAT*]
They kept asking for names,
so I had no choice...
They kept asking for the examinee's name,
and I heard you kept giving your own name?
(Kim Shin)
I wonder if this is alright as a gift for passing and enrolling in college
This pretty thing
[THE BREATH OF EXCITEMENT]
It's alright, I'm totally
Wow, it's okay
(Kim Shin)
I knew it would be fine
[Eun-tak's breath of excitement]
Congratulations on your admission
[EUN-TAK'S JOYFUL GASP]
(Eun-tak)
I really missed you, unni
Bag, perfume, oh...
(Kim Shin)
I don't have five hundred, I used it for tuition
Mister
Don't get too emotional, I'm just lending it to you.
(Eun-tak)
That's right
Why did you just give it to me at first
and now you're lending it to me?
How can a person's feelings change?
You're the only person in this house
If you still don't realize that, what should I do?
Wow
(Kim-shin)
You have to pay back 5,208 won every month
over 80 years
You can't miss even a month
80 years?
(Kim-shin)
Yeah, you can't pay it back faster either
Why, do you not want to?
No
If your will is at this level
I've made up my mind
I've decided, I have
What?
Date
[LIVELY MUSIC IS PLAYING]
(Euntak)
You fool, when I was at the ski resort
not the report card
If you had brought this bag
I would have quickly come along
Wow, I was just about to do that
- Did the grim reaper stop you?
- Yes
As expected, the grim reaper saved a life
(Euntak)
If not
I would have killed you on the spot
Don’t eat my food, eat yours
I ate all of mine.
[Eun-tak's Laughter]
(Kim Shin)
Don't keep eating while laughing
Just one bite
But
What else?
Is there love somewhere in these things?
Look closely, I tried to include it
[SHE SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(Secretary Kim)
Here is the list of preferred gifts for high school and university girls that you mentioned
(Chairman Yoo)
BTS?
What kind of boys are these?
♪ Why are you shaking my heart
shaking it ♪
(Chairman Yoo)
Oh, it's about doing things that touch the heart.
These days, I'm shaking things up a lot.
(Chairman Yoo)
EXO? Is EXO a drink?
No.
(Secretary Kim)
♪ Growl, growl, growl ♪
[Chairman Yoo's laughter]
(Chairman Yoo)
Being a secretary is indeed an extreme job.
Well, well.
I always work joyfully.
I'll make the gift three times.
(Secretary Kim)
Ah...
(Chairman Yoo)
I also know about digital cameras.
[Chairman Yoo's Laughter]
(Secretary Kim)
Ah, yes
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
[Camera operation sound]
[Camera shutter sound]
(Chairman Yoo)
[CAMERA OPERATION SOUND]
[Camera shutter sound]
(Chairman Yoo)
[CAMERA OPERATION SOUND]
Oh, you startled me
Ah, goodness, oh, you surprised me
(Deokhwa)
When have you been here
and why are you here?
No, why are you so surprised?
Did I do something wrong?
You were surprised because of my face
(Deokhwa)
Aren't I good-looking?
Ha, that's too much, going overboard
(Euntak)
You say you have no money, so why a camera?
Ah, this is yours
Why is this mine?
(Deokhwa)
It's a gift from my grandfather
[surprised breath]
My selfie is the gift I give
Really?
[EUNTAK'S BREATH OF EXCITEMENT]
That's touching
I've only received a building as a gift until now
You get to receive a digital camera, how nice
Please tell the chairman that I'm really really grateful.
(Eun-tak)
Please give me my camera
Just 10 minutes
- Please
- Just 5 minutes
- 5 minutes...
(Deok-hwa)
[Pleading]
Just 5 minutes
- (Eun-tak) Ah, please
- (Deok-hwa) 5 minutes... 3 minutes, 3 minutes
- (Eun-tak) Ah, I said please
- (Deok-hwa) Ah, even 3 minutes...
- (Eun-tak) Ah, please
- (Deok-hwa) 3 minutes, 3 minutes
- (Deok-hwa) Huh? It's a goblin!
- (Eun-tak) Oh dear...
[EUN-TAK'S STARTLED GASP]
[EUN-TAK'S IRRITATED SOUND]
(Grim Reaper)
Indeed, a house needs to have children
to feel like a place where people live and such.
[KIM SHIN CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
The afterlife registry?
Hasn't come yet?
If it had, you would have mentioned it
I was indeed curious
about what your plan is.
Do you remember that time
when the man came in
through the door of your tea house?
[THE GRIM REAPER CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
How could I forget?
But?
There is no door that the human's desperation can't open,
and sometimes, that one opened door
might just be a variable in God's plan, don't you think?
(Kim Shin)
So I've been looking for it, desperately
What door should I open
that could be a variable in God's plan
I don’t know if it will take a hundred years or ten months
But for now, I’m going to try to make
the choice next to that child
Well, then
I don’t know which door I might end up opening
I just hope it's not my own
But isn’t it a bit petty for God's plan to have variables?
[THE GRIM REAPER'S DISSATISFIED BREATH]
What reason does God have to stop him?
I just heard my heart beating a little?
(Deokhwa)
Uncles
[Deokhwa's hurried footsteps]
[Camera operation sound]
[Camera shutter sound]
(Euntak)
Me too, me too, me too, me too
(Deokhwa)
Alright, I'll take the picture
[Grumpy sound of the Grim Reaper]
[SOFT MUSIC]
Ah, what are you doing? Don't move aside
Let's take one picture just the two of us
(Grim Reaper)
No, I was sitting first
[Deokhwa's displeased groan]
I'm going to take it.
[THE GRIM REAPER'S GROANING]
[THE LAUGHTER OF KIM SHIN AND EUN TAK]
[THE SOUND OF THE CAMERA SHUTTER]
(Grim Reaper)
I have a question, if you answer, step aside
(Eun Tak)
Oh, what is it now?
Reversing during a storm
Solving math problems with a compass
Laughing when talking
[The grim reaper's sigh]
Giving space when walking
I have no idea what our boss likes
Prepare everything
What are you doing, since earlier?
Contacting after a million years
It's dangerous, so I'm trying to guide you to the inside of the sidewalk.
Is it really that unnatural?
You said you have something to say, so let's start with that.
(Sunny)
I'm dying of curiosity.
Religion, no religion.
What?
(Sunny)
How come you speak so well?
Do you perhaps have a religion?
Have you been thinking about that all this time?
I feel like I couldn't let you know.
[Soft music]
[Awkward laughter]
But why are you laughing so much since a while ago?
(Sunny)
Is my makeup weird or something?
Isn't that cute?
Where are you going?
(Sunny)
Why didn't you meet me on Christmas?
It would have been cute if you had called that day
What did you do?
You probably didn't go to church since you're not religious
Christmas is a bit like that
(Grim Reaper)
Still, it's someone's birthday
It's a kind of moral obligation
But I'm not religious?
Isn't it really not cute?
Ah, goosebumps
Well, not that much
No, it's déjà vu
(Sunny)
[Surprised]
I feel like I've seen this scene somewhere
Wow, it's so vivid, oh, I'm getting chills
(Euntak)
You don't have to see me off
You should have said that earlier, why wait until everyone comes to say it
See you later
Huh? It's the grim reaper
(Euntak)
He accounts for
a large portion of our store's sales,
that guy
Unlike others
Tch, how much is one chicken?
I think I might buy the whole store
Oh, but I'm scared of chicken blood
I saw it all when I was doing the
background check, it's not that I'm
scared in the book I'm just keeping
my distance (Euntak) Wait, so
back then you were trying to get me
a part-time job at the chicken place?
To keep me at a distance?
Ah, when are you talking about...
(Euntak) Right, it
was all in that context.
I didn't even know that,
but it's fine, since I
know now, just go.
I'm going to live here for
a thousand years, so
don't come looking for me.
Coward, what, what, what coward?
Ah, I've never heard
that before It's really the
first time, really the people
have said that to me, huh?
(Kim Shin)
'Wow! Hooray!'
[SIGH]
Do you show me how brave I am?
[SNORT]
(Eun Tak)
Where are you going in?
Our boss
is not an ordinary person
[PLAYFUL MUSIC]
[SIGH]
[EUN TAK'S COUGH]
[Sunny's cough]
[Eun Tak's puzzled moan]
(Sunny)
Is it that guy who gives you the cold shoulder?
[EUN TAK'S AWKWARD SMILE]
I can hear everything, boss
(Kim Shin)
[Imitating the Grim Reaper]
Don't you recognize my voice?
It’s not a voice you can forget
That call back then?
[THE GRIM REAPER'S AWKWARD LAUGHTER]
I can hear everything, shut up!
Was that so?
(Sunny)
Really nice to see you again
I’m surprised you two are friends
I came looking for you, to the previous store
(Eun Tak)
Ah, I see
- How much did you talk...
- Didn’t say much
(Sunny)
Oh, didn’t say anything
So I still don’t know your identity
Excuse me, but how old are you?
Knowing it's rude, why are you asking?
[AN ABSURD BREATH]
(Sunny)
Yet you subtly avoid answering, huh?
(Kim Shin)
It's not subtle; it's outright not answering.
(Sunny)
And then you drop the formalities, what's up with that?
What's up with that?
It's more complicated than it looks, there's more to my age.
[EUNTAK'S SIGH]
(Euntak)
[Clapping the table]
Come on, if you've eaten enough, please leave.
It's almost time for the guests to arrive.
I haven't even finished eating yet.
No, you've eaten everything.
Please just go home now.
The atmosphere here is
too strange because of you!
(Euntak)
Guest?
Guests, please get up and
leave together, both of you, hurry!
(Together)
No!
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
(Grim Reaper) Look,
polynomial, 'What is X?
' 'What is X?
'
right?
What are you doing? (Grim Reaper)
[YOU REALLY DON'T UNDERSTAND WOMEN]
It seems you don't know the answer, do you? Just drink.
The grim reaper's cough. Excuse me, Mr. Kim Seon.
[Exciting music]
(Reaper)
Could I get two more beers, please?
Who?
(Reaper)
Two beers...
Could you please look at me for a second, separately outside?
(Reaper)
Ah, sure, go ahead.
What is it?
What do you mean?
A moment ago
You called me 'Kim Sun.'
Why is that...
How did you know my name?
I don't think I've ever told you my real name.
(Reaper)
[In a strained voice]
Sorry, but we didn't meet today.
(Sunny)
I’m asking how you knew.
Why wouldn’t I know?!
You said 'Kim Sunny.'
Oh, it’s really cold, isn’t it? I’ll get my coat...
(Sunny)
I’m not finished talking yet.
[Meaningful sound effect]
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
(Reaper)
Something is wrong.
Maybe
It seems to start with you.
[A SURPRISED GASP]
[EXCITING MUSIC]
What on earth
Why...
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
(Grim Reaper)
The woman in the scroll is Kim Shin's sister.
(Sunny)
What did this ring mean?
(Grim Reaper)
The moment I first saw the woman in the scroll, I cried.
(Jungheon)
In this world, under my emperor's feet.
That emperor under my feet.
You bastard!
You bitch!
(Kim Shin)
I will
carry out the command.
Do you even know what you’re asking for before you ask it?
You must come to see me often.
(Kim Shin)
Do you know what this interest is about before you meet?
Is it the grim reaper?
I was contemplating whether to hold Sunny's hand once more
So, is it not okay to hold it today?
If only I could hold it when she was a year younger
(Grim Reaper)
Could it be that the history of the two
is related to my erased memories?
(Chairman Yoo)
Yes
I suppose it is meant to be
[CHAIRMAN YOO'S LAUGHTER]
[CHAIRMAN YOO'S SIGH]
Subtitle: Choi Hyeran