[THEME SONG]
(Ghost)
[English]
I see you again
(Euntak)
[Korean]
That's right
[THE SOUND OF FOOTSTEPS ECHOES]
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
'That's right'?
(Euntak)
Did I just say 'That's right'?
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECTS]
[English]
I'm waiting!
(Street vendor)
Miss
(Euntak)
Me?
It's nice to see you like this
Do you know me?
No
That necklace you're wearing
(Euntak)
This one?
I made it
(Street vendor)
I made it at the request of some man
It's been at least 10 years
10 years?
What kind of man?
The person who received it would know better
Do you know what that means?
No
(Street vendor)
In French,
it means 'The destiny given by the heavens'
An absolute fate that transcends human realms
Are you living happily with the person who gave it to you?
[THE STREET VENDOR SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(Kim Shin)
[Japanese]
What is this?
[Playful music]
[Sipping the drink]
[THE DOOR OPENS WITH A CLICK]
[Russian]
Thank you
[A SIGH]
[SIPPING THE DRINK]
[THE DOOR CLOSES WITH A CLICK]
[Korean]
Stop it, we have nowhere else to go now
There’s only one place I haven’t been
Where that kid is
Then let’s go there, I’ll allow it
Can I go?
If I go there
Can I confuse that kid?
(Grim Reaper)
Can I confuse you?
It’s driving me crazy
My heart feels empty, that's why
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
[A SIGH]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[GRAND MUSIC]
(Grim Reaper)
Are you insane?
[THE COFFIN RATTLES]
[KIM SHIN COUGHS]
(Grim Reaper)
Oh, man
No, they say he lived a long time
Aren't you going to take him away soon?
Before an international conflict arises
Take him away quickly
[THE GRIM REAPER CLICKS HIS TONGUE]
(Kim Shin)
Cough, let's go, oh man
That guy is really scary when he's mad
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[THE DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
[A SIGH]
(Eun-tak)
Ah, I'm really strange today, seriously
How did we run into each other here?
I'm on a business trip
I needed that, the reference for the corner of the furniture
What are you talking about
What do you mean
Have you been well?
Did you follow me by any chance?
If so, should we get caught?
- What should we do?
- I'm not a bad person
How should I know that?
You wouldn't know if you hang out with me, would you?
There's no reason to hang out with you.
Well, our company has sponsored the PD's program
(Kim Shin)
At that time, you definitely said you would buy me a meal
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
Director, it’s your first time in Canada, right?
So, let’s go this way
But did I say I was going to Canada?
(Eun Tak)
I think you just said abroad
(Kim Shin)
I think I did
Well, I feel like I heard something about the maple country
Ah, maple country!
Yes, I remembered
(Eun Tak)
Um
This way
[LIVELY MUSIC]
(Kim Shin)
Is this enough?
[EUNTAK CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
(Euntak)
It's okay, it feels like a picnic and it's nice.
(Kim Shin)
Ah, I'm not talking about the PD.
I'm asking if this is enough for me.
I already sponsored quite a bit for the PD.
[EUNTAK COUGHS]
(Euntak)
Ah, this is not
[coughing]
the trip I planned,
it just came suddenly
I could only exchange a little money, the exchange.
- What do you like?
- So-yo.
I don’t really like meat.
Do you like me?
How do you know?
[Smiling slightly]
Oh, is there someone who doesn’t like meat?
(Euntaek)
No, don’t beat around the bush.
Representative, did you perhaps
conduct a background check on me?
Like, whether your family matches with the chaebol or not
something like that?
[Chuckling]
Who says they’re dating you?
You're actually not that great.
But still, I need to buy the meat.
It sounds delicious, I’ll call you later.
[Snapping up the cup]
Then I'll be going now
[EUNTAK SUDDENLY DROPS THE CUP]
There’s nothing much here, this way
I’ll guide you
[EUNTAK CLEARS HIS THROAT]
Is it okay for me to do this?
I was worried it might be too much trouble
It’s fine, even if it’s a bother
It must be because you were excited
You seem to know Quebec well? Have you been here?
(Kim Shin)
Yes, I came with my first love
This is our fourth time together
(Euntak)
Ah
So you have a girlfriend
We broke up now
(Euntak)
Why did you break up?
(Kim Shin)
I was away for a really long time
It must have been really hard
I guess they forgot all about me
It's just how first loves never come true
I guess you loved her a lot?
I suppose so
Seeing how hard this is to bear
What are you trying to endure?
I want to hold hands
I want to hug, that kind of thing
[SOFT MUSIC]
The woman has forgotten everything
(Euntak)
So you haven't been able to forget her, huh?
Yes
Not even for a single day, not even for a single moment
[Kicking the fallen leaves with my feet]
I bet she's happy
Do you happen to know that?
(Kim Shin)
If you catch a falling maple leaf
Your love with the person you walked with
will come true
[EUNTAK'S HOLLOW LAUGH]
Did that person from my first love tell you?
Yes, I caught a maple leaf too
(Euntak)
But do you believe that?
Even if I catch it, it didn't come true
You're walking with me right now
It didn't come true
You have a crush on me, right?
Men talk about their
exes to girls they are into.
(Eun-tak) Like a fool
- (Kim Shin) Is that so?
- Isn't it?
[EUNTAK TURNS OFF THE FAUCET]
Oh my, are you an idiot? Are you in high school?
Do you believe that catching maple leaves
will bring love?
Oh dear, you've totally been caught by a girl
and you don't even realize it
Oh dear, you're a fool, a fool
[SIGH]
What are you, anyway?
(Street Vendor)
[English]
Is the person who gave you that
living happily with you?
[Korean]
I don’t remember.
I don't know where the memories start
[SIGH]
Oh my
(Euntak)
Nothing is coming to mind
It's not coming to mind
Tsk, let's just go ask
That would be faster
Why are you here?
Are you staying at this hotel?
- Yes
- (Euntak) Ah
But excuse me
(Euntak)
Have we possibly
met before?
About 10 years ago?
(Euntak)
Sir!
This kind of line
isn't a pickup line, you know.
I just keep feeling strange
[SIGH]
[KIM SHIN'S SIGH]
Do you like me?
No, I'm not doing this for work
Yes
[CALM MUSIC]
You say you like me
(Eun Tak)
By the way, I
don't have a boyfriend
I guess I just have no ties with guys in this life
That's just how it is
Then I'll take my leave
Enjoy your walk
- (Kim Shin) Excuse me
- (Eun Tak) Excuse me
[SHE SMILES SLIGHTLY]
Let's talk first.
It turns out that a sandwich just won't do.
How about an early dinner? Aren't you hungry?
I'll treat you.
I was actually trying to say we should eat together.
I know a place with delicious beef.
[smirking slightly]
Beef.
(Euntak)
[sighs]
I wasn't thinking clearly.
I didn't bring my sneakers, and my feet are killing me.
[Sunny smiles slightly]
Even if your feet hurt, at least you looked nice, it's okay.
"Next time, I have to remember to bring my sneakers."
You realized it, right?
(Eun-tak)
So, I mean, I should
have visited a foreign country
(Sunny)
Why, of all times,
during my "a-ha!" year, would I go abroad?
When I was twenty-nine
I didn’t even go to the supermarket in front of my house.
[Employee 1 pours water gently]
Really?
[English]
Thank you (Sunny)
[Korean]
Uh,
I don’t have any promises (Eun-tak)
But still, I don’t look like someone who's come
to a foreign country for the first time
I’m really doing well, just a bit of
wandering, and I’m not starving
I’ll eat a big piece of beef; I’m at a nice restaurant with some guy.
What if the restaurant is nice?
The man should be nice.
I'm sleepy, let's hang up.
[LAUGHTER]
Yes, sleep well.
(Kim Shin)
So the future I saw was right.
[SOFT MUSIC]
CEO, over here.
(Kim Shin)
You met that guy who's the CEO after all.
I can't hide my smile, so this is quite awkward.
[KIM SHIN SMILES FAINTLY]
Did you perhaps come here with your first love?
You must have fed them something really expensive.
But it turned out to be useless, forgot it all.
Did you see them after breaking up?
(Kim Shin)
Yes.
(Eun Tak)
Ah.
[SIGH]
(Eun Tak)
First loves are originally
beautified and altered in memories.
They say when you see them again, they're really nothing special.
Not at all, they're still pretty.
(Eun Tak)
[English]
Over here!
[Korean]
I want to order, have you chosen?
(Kim Shin)
Ah, yes.
- (Kim Shin) I...
- (Eun Tak) Not just still pretty.
(Eun Tak)
How about just being pretty right now?
I'm just starting to look pretty these days.
Of course, that's my opinion.
Shall we meet again tomorrow?
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
I have a flight tomorrow afternoon.
Before I go, and even after I go,
[Sunny taps the keyboard]
(Employee 2)
Welcome.
You didn't come out today either?
(The Grim Reaper)
Please just deliver this.
Somehow, I wanted to go to work.
[SUNNY'S SIGH]
By any chance
[SPARKLING SOUND EFFECT]
Whoa, oh, ah, I was surprised.
The person you were looking for...
Yes, it's you, Andy Lau?
I'm the landlord (Sunny) Do you remember the chicken
restaurant that was on the first floor of that building 9 years ago?
Of course, you often fell behind on
the rent, but what brings you here?
You sent a letter
through this person, right?
Can I get this person's
contact information?
This person? This isn't
my contact information?
I'm kind of busy, you know?
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
[CONTEMPLATIVE BREATH SOUNDS]
[SATISFACTORY MOAN]
Ah, let’s see, a place just starting
for lovers A rather secluded spot...
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECTS]
There's nothing special here, this way
[A SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
This person
Is he the representative?
(Euntak)
Representative
Are you perhaps a ghost?
Did you die at that time?
So that's why you kept appearing in front of me?
Do you still
see the dead?
'Still'?
How do you know I saw ghosts?
Who are you?
Are you really a ghost?
(Euntak)
How do you know I saw ghosts?!
Is your name
Kim Shin?
You came here with me 10 years ago, right?
But why can't I remember anything?
Answer me, who are you?
Why did I write not to forget you?
Why did I write that you're my bride?
You're Kim Shin, aren't you?
Right?
No.
It's late, so let's go back to the hotel.
[A SIGH]
[CALM MUSIC]
[SUNNY'S SIGH]
Why aren't you surprised?
(The Grim Reaper)
Excuse me?
I just sat down here all of a sudden
Why
aren't you surprised?
(Sunny)
Do you know who I am?
It's definitely a familiar look, right?
No, this is the first time we meet...
You just sat down, so you
came to our store, right?
With that producer's
letter (Reaper)
Yes, I cried on the
street (Sunny)
[slightly
smiling]
It was cold, and I
remembered because a grown man was
walking while crying
I wondered, did you cry because of me?
There are many surprised people
But
not many who cry; it's not such a
common face resembling some woman, but me
Anyway, let's introduce ourselves.
What's your name?
Wang Ye.
Sounds like a royal name.
(Sunny)
I'm Sunny.
S, U, N, N, Y
[SHE SMILES SLIGHTLY]
I've wanted to see you.
I saw you on CCTV.
You're so good-looking.
I was really curious about how handsome you'd be in person.
But the screen is better.
[A HOLLOW LAUGH]
(Sunny)
Thank you for delivering the letter.
Thanks to you, our PD Ji got to go abroad and
I've seen you in person, so I'll stop by now.
I need to get back to work.
It's cold, so don’t walk around crying.
Your face will freeze.
(Grim Reaper)
Nice to meet you.
[Melancholic music]
I was glad to meet you.
[SHE SOBS]
[SUNNY SNIFFLES]
I was also
happy to meet you.
Mr. Kim Woo-bin.
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
(Eun-tak)
Remember.
You must remember.
[Sobbing]
That person's name is Kim Shin.
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
What kind of rain is this?
Why isn't the part-timer here?
[SOUND OF CELLPHONE MANIPULATION]
What on earth is happening?
[THE RAIN POURS DOWN]
(Sunny)
Oh? You scared me!
Hey, why are you doing that?
Grandma hasn't come in yet.
No, then you should go in at least.
(Sunny)
You're Eun-tak's friend, right?
Come in first, Eun-tak's sister isn't here.
I canceled my part-time job today.
Come here, come here.
(Sunny)
Oh my, oh my, goodness.
[SUNNY'S HEARTRENDING MOAN]
(Sunny)
Here, it's hot.
Blow on it and drink.
[SUNNY'S STRAINED MOAN]
When will Grandma arrive?
It's later tonight, I'm going to earn money
Your fate is really cold
There are many people colder than me, my grandmother said
You're kind
Anyway, the problem is God, right?
Shouldn't he share things a bit
So that only cold people are completely cold
Isn't that so? No common sense at all, anyway
[Sunny is crushing the snacks]
If you say that, you'll be punished
It's okay
Auntie has experienced all sorts of things with goblins and grim reapers
So it's fine to curse a bit
(Sunny)
It made me remember my past life, then tried to
erase it—how many people are
suffering from that author, I don’t know.
Isn’t forgetting a
courtesy from the gods?
[The sky rumbles] Thunder
[RUMBLES SO WE WON’T SUFFER]
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
Tch, hey, who do you think you
are, huh? Who are you to decide?
(Sunny)
Do you see that?
[MAJESTIC MUSIC]
In my store, even water is
self-service; my life is
self-service, my memories are mine,
but without even asking
why does it have to be decided by you?
[SUNNY'S SIGH]
My life is something I want to handle on my own.
I wish that author would just go away.
This lady.
[SIGH]
Yes, I understand.
Tsk, who are you to know?
[SNORT]
[THE SKY RUMBLES]
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
[THE SOUND OF FLAPPING WINGS ECHOES]
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECTS]
[Worker 1's strained groan]
(Worker 2)
Ah, right, uh, just a little bit more.
Thank you, ah.
[Worker 2's strained groan]
[Lion's surprised groan]
- (Lion) Be careful.
- (Worker 2) Ah, yes.
[The lion smiles slightly]
(Sunny)
Are you moving?
Yes, I've been saving money diligently.
Still, I'll eat chicken there.
[SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(Sunny)
Come on over, I'll give you a discount.
You’re working hard.
- (Eun-tak) I will carry this.
- (Worker 3) Ah, yes.
[Meaningful music]
[Workers are busy]
(Eun-tak)
Hello.
I moved in today, to the rooftop.
Please take good care of me.
Ah...
Then
It's our first day starting today
Yes
(Customer)
Over here
Yes, ah, just a moment
(Employee 2)
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
[A STARTLED BREATH]
Brother?
[A WELCOME SMILE]
[SOBBING]
[THE GRIM REAPER IS SOBBING]
[THE GRIM REAPER KEEPS SOBBING]
(Sunny)
My oblivion
[significant sound effect]
To you, whom I thought was my peace
[SUNNY TAPS THE KEYBOARD]
(Sunny)
The moment our eyes met, I knew.
[HEAVY MUSIC]
You too keep all the memories
That's why in this life we
(the grim reaper)
You alone
I hope for a happy ending like this
[Tapping the keyboard]
(Sunny)
In each of our happy endings
We have to pretend we don’t know this tragedy
Hopefully in the next life we
A man whose meetings are short and whose waits are long
(Sunny)
With a short wait and a long meeting as fate
Religion, no religion
[SMILES SLIGHTLY]
Did you call ten
times to say that?
(Sunny) A face that can
be met without any excuses.
With a desperate name that is
the only one in this world [sobs]
What is this?
Is this a coincidence?
(Sunny) If we happen
to run into each other
While running over to greet.
My clumsy actions
They're all incorrect.
(Sunny) With love that
is always the answer
I hope we meet like that.
(Grim Reaper)
Nice to
meet you
(Sunny)
Now that I've seen your face, that's enough
Yes
Kim Woo-bin
(Sunny)
Maybe Kim Woo-bin
Wang Ye
(Sunny)
Maybe you are Wang Ye
Please, for a long time
Goodbye
[SOBBING]
[SNIFFLING]
[DEOK-HWA'S PUZZLED BREATHING]
(Deok-hwa)
Why did the chicken restaurant owner
ask for the number of Uncle in the last room?
Who is Ji Eun-tak, who was written in that letter?
[SIGH]
Why does it feel like I'm the only one who doesn't know?
Of course, being a chaebol means you should go through
some degree of amnesia
Ah, but
I feel like I might have been
really important during that time
[SIGH]
[SOFT MUSIC]
(Kim Shin)
I had a short-sighted thought
If you've forgotten
You're someone who can be forgotten
I just really
wanted to see you
[SIGH]
[HEAVY SOUND EFFECT]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
(Eun Tak)
Mister
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
(Eun Tak)
If I catch the falling maple leaves
- The person I walked with
- (Kim Shin) The person I walked with
- (Eun Tak) They say love comes true
- (Kim Shin) Love comes true
(Eun Tak)
No matter how I think about it
I feel like you’re a goblin, uncle
I love you
[SHE SMILES SLIGHTLY]
Where is the sorrow that lasts for a thousand years?
Where is the love that lasts for a thousand years
(Eun Tak)
I vote for 'there is'
Which side will you bet on?
Sorrow or love?
[Choking up]
Sad love
I missed you
(Kim Shin)
I won't let you go
Why? Is it because I'm a goblin's bride?
[THE MUSIC BUILDS UP THE ATMOSPHERE]
[I BLOW AIR THROUGH MY LIPS]
[I SOB]
I want to see you
Where are you?
I want to see you!
[Mysterious sound effect]
[Eun-tak's surprised breath]
(Eun-tak)
Thinking about it, it's so amazing
You said it was going to come with rain, and you said it was going to come with snow
It really came with snow, on the day of the first snow.
'Eul responds to Gap's summons every year on the first day of snow.'
(Kim Shin)
'Because Gap will be waiting.'
Was it really because of that vow?
Really
(Eun Tak)
I told you not to go like that
How can you go?
Even if it was the best choice
How could I...
I'm sorry
Since you kept your promise
[Soft music]
(Eun Tak)
But what did it mean to return to nothing?
Not being able to see you
Without knowing the reason
When it rained, I felt
like a crazy woman.
(Euntak)
I’ve been in pain, crying, and muttering alone
Even with medication, it doesn’t help
Out of respect for the love I received
I should have lived well and cheerfully
I’m sorry
From now on, I’ll make you happy continuously
(Kimshin)
It seems like you’re saying this without awareness
Why do you keep touching me
It’s quite troublesome
I’m trying to confirm
(Euntak)
I’m in a daze
I thought it wasn’t a dream
It’s not a dream
(Euntak)
Such a dream
I’ve had it too many times
It’s not a dream
I can't believe it anymore
(Eun-tak)
I'm so surprised
My heart is still racing
[KIM SHIN'S SIGH]
Should I do something even more amazing?
[MYSTICAL SOUND EFFECT]
I can buy everything from there to here
In a lump sum
(Eun-tak)
Oh
Then alcohol
[Clinking beer cans]
What about you, uncle?
Sounds good
[POPPING OPEN A BEER CAN]
[EUN-TAK'S EXCITED BREATHING]
[WE EXHALE TOGETHER]
But what about the title?
(Euntaek)
Ugh, isn't 'uncle' a bit much now?
'Oppa' is a bit weird too
Well, in 10 years we'll be the same age now
So how about just from now on
'Hey, you'?
(Kim Shin)
No
[EUNTAEK'S LAUGHTER]
(Euntaek)
Hmm
That's right
Have you met the boss?
Just from a distance, I’m all alone
The boss has made a lot of money
and has become a property owner
(Euntaek)
I wonder if it's thanks to Brother Boshin visiting
Anyway, I'm doing well.
Have you met the Grim Reaper?
Is he still living in my house?
I don't know if he's doing well,
but now I've really formed a friendship with him,
[AND KIM SHIN CLICKS HIS TONGUE]
(Kim Shin)
It's been like that for a while now.
[HE SMILES SLIGHTLY]
The fate of the two of you is truly,
[SIGHS KIM SHIN]
[SOFT MUSIC]
I also
really wanted to see you, a lot.
I love you.
(Eun-tak)
A lot.
There he goes again, tsk.
I also want to spend more time with Kim Shin.
I haven't taken much vacation
(Euntak)
I'm human, so
I have to take a taxi to the airport from here
and leave an immigration record
Otherwise, I'll get handcuffed
I'll come visit
Ah, this guy
(Euntak)
Or do you want to fly with me?
Wow, that's fresh
You don't want to? It's with me
I want to, but I don't have my passport
I rushed over and didn't have time
[SIGH]
About seventeen hours later
I'll see you in Korea
Hmm, when are we going?
I’ll be late, let’s go
Just one more minute
Just one more time
[EUNTAK SMILES SLIGHTLY]
[LAUGHTER]
[EUNTAK'S DELIGHTFUL MOAN]
(Euntak)
Did you wait a long time?
(Kim Shin)
Seventeen hours, I thought I was going to die
The gate opened, and I see you perfectly, wow
[Euntak smiles slightly]
(Euntak)
There was no angel, right?
Angels do exist
[Kim Shin's laughter]
(Euntak)
Let go of my hand, I dare you to let go
(Kim Shin)
Absolutely not
[EUNTAK'S SURPRISED MOAN]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
(Euntak)
Wow!
Did you forget that my boyfriend is a goblin?
Wow, this is cheating
I’m really excited right now?
Ha, Uncle, behind the door
there's always a wonderful place
(Euntak)
I forgot, I
[THE SUITCASE IS ABOUT TO FALL]
[SOFT MUSIC]
(Employee 2)
Welcome
Huh? Director
Where's the boss?
Oh, you should call him
He didn’t come today
I guess he made enough money
Got it, take care
[CALL CONNECTION SOUND]
Where have you gone?
Are you busy?
[MOBILE PHONE MANIPULATION SOUND]
(Deceased 1)
I'm a bit nervous
It's silly at my age
It's a long way
You’ll be here soon
70 years of time probably didn’t pass
As slowly as it does now
[SIGH]
[THE SCENERY RINGS]
[SAD MUSIC]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[A SURPRISED BREATH]
[DECEASED 2 INHALES]
I’m very late
How many years has it been since we last met?
73 years
(Spirit 1)
It was the first birthday since our marriage
They said they'd come as soon as the training was over
They said they would come without delay
But the ceasefire line has been drawn, hasn't it?
(Spirit 2)
That's right
[THE TREMBLING BREATH OF SPIRIT 2]
I thought it would clear up soon
But it took this long, huh
[I SMILE SOFTLY]
Now that we're all old, we can't even flirt
(Spirit 2)
Still
Beautiful
I've been ruined waiting for you
. What is beautiful?
(Spirit 1)
If you're going to make me wait this long
I'll be coming right away," he said.
(The Grim Reaper)
"Please sit and have a chat."
"The tea seems to have cooled down, so I think we need to heat it up."
"Because it's cold outside."
"Thank you very much."
(The Deceased 2)
"I have no regrets seeing your face like this."
(The Deceased 1)
"So, where are you buried?"
"Are you buried somewhere warm?"
(The Deceased 2)
"I was buried up North."
"In spring, that mountain was full of azaleas."
"Is it late?"
"Oh, an unexpected deceased has come."
"You have an unexpected guest as well.
Grim Reaper
[EUNTAK SMILES SLIGHTLY]
Is it now Mr. Grim Reaper?
Other missing persons
This is really an unexpected development
I remembered everything, you recognized me
[EUNTAK SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(Euntak)
'Other missing persons'
It's been a really long time since I heard that
I've heard everything
How can you know everything
and not come to see me even once?
(Grim Reaper)
What good is it for a human to meet the Grim Reaper anyway
It's been a long time, Other missing persons
I'm listening to the radio well
It's been a long time
It's been way too long
I'm already twenty-nine
Twenty-nine?
I see
[HE CHUCKLES SLIGHTLY]
(Grim Reaper)
Let's eat, just wash your hands and come out
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
(Grim Reaper)
Shall I tell you a secret?
Yes
(Grim Reaper)
Even at twenty-nine,
you'll meet the Grim Reaper
Even if it's not me
That's the fate of other missing persons
The living world needs order
And nine is the number of God and the number of completeness
It's an unfinished number closest to nineteen.
Do well on this too.
In the end, you
met me even at twenty-nine.
The grim reaper.
(Doctor)
Ms. Ji Eun-tak, hasn't it been less than a month?
Is there a possibility that the symptoms...
(Eun-tak)
No, I'm here to greet you.
I wanted to thank you for everything.
Thank you.
Thank you for keeping me alive.
Otherwise,
I would have truly been unhappy.
I just remembered how to be happy now.
(Doctor)
That's great.
But what is that method?
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
[Blows air through the
mouth] [Mystical sound effect]
(Euntak) Ah, it seems your meat
smell cravings haven't changed.
Ah, I just put the
frying pan on the
fire, hold on a second.
Ah, have you eaten?
If you haven't, let's
[EAT TOGETHER AND LAUGH]
[LAUGHTER]
[BLOWS AIR THROUGH THE MOUTH]
[MYSTICAL SOUND EFFECT]
[LAUGHTER]
(Euntak) Oh, look at that
book I was holding 9 years
ago I'm holding it again. When
am I going to read all of this?
(Kim Shin) A true man reads the same book
a hundred times and writes a hundred times...
Oh!
[LAUGHTER]
Look at you lying, cute
[EUNTAK'S LAUGHTER]
- Can you tell?
- (Euntak) Yes
[APPLICATION SOUND EFFECT]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
What is this? Where is this?
[EUNTAK SMILES SLIGHTLY]
It's under the blanket
You, you are very sexy, huh?
If you don't like it, you can go
(Euntak)
Ah, it's warm
(Kim Shin)
Uh, no, why, why are you doing this now?
It's warm so I'm sleepy
[SURPRISED BREATH SOUNDS]
[TREMBLING BREATH SOUNDS]
[BLOWING AIR THROUGH LIPS]
One, two, three
Four, five
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
(Kim Shin)
What’s happening?
[EUNTAK'S SCARED BREATH SOUNDS]
(Euntak)
I was so scared
I was wondering if this is all a dream
I’m still wondering if I’m in a dream
[SCARED BREATH SOUNDS]
(Kim Shin)
It’s not a dream
You were surprised, at this dawn
[EUNTAK'S TREMBLING BREATH SOUNDS]
Next time, appear in thirty thousand, understood?
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC]
Don’t go anywhere, understood?
I got it, I won't go anywhere
[Euntak's trembling breath]
Let's lie down
Even though you left
[A SIGH OF RELIEF]
I'm sorry
[SOUND OF ADJUSTING THE BED]
[A BIRD CHIRPS]
(Sunny)
Hey, big brother?
Why are you staring at my house after leaving Director Ji's house?
Could it be that restaurant?
Restaurant?
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
[SIGNIFICANT MUSIC]
[SUNNY'S LAUGHTER]
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
(Kim Shin)
So that's how it is
In the end, you're going down that path.
As long as you’re smiling, that’s all that matters.
Who is smiling? Am I smiling right now?
[LAUGHTER]
How can one’s nature be so consistent...
(Kim Shin)
Even if it’s not now,
it ultimately means that as long as you laugh, it’s enough.
(Sunny)
No, where are you going looking like that?
Why are you going out the front door? Hey!
[SAD MUSIC]
[sighing]
Our part-timer
Please make me happy, brother
This unsightly sister
will also be happy.
[DEOK-HWA YAWNS]
(Grim Reaper)
[Slamming the plate down]
Where have you been since this morning?
Scalpel
[THE GRIM REAPER SLICES THE BREAD]
Uncle from the last room
(Deokhwa)
What's that watch? I'm jealous
Due to my job, I have to be precise with time
The Grim Reaper is sleek in black
(Grim Reaper)
I like it
Is this your breakfast, do you like it?
(Kim Shin)
Look at me, hey?
The careless Grim Reaper, just like always
Do you even know what you're blabbering about?
You just got caught by Deokhwa.
[THE GRIM REAPER
THROWS THE BREAD DOWN]
(Deokhwa) Uncle caught
on before me, you know.
When he came to our house
back then, there was blue fire
coming from his body
[the sigh of the grim reaper]
Ha, I thought it was
spontaneous combustion (grim
[REAPER) OH, THE CLUMSY
GOBLIN, SIGH OF THE GRIM REAPER]
Deokhwa, it may be hard to
believe, but now you need to know...
What?
(Deokhwa) Uncle is a goblin and the
Uncle in the last room is the grim reaper?
(Kim Shin) [Surprised]
How did you know?
We just talked about it a moment ago.
- (Grim Reaper) Oh my
- (Kim Shin) Ah, that's
right (Kim Shin)
But I really don't understand why
you're not surprised
I don't know what to think,
my grandfather has been telling me
since I was six
years old (Deokhwa)
I have an uncle who is a
goblin, the Yoo family has been
hosting goblins
for generations, so I thought, huh
It's quite an
unusual religion, I didn't think it would actually
be
a real goblin, yes, I understand, you probably
can't imagine it well, so prove it
(Deokhwa)
Please prove it
If possible, both of you [Comedic music]
[Kim Shin's scoff]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
(Grim Reaper)
How is it?
[Mysterious sound effect]
[Kim Shin's strained groan]
[Grim Reaper's applause]
(Kim Shin) Welcome, it's your
first time with psychokinesis, right?
[Smiling]
How is it?
(Deokhwa) Oh, anyone can do this
Don't you know David Copperfield?
[Kim Shin's incredulous
breath] [A frying pan clatters]
Get out [scoffing]
Is that all there is?
First, you have to follow me.
[Eerie sound effect]
(Grim Reaper)
You'll know when you see it.
It's not a good place.
Uncle.
If there are four of you, you can't do it.
[KIM SHIN'S SCOFF]
(Kim Shin)
The kid was really nice.
[EERIE SOUND EFFECT]
[THE GRIM REAPER SLICES BREAD SWIFTLY]
[Mobile phone manipulation sound]
I will take revenge.
I have to do it before I get attached, before I get attached.
[Mysterious sound effect]
[Deokhwa's surprised groan]
[GRAND MUSIC]
[DEOKHWA'S AWKWARD LAUGHTER]
(Deokhwa)
Uncles, it's a misunderstanding, a misunderstanding.
How do I get that from the Seongbuk-dong branch?
I was going to ask that, you know.
Uncles.
Uncles?
Uncle.
[THE DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
Th, aunt.
Why are you so surprised?
It's not like I came to a place I can't come to.
Is there food?
(Aunt Euntak)
No food? I knew you would say that.
Just because the girl has made some money,
does she order everything to be delivered again?
Come in.
I'll set it up for you.
Just set it up roughly.
If there's something to grill, go ahead and grill it.
[CALM MUSIC]
(Euntak)
How about Kyung-mi and Kyung-sik oppa?
- Did you see them?
- Ah, I don't know, those bastards
(Euntak Aunt)
No news has been good news for a long time
It's all good, I guess
Oh, it's better that those bastards are gone
Hey, but are you really buying this house with just your earnings?
What, even if you study well, it's all crap
Is this a jeonse or a wolse?
Oh, right, hurry up and set the table
You must be busy too
(Yuna)
Then next time...
We will look into case laws that
are closely related to daily life.
(Radio Host)
Yes, thank you
So far, it was attorney Kim Yuna for a snippet of legal advice
(Yuna)
Have a sensible weekend without any need for the law
(Radio Host)
Alright, then let's listen to a song
and after sending out the ads
We'll meet again in Part 3
How did I do today?
Hey, change your job
You're really good at broadcasting
Psh, I don't even listen, so what
[AWKWARD LAUGHTER]
Why do you look like you've eaten shit?
(Yuna)
Want to have a drink in the daytime?
[SHE CLICKS HER TONGUE]
[LAUGHTER]
No, I have to see the chicken shop owner
(Eun-tak)
I have an appointment, so let's do it next time
Then I'll go first
(Yoon-a)
Good work
[THE DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES WITH A CLICK]
(Sunny)
Then let's organize it by the weekend
(Real estate agent)
Understood
I will contact the landlord like that too
Yes
[EUN-TAK'S PLEASANT BREATHING]
(Sunny)
[slightly smiling]
What's going on?
Did you go abroad once and
suddenly start with foreign-style greetings?
Boss, I missed you
(Eun-tak)
You weren't at the store or at home
What have you been doing these days?
Preparing for the move
(Eun-tak)
Moving? To a new house or a new store?
Both
I was trying to overcome new house syndrome
That's not what I meant
[EUN-TAK RUMMAGES THROUGH HER BAG]
This, it's a gift from Canada
I brought it with me to give it to you when we meet
So, did you find what you were looking for?
I found everything, all of it
You probably won't believe me if I tell you?
[SHE SMILES SLIGHTLY]
Did you find your boyfriend while searching for it?
In Quebec, no less
It's destiny
Is that destiny handsome?
Very much so
(Euntak)
He has clear and big eyes and has worked for the country
He must be very stubborn
[Smiling]
Yes
[CALM MUSIC]
What?
(Sunny)
I know your PD has low standards
So, what about that wonderful restaurant?
[LAUGHTER]
I'll introduce you to the restaurant person later
I really want to show you, to the owner
That's enough
What?
I saw you coming down from the rooftop
You take care of it
Why?
Just, it reminds me of old times
[SIGH]
Yeah, you take care of that thought too
Stay healthy
Why are you like this?
Like someone I won't see forever
(Euntak)
Then take care, I have an appointment
(Sunny)
Yeah
[THE DOOR SUDDENLY OPENS]
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
(Ghost)
[English]
I'm seeing you again
(Euntak)
[Korean]
That's right
(Euntak)
Canadian ghost, Canadian ghost
That man
Was he a ghost?
He didn’t show up for a while, why can I see him again?
What are you thinking so much about?
Did you come?
I'm thinking about Canada
You weren't thinking about me?
(Euntak)
As I was thinking about Canada
Kim Shin's thoughts naturally came to mind
I went to see my first love four times
I fed my first love a cow
My first love said she was still pretty
But?
So I thought that first love might not be me
[smirking]
But?
But something feels a bit strange
(Euntak)
Then what about that first love they say was met during the late Joseon Dynasty under Cheoljong?
You
[soft music]
Lie
(Kim Shin)
Even before we met
That time I didn't even know
You stayed for a while and left
I saw you in the winter of the 12th year of Cheoljong
You, who are in the distant future
Lie
Really like a lie
[EUNTAK'S LAUGHTER]
(Eun-tak)
Ah, it's amazing, ah, it's exciting
It really feels like a lie
That all those first loves were me
Ah, right, then that time
When I was summoned on the first snow day
That appearance
Is it possibly the appearance of the god Mu-shin Kim-shin?
(Kim-shin)
Yeah
(Eun-tak)
Ah, I see
I was really curious
You from a time I didn’t know
I saw you like that
(Kim-shin)
Was it strange?
(Eun-tak)
No, it was cool, a Goryeo man
[EUN-TAK'S SMILE]
Sure, that's why I'm saying this
(Kim Shin)
I'm saying this because the weather is a bit nice today
I'm saying this because you keep shining
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
All those first loves
I'm saying this because they were you
On another day when the weather is nice
Will you become the bride of this Goryeo man?
[THE WIND IS BLOWING]
(Sunny)
I hope it lasts a long time
Goodbye
(Grim Reaper)
(Sunny)
Is this our happy ending?
(Grim Reaper)
That's
It's instinct in that moment
It's entirely a human choice
[IT CRASHES]
I'm sorry
(Euntak)
I'm really sorry
[KIM SHIN SOBS]
Subtitle: Choi Hyeran