[THEME SONG]
[HEAVY MUSIC]
(Three Gods)
When the moment of life and death comes
I earnestly pray with my wishes
Perhaps some weak-hearted god
might be listening
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECTS]
[Tire screeching sound]
[Shocked gasp of Loan Shark 1]
[Tense music]
(Loan Shark 1)
Hey, you punk, can’t you drive properly?
- (Loan Shark 2) Hyung
- (Loan Shark 1) Huh?
(Loan Shark 2)
Over there
[Streetlights flicker off]
(Loan Shark 1)
Huh?
[LOAN SHARKS' SHOCKED GASPS]
[Streetlight bursts]
(Loan Shark 1)
What’s going on, what’s going on?
[Tense sound effects]
(Loan Shark 1)
What’s going on?
[MAJESTIC MUSIC]
[TENSE SOUND EFFECTS]
[FOOTSTEPS ECHO]
What, what are those punks?
Is it 'Men in Black'?
[Eun-tak sobs]
[Loan Shark 1's frightened gasp]
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECTS]
[LOAN SHARK 1'S SHOCKED GASP]
[THE HEADLIGHTS ABRUPTLY GO OFF]
(Loan Shark 1)
What are these punks?
[Trembling Moan] [Loan
Shark 1's Scared Breathing]
(Loan Shark 1)
[Stammering]
Hurry up -
(Loan Shark 1)
Step on it, step on it!
[- (LOAN SHARK 2) UH, UH
THE SOUND OF A CAR ENGINE]
[SHARP SOUND EFFECT]
[Sizzling]
[Loan Shark 1's Curious Moan]
[SHARP SOUND EFFECT]
[ELEGANT MUSIC]
[SCREAMS OF THE LOAN SHARKS]
[CRYING]
Oh, mom's car
[SUDDENLY STOPS]
[SOBBING]
[Sobbing] Mom
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
[THE CAR CRASHES DOWN WITH A BANG]
[EUNTAK'S TREMBLING BREATH]
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
[SOBBING]
[EUNTAK'S SURPRISED BREATH]
(Kim Shin)
You have to get down
Pack your things
[EUNTAK SNIFFLES]
[EUNTAK CLINKS HER THINGS TOGETHER]
[EUNTAK'S STARTLED MOAN]
[EUNTAK'S HEAVY BREATHING]
(Kim Shin)
Are you hurt? Where?
[SOBBING]
[SIGH]
[The car crashes down]
[Euntak's surprised breath]
[THERE’S A SCREECH FROM THE CAR]
It’s hurt, that...
[SNIFFLING]
(Kim Shin)
What?
Are you hurt?
[TREMBLING BREATH]
Is it okay to ask that?
After tearing the car like that?
[EUNTAK SNIFFLES]
(Kim Shin)
Wait here for a second
[EUNTAK SNUFFLES]
(Euntak)
What are you going to do?
Are you going to kill me?
You’re not going to kill me, right?
- No
- What, you always say no when you just talk
The grim reaper came along too
(Euntak)
What, do you think that guy
came to save me?
That context is more natural, right?
(Kim Shin)
Don't worry, I won't kill you
I'm just trying to show you that I'm angry
It feels like dying would be better
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
[CREAKING]
[THE PAINFUL MOANS OF LOAN SHARKS]
(Loan Shark 1)
Oh, oh, my leg
[Moans of Loan Shark 2]
(Loan Shark 2)
Please save me, I really messed up
[Moans of Loan Shark 1]
Please save me, please save me
- (Loan Shark 1) Please save me
- (Loan Shark 2) Bro, are you okay?
(Loan Shark 1)
Ah, please save me
This road will disappear from the map
in two days
That means there will be no luck of being found
by anyone in two days
(Kim Shin)
It will hurt enough to die, but I won't die
Fortunately, two days later
I will be found by the police
I can pay the price at the police station
Be grateful that you don’t have to pay it to me
God sometimes
hides among those you have oppressed
Express your gratitude to that child and
[TENSE MUSIC]
(The Grim Reaper)
They just fought, that's all.
[Meaningful sound effect]
You saw nothing
Ah, the two will never reconcile in their lifetime
Just for your reference
[EUNTAK'S SIGH]
(Euntak)
Did you
not bring the car?
Ah, we don't really drive around
(Euntak)
Ah
By any chance, I'm just asking this out of curiosity
Am I dead by any chance?
(Euntak)
Is this road taking me to the afterlife?
(Kim Shin)
This is just a country road
We saved you a moment ago and
So are you going to kill me now?
( Eun-tak ) Am I
possibly captured, alive?
( Grim Reaper ) I'm curious, when do I get to
hear 'Thank you for saving me, I appreciate it'?
( Kim Shin )
Calm down, we are
currently with a nineteen-year-old
[HIGH SCHOOL GIRL WHOSE ANGER HASN'T SUBSIDED]
( Eun-tak )
I didn't know you two
were this close. What if you bring the
Grim Reaper to someone asking for their life?
( Grim Reaper ) I'm curious, when do I get to
hear 'Thank you for saving me, I appreciate it'...
(Kim Shin)
Ah, be quiet! Tsk
No, why are you shouting...
[EUNTAK SNIFFLES]
But there’s not a single car passing by on this road!
[EUNTAK HUFFS]
(Reaper)
I haven’t allowed any cars to pass on this road for two days, so who
(Kim Shin)
I said to be quiet!
Why haven’t you left yet?
You said you were leaving
Soon
Ah, don’t worry about it
(Euntak)
Well, I wasn’t really that curious to ask
(Kim Shin)
I know
But how did you get here?
I couldn’t light my lighter earlier
Well, it just seems like I heard it
(Kim Shin)
“Please save me,” something like that
I thought it to myself
I guess I tend to think loudly in my head
You could have not come
There was no reason not to come
I’m sorry
For coming to save someone like me, who’s not even a priest, in such a busy time
(Euntak)
I’ve done some inquiries, but...
You said you would buy me as a bonus before
That saying turned out to be true
19 years ago
You saved me and my mom, right?
So, I’m okay with being a bonus
Because I met my mom thanks to being born
So
I’m trying not to hate you anymore
But it seems like you do hate me?
Not really
If we meet by chance
I really wanted to tell you
I guess you hoped we wouldn’t meet
But it seems like you do hate me
Not true
From now on
I'm not summoning anything, not thinking about anything
So I won't do anything
(Euntak)
Please leave with a peaceful mind
I hope your home is filled with peace
I really hope you meet a good person
Someone who helps you discover your true self
Someone really pretty
Ah, I mean the heart, not the face
Since you said you wouldn’t see faces
[EUNTAK'S SIGH]
It's all boiled now, so please eat
Then I’ll be going
Oh, um...
I didn’t eat this, but am I taking it?
(Euntak)
You said to eat it, mister.
I didn't eat either.
And I have no money.
Then I'll pay, so you find some time and eat.
Right now.
Are you feeding me dinner?
Oh.
They wouldn't have fed you and kidnapped you.
I don't want to, I don't want to eat with that uncle.
(Euntak)
If that's the case, please wrap it up.
I'll gratefully accept only the tteokbokki.
You really do hate him.
[ANGRY BREATH]
Okay, uncle, listen carefully.
(Deokhwa)
Euntak lost his parents when he was young.
I heard that they were bullied by their aunt and siblings.
Shaba shaba, ah shaba
How much did they cry?
Who made them cry?
[DEOKHWA SLAMS DOWN A PHOTO]
(Deokhwa)
Aunt and siblings
What is this, there's nothing deep to dig
It's just that there's a lot of gossip in the neighborhood
There’s a kid named Euntak
who has insurance money left by their mom
It’s about 150 million won
When this kid becomes an adult
they can't do whatever they want with that money
Looks like the aunt really has a grip on the kid
Why are you looking at it that way?
I'm surprised that you're useful
Ha, really
(Deokhwa)
When it comes to chaebols, they should
use money and power
You have to investigate others at least once...
Where did you get the photo?
I took it, while stalking
But I didn't see Euntak, I guess she's busy
What's that?
(Deokhwa)
I thought it came out well
[AWKWARD BREATH]
But uncle, why did you want me to recognize this?
[While tidying up the photo]
To punish you
How?
[SPARKLING SOUND EFFECT]
(Duk-hwa)
Uncle, are you in pain?
Is this punishment?
Is it gold?
No, what kind of punishment is given in gold?
- Me? - You did well (Duk-hwa) Ah, why, me!
Why can't I receive this, huh?
Haven't I committed a lot of sins?
Don't I truly deserve divine punishment?
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
(Eun-tak aunt) Ah, these bastards
have caught the child, what's going on?
Why is there no call?!
[TV sounds are playing]
[Gyeong-sik and Gyeong-mi's laughter]
Ah, be quiet, you bastards!
Mom's insides are burning away, just, huh?
Oh my, just
[PAINFUL MOANS]
That cash is about to be given all to those
scoundrels' bellies (Aunt Eun-tak) Oh my!
(Kyung-sik) Anyway, it's all
[MONEY THAT MOM BORROWED]
Kyung-sik crunches the snack. Right, Maybe
I should have let you guys starve to death?
(Kyung-mi)
Even now, well, it's not really any different.
Right, I'm the crazy one, the crazy one thinking about what
movie I'm going to watch
Having kids one after another..
[]
[EXCITING MUSIC]
A surprised moan.
(Kyung-mi) What is this?
(Kyung-sik) It's
gold, you idiot.
Wow, Ji Eun-tak She
turned all that money into gold
(Aunt Eun-tak)
So there was a reason she
insisted she didn't have a bank book [sniffling]
That's why she's saying
she doesn't have a bank book.
Let's go to the gold
shop as promised at
dawn, we're going to split it
exactly the same way, exactly.
Just keep messing around (Aunt
Eun-tak)
This bastard to mom, damn (Kyung-sik)
Damn [Kyung-mi's strained moan]
Give it, give it, give it, give it.
- (Aunt Euntaek) Let go, let go, let go, let go!
- (Kyungshik) Give it to me, give it to me...
[Kyungmi's urgent moan]
[EXCITING MUSIC]
[THE CLOCK TICKS]
[TIRED GROANS]
Uh, uh!
(Kyungshik)
[Tapping Aunt Euntaek]
Mom, wake up
That Kyungmi girl ran off with the money!
[PLAYFUL SOUND EFFECTS]
(Aunt Euntaek)
Oh, crazy girl!
[AUNT EUNTAEK'S URGENT BREATHING]
(Aunt Euntaek)
Ah, she's still on the phone
(Kyungshik)
So, she's still on the phone, right now
[Aunt Euntaek's urgent breathing]
What the hell is she talking to, damn it!
[AUNT EUNTAEK'S LABORED BREATHING]
She's talking to this guy, this guy
Hang up quickly, damn it!
Hurry up, hurry up, get a taxi, taxi
- (Kyungshik) Taxi, taxi!
- (Aunt Euntaek) Taxi, taxi
[Woman 1 speaks]
(Aunt Euntaek)
I'm busy, busy
- (Aunt Euntaek) Busy, busy, busy, busy
- (Kyungshik) Move, move, move
- (Euntak Aunt) Sir, Gangnam
- (Kyungshik) Depart, depart
(Deokhwa)
Yes, Grandpa, Uncle is eating right now...
No, he took a spoonful of rice and
I even added kimchi for him
Seolleongtang, yes, yes
Ah, but Grandpa, I need the card...
Hello? Hello?
[DEOKHWA'S SIGH]
(Deokhwa)
Actually, if Uncle could just say a word about this issue...
Uncle, did you hear what I said?
Ah, what are you watching, what?
Television
He's a pitiful person.
I'm not angry at a poor person
A third-generation chaebol
Was exactly that age
Who?
The king I was protecting
Was seventeen
You protected the king? Wow
(Deokhwa)
Uncle, were you a eunuch?
I was
[SIGH]
You said it was a poor person, Deokhwa
You need to help, right now
The sunniest part of the day
[HEAVY MUSIC]
My eyes were stinging
I kept blaming someone
Whether it was the king or a god
Or me
I forgot that
(Kim Shin)
Is that them?
[THE SOUND OF THE TV FLOWS OUT]
(Grim Reaper)
What?
My thousand years of rage, the
reincarnation of the king who
killed me, look closely, has he reincarnated?
I don’t know, if there’s a reincarnation, it’ll be
exactly around that age (Deok Hwa)
[smiling
[SLIGHTLY]
YOUR HONOR, YOUR HONOR, MY LORD, THE GRIM REAPER’S SIGH]
Forget it, all that hatred and the desire for revenge
(Grim Reaper) Is making you unhappy right now...
Are you happy because you can’t remember?
(Grim Reaper) I just can’t tell by looking,
you have to touch to know what it is?
What are you really saying,
that I should use you?
(Duk-hwa) No, what
would I know if I touch it?
(Grim Reaper) Sigh, but why do you think it
must be because I reincarnated as a man?
That guy?
Just because I can't see
doesn't mean I don't know.
You have to touch it to know, ah,
what about touching it, what about it?
Is it him? Just say it’s him,
I think I'm ready
to forgive, right?
A thousand years of rage?
Everyone must have had their
circumstances, as you know, rage
is everywhere and nowhere at
all... [Sigh of the Grim Reaper]
(Kim Shin) Where are you going?
Ah, what is it? What about touching it?
Ah, why are they only talking
[AMONG THEMSELVES, DUK-HWA'S SIGH]
(Grim Reaper) Oh
dear, oh dear, oh dear!
[THE TV SOUND KEEPS FLOWING OUT]
[WOMAN 2 IS SOBBING]
(Reaper 1) Hello,
senior I am Kim, from the
21st batch (Reaper
2) Hello, senior I am
Kim, from the 23rd batch
(Grim Reaper) Yeah,
good job, sit down
(Reapers) Yes, I will work hard!
(Reaper 3) Oh dear, so
green, yeah we also had a
[TIME LIKE THIS, REAPER 3'S LAUGHTER]
(Reaper 1) 21st batch,
[KIM, REAPER 3'S LAUGHTER]
(Reaper 4) Uh, take a break.
(Lions)
Yes, I will work hard!
(Lion 4)
Have you come out?
But why don't you seniors check your company emails?
There are missing others, you know?
The draft has been approved and a dedicated team has been established
Before the year-end settlement
Please upload the list
I don't have any, but you have two, right?
Who said that? I have two
Well, everyone says you have two
I will upload it soon
(Lion 4)
I would appreciate it if you could
Ah, I must take my leave
It's time for me to go
See you at the winter workshop
(Lion 3)
Hey, good job
That's him, that's him
That guy
[APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS]
[CHEERFUL MUSIC]
(Lion 5)
Hello, senior
This is Kim from the 23rd batch
[LION 3'S LAUGHTER]
Oh, yes
I will take my leave
(Lion 3)
Oh, go ahead
[LION 3'S LAUGHTER]
Beautiful, right?
He should be an angel
Why is he playing a grim reaper?
[LION 3'S LAUGHTER]
They're really excited
because of him.
[LION 3'S LAUGHTER]
In our class,
you look the most excited, because of him
[LION 3'S COUGH]
(Doctor 1)
Please step back
- (Doctor 1) Step aside!
- (Paramedic) Move, move aside
[Nurse 1 shouts]
(Woman 3)
[Sobbing]
Oppa, oppa...
[IT'S NOISY]
Then I'll be on my way
(Lion 3)
Uh, ah, and, um, at the end of the month
there's a initiation ceremony and a gathering for the 23rd group
If you miss it, there's a fine, so don't skip
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
(Grim Reaper 1)
21st Class Kim Chasa
[ECG beep sound]
Has the operation room called?
There's no time, hurry up
[SIGNIFICANT MUSIC]
(Grim Reaper)
Mr. Choi Yeong-jae?
[Significant sound effect]
(Doctor 1)
I'm sorry, but later
The guardian is outside...
(Grim Reaper)
Age 33, Year of the Metal Ox, Month of July, Day of the 10th
Died at 17:41
Cause of death, overwork
Is this you?
Am I dead?
(Doctor 2)
Hey, Choi Yeong-jae!
[Heavy sound effect]
[Doctor 3 sobs]
Choi Young-jae!
(Doctor 3)
[Sobbing]
Get up
(Doctor 2)
Young-jae
[DOCTOR 3 CONTINUES TO SOB]
(Doctor 2)
Choi Young-jae!
Young-jae
(Doctor 3)
Young-jae oppa
(Grim Reaper)
Thanks to the emergency treatment by the doctor,
this patient has survived
[THE ECG BEEPS]
(Nurse 2)
Vital signs are stabilized, the patient survived
That's a relief
[THE ECG BEEP SOUNDS AGAIN]
"Ji Eun-tak"
[THE SOUND OF INSECTS CHIRPING]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
(Euntak)
I'm going to get married, to the uncle
No matter how much I think about it
I feel like the uncle is really a goblin
I love you
I found it
(Euntak)
Close your eyes, we can't look at each other
[in a small voice]
That person is a grim reaper
I don't know
Whether you leave or not
Has it already been sold?
(Deokhwa)
No, why on earth can't I get a refund?
(Staff)
As I mentioned earlier, customer
If you don't have a receipt, it's difficult to get a refund.
(Deokhwa)
I was trying to buy a book.
I wasn't trying to buy someone else's memories.
(Deokhwa)
Look, what if there's something like this in the book?
Please refund it.
(Staff)
Ah, even if you say that,
you need to bring the receipt...
I'll buy this.
(Deokhwa)
Is the student the owner of these memories?
Memories... Yes, yes.
They're my memories, I'll buy them.
But there's no proof that it's the student's?
(Duk-hwa)
Guess which neighborhood this autumn foliage is from.
(Eun-tak)
Uh...
But even if I tell you the name of the neighborhood,
you wouldn't know it anyway.
Correct answer.
I thought I had lost it, thank you.
(Duk-hwa)
Well, I get it.
But I think I'm past the age to read that.
Ah, it's just for research purposes...
(Eun-tak)
What about you? Why this book...
Ah, I have a goblin I know,
What?
Why? Doesn't everyone have at least one goblin they know?
Really?
"Is that real?" said the girl.
If someone asks for a guarantee,
what should I do?
'No'
If someone says,
'This mat is nice',
what should I do?
'I don't like it'
If someone says they'll buy snacks,
what should I do?
'Ah, just go away'
I pay for the book, ten thousand won
How long do I have to sit here?
(Eun-tak)
Ah, I'm sorry
But,
Shouldn't this book be considered a used book?
(Deok-hwa)
No, I don't like it
[EUN-TAK'S LAUGHTER]
(Eun-tak)
Please, just once...
[Deok-hwa's laughter]
(Deok-hwa)
Go away
Uncle
[Stammering]
Grandfather
(Chairman Yoo)
Yeah
I stopped by to check in while picking up the laundry
But there was a guest here
[Awkwardly smiling]
Ah, guest, guest...
(Deok-hwa)
Who is the person with you?
How did you come to my uncle's house?
[SIGH]
(Grim Reaper)
The author's friend
[BOUNCY MUSIC]
Visiting this house...
(Duk-hwa)
Ah, you came to visit, at your friend's house
Your uncle must be a really close friend
Oh, your uncle is going overseas, so
you came for the farewell party
Safe travels
Stay healthy and don’t ever come back
(Grim Reaper)
Be happy and live long
until you die there...
You go on, we’re not friends anyway
(Kim Shin)
Get out, quickly, from my house
Don’t ever come back again
(Duk-hwa)
Hey, uncle, why are you like this?
To a really close friend
You don't think so?
You go out too, really really quickly
(Deokhwa)
Wow, how can they do that?
Isn't it really too much?
That's right
Isn't it?
No, how can they chase me out too?
If they were my uncle, would they do that to me?
[Tension-building sound effect]
[A rustling sound is heard]
[DEOKHWA'S SURPRISED GASP]
(Deokhwa)
[Smiling slightly]
You'll be leaving soon
(The Grim Reaper)
That’s how it should be
Otherwise, you’ll be leaving soon.
Somewhere
The good thing about that place is
It's probably not, right
Come in
[Deokhwa's scoff]
(Deokhwa)
That's enough
No matter how much I ask you to come in...
(Kim Shin)
Not you, you go home, to get scolded
1 to 0
[EXCITING MUSIC]
[Mysterious sound effect]
(Deokhwa)
Am I getting scolded?
Why am I getting scolded?
Uncle, no way
Did you tell Grandpa everything?
(Deokhwa)
Wow, that's so petty.
What, how far did we talk?
What do I need to know to match your words?
(Kim Shin)
Did you match your words with me and put the house up for sale?
[KIM SHIN'S SNICKER]
Can't go, where to go, really
Even if I die, I'm a ghost of this house
[KIM SHIN HUMS]
(Kim Shin)
[Inhaling]
Oh, yes
[HUMMING]
[SNAPS HIS TONGUE]
[TENSION-BUILDING SOUND EFFECTS]
[KIM SHIN'S SCREAM]
(Grim Reaper)
Good night, one on one
[Kim Shin's surprised moan]
What, did you say something?
[Heavy music]
[BREATH OF FEAR]
Hey, the afterlife! Aren't you going to clean this up?
[MOAN OF FEAR]
Oh, I'm sorry, let me clean this up...
Hey!
(Eun-tak)
Yes?
You
Are you sleeping here?
(Eun-tak)
Ah...
I'm sorry
I was going to tell you
but I just couldn't find the right timing
I'm really sorry
But how did you know?
(Sunny)
I don't brush my teeth at the store
[I SET THE TOOTHBRUSH DOWN]
There’s more evidence.
[SUNNY IS RUSTLING IN HER POCKET]
[EUNTAK'S SURPRISED BREATH]
[LIVELY MUSIC]
(Euntak)
Boss, actually I'm sleeping in the store.
[CLEARS THROAT]
[SIGH]
(Euntak)
Boss, can I depend on you for a while?
Boss, I'm in a situation where I'm
dealing with lodging issues at the store
(Euntak)
I'm staying well.
[sniffling]
I was kicked out of my house, please save me.
Save you, what do you mean by save?
I'm sorry.
Is it because of my aunt?
It could be
but things just keep piling up
I get it
Aren't you going to ask anything more?
(Sunny)
What's the point of asking?
It's not like it'll solve anything
What I can do is
just give it to you
Here, this is a week's worth of part-time pay
I'm giving it to you weekly, why?
[Sighs]
If I give it as a salary, you might not be able to receive it
Even if you sleep here, go to the jjimjilbang to wash up
Buy some sikye
[SNIFFLES]
(Euntak)
Thank you
(Sunny)
I’m receiving what I deserve, but if you
express your gratitude like that, people will
think you’re ridiculous. I’m grateful not for
money but for the boss's coolness; that’s what
makes money cool. Hey, part-timer, wash up before
you go and can you grill just one squid for me to drink with?
No, just the squid; I
won’t even touch the alcohol.
If I drink too
much, I’ll get drunk, okay?
[CRUNCHES ON THE SNACKS]
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
[The car crashes down]
[Eun-tak’s surprised breath]
[A WHOOSHING SOUND COMES FROM THE CAR]
[Eu-tak's surprised gasp]
[Blowing air through lips]
Ah, no, no, no
No, it's a cancellation, cancellation, no!
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
[SIGH]
(Eu-tak)
I see you were reading a book?
(Kim-shin)
I always keep a book close
and have a deep appreciation for music and art.
(Eu-tak)
I’m sorry for interrupting your reading.
So why did you interrupt?
You said you wouldn’t call me.
(Eu-tak)
I didn’t call, it was a mistake.
The fire caught my leg while I was grilling squid,
that’s why I was called, okay?
Was it delicious?
Why are you here? Haven't you left yet?
I was in the middle of packing.
(Kim-shin)
Packing books first, always books first!
Well then, I should go now, I still have to finish packing.
- (Eu-tak) Um...
- You always talk to me when I'm about to leave?
Whenever I try to start a conversation,
it's always you leaving, you know?
I’m curious about something
- I won’t give you five hundred
- Ah, you startled me
I heard you say 'I won't confess.'
(Euntak)
It's because you are jumping to conclusions and saying ridiculous things,
[RIGHT? ABSURD BREATHING]
At what point did this become my fault?
From there, the part where I have
to see something, there
(Euntak)
So
What exactly am I supposed to see?
For you to find value in me?
If you tell me, will I be able to see it?
No, even if I see it, I plan to say I can't see it (Euntak)
What if you suddenly start treating me well because of that?
Giving me five hundred Oh?
Saying you’ll buy me meat and all?
Don't you have anything you want?
Then I'm really tired.
I really don't like uncles.
(Kim Shin)
Well...
Ha, this is the first time I've heard something like that.
It's true, I really haven't heard it before, really.
When adults talk, where do you look?
If you don't want to answer, don't.
Don't you see something unique like this?
Like, something that looks really painful?
Oh, that?
Can you see it?
What can I say?
Goodbye, I'm busy so I have to go now.
(Kim Shin)
Hey, do you want to eat meat?
Don't you want anything?
It's five hundred.
You said you were busy, quickly go now.
Then meat, over here.
[LIVELY MUSIC]
[THE MEAT SIZZLES]
[EUNTAK IS SLURPING]
This is the last piece of meat, can you see it?
(Euntak)
Yes.
It looks really delicious.
[SIGH]
(Euntak)
Thank you for the meal.
(Kim Shin)
Ah, can you see it? You can't see, can you?
Are you getting annoyed with me right now?
Did it come across like that?
Yes.
Ah, I'm sorry.
What do you think about fresh fruit juice after a meal?
That was a bit loud, wasn't it?
Fresh fruit juice?
[CHEERFUL MUSIC IS PLAYING]
(Kim Shin)
What do you want to drink? You can order something expensive
(Eun Tak)
Ah, I'm full
I'll have this in a large size
Aren't you full?
(Grim Reaper)
I'll have the same thing
(Clerk)
I'll help you with the bill
(Grim Reaper)
They said they'll help with the bill
The author won't help
(Grim Reaper)
What's going on?
You said you hate the fruit being too
spicy (Kim Shin)
What brings you here?
Well, who are we killing here today?
I'm a regular here (Eun
Tak) Is it me by any chance?
Is the one who is dying
here today possibly me...
Lured by beef Am I
caught in a trap called juice?
Are you two really in the same gang?
Oh no, actually I'm in
the same gang as you,
[THE SUSPENSEFUL SOUND EFFECT]
(Grim Reaper)
I can see the
sword, I can see the sword,
what are you doing drawing that sword?
What does that mean? Why
are you in the same gang as me?
What is this? Why isn’t it getting caught?
It’s a kid that goes beyond all expectations
(Grim Reaper)
You’re saying the attached documents aren’t a joke
[CALL NOTIFICATION]
Then have a good time
I have a prior engagement on this side
(Eun-tak)
I guess I really came just to drink juice
It’s refreshing
But why do you say you’re on my side?
It’s the gods’ business, you don’t need to know
But that guy
Isn’t he just unnecessarily handsome?
(Eun-tak)
If you’re handsome, people follow you
Did they only hire people like that for work?
[Kim Shin’s smirk]
Are all grim reapers handsome originally?
[KIM SHIN’S SMIRK]
Is that handsome?
Yes, that is exactly what handsome looks like
(Kim Shin)
Then what about me?
You, sir
Um, you just look the way you do
(Kim Shin)
Stop eating
You’re full
(Eun-tak)
Oh, that guy is also handsome
The water here must be good
[slightly laughs]
[phone operation sound]
(Male 1)
[In a cute tone]
I'll be there soon, see you in a bit
I love you
(Female 4)
Yes, babe
I'll hurry because I miss you
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
[THE CELL PHONE FALLS WITH A THUD]
What are you doing?
(Kim Shin)
Something anyone would want to wake up to
Are you okay?
Magic
[EXCITING MUSIC]
(Female 4)
Oh my, I'm sorry
Ah, I'll fix it
(Male 1)
What?
Oh, um...
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
[THEY ARE SURPRISED TOGETHER]
[MAN 1 COUGHS]
(Man 1)
Why here, why here...
[WOMAN 4'S PAINED MOAN]
[Smiling slightly]
Just a moment, just a moment, this...
- (Man 1) I'm sorry, I'm sorry
- (Woman 4) It's okay
(Man 1)
Yes, yes, it's been released, it's been released...
It's been released
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC]
[EUN-TAK'S SURPRISED MOAN]
Are you okay?
(Woman 4)
Yes
Today is quite a strange day
It feels like I've been enchanted
[MAN 1 SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(Men 1)
So I'm asking
Do you have a boyfriend?
No, my family is strict
Ah, so strict
Do you have a girlfriend?
I'm a virgin
I've been waiting for you
[in a small voice]
Kiss, kiss, kiss, kiss, kiss
(Euntak)
Is your side job Cupid?
That was just what you mentioned, right? Guardian, that
(Kimshin)
One or two people in a hundred years
There are people who are born
with the same face as in their past lives
That's why I know the man's past life.
That woman is a woman that a man cannot miss
(Euntak). And what was the past life?
Is he the man who saved the
country that I've only heard about?
The author's past life was a worse landowner
than a poor tenant farmer
he exploited, so why help?
Are even bad people
given a guardian deity?
Where is that common?
Those who lived kindly are all
drained; I am not their guardian
deity, but the guardian deity of
[A MAN AND A WOMAN THEY JUST MISSED]
Exciting music. (Man 1) I love you.
(Girl 5)
I love you too
(Girl 4)
I want to see you, so I'll hurry
(Boy 2)
Don't come quickly, come slowly
You'll get hurt, got it?
(Euntak)
Wow
Men are liars and cowardly
Women are full of vanity and
Don't know how to be grateful
Now those two
Will become each other's hell
Wow, that's kind of cool?
I often create
magical moments for humans
Um, but
(Euntak)
Why do you keep talking in a historical drama tone since earlier?
I can't figure it out
[EUNTAK'S LAUGHTER]
Then
Is my life this way
(Euntak)
Because I committed a great sin in my past life?
Is being born as a goblin bride a punishment for that?
I don't know what your past life was like
But to discuss the present life
Nineteen years old is still too early
You're not a goblin bride
Oh, not fooled
(Euntak)
It's been eventful, but
I still like my life
I was loved greatly by my mom
I got an umbrella
and meeting an uncle is nice
Ah, it was good, it's in the past
There are lingering feelings
(Kim Shin)
Whether you see it or not
I haven't answered yet
Do you see it, or not?
My mom used to say
People should stretch their legs according to where they can lie down
And they should know when to leave
You know what I mean, right?
I don’t understand
It means this is as far as we go
I’m going this way, goodbye
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
(Euntak)
Oh, that’s pretty cool?
(Deokhwa)
Wow, that’s pretty cool?
Uncle, it was just like a painting
What about Uncle in the last room?
- Not yet
- Well, mainly working overtime
(Deokhwa)
Uncle, you know
When I die later
I wonder if I’ll end up being a grim reaper like Uncle in the last room
When you open the last room of the corridor called life
There is death, right?
That greeting is Uncle in the last room coming out
Wake up, it’s impossible with your sins
I don’t want to say this, but
In the previous life, you must have committed a great sin to become a grim reaper...
(Deok-hwa)
Great sin? Great sin, what?
How did you know?
Wow, no way, are you really a murderer?
(Deok-hwa)
Wow, you really can't tell a person
just by looking at their face, seriously
Aside from that, how did you know that person
was a grim reaper?
Uncle, don’t you think it’s
way too late for that question?
(Deok-hwa)
Back then, why, you were so depressed
when there were clouds in the living room
and it was thundering and all.
[Quarreling] When Uncle came out of
the last room I was a bit startled, you know?
Wow, but that uncle
didn't change his
expression at all.
Why is he like that?
(Deok-hwa) And in front of
everyone, I mean I already
told you all about the
reaper's foresight and
everything, uncles (Kim-shin)
The reaper talking all
sorts of things in front of
the kid, I hope you don't
underestimate the reaper's
foresight (Deok-hwa) Is that all?
His face is pale while
his lips are red, and
his clothes are black. [Reverent
music] [Deok-hwa's flustered laugh]
(Dukhwa) What kind of celebrity do
you think I am? Then I will take my leave.
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
(Grim Reaper)
You
How did you find out that I am the Grim Reaper?
How can you not know when I'm saying this?
(Deokhwa)
The person who was over there is suddenly right here
Really, be careful
Uncles are too careless and naive
(Grim Reaper)
It was because of you that I got caught
A goblin who only gossips about others
(Kim Shin)
Look at yourself, it might be because of me
The Grim Reaper who might have been a murderer in a past life
[THE GRIM REAPER'S HOLLOW LAUGH]
(Grim Reaper)
What am I, not even killing
a single ant on the street
I guess this is why I'm being punished like this
Ha, really
[THE DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES WITH A CLICK]
I guess I'm really hurt, what to do?
Can't you see my face is just as clueless?
[HEAVY MUSIC]
A big sin
(Grim Reaper)
Disrespect, disloyalty, irreverence
Infidelity, adultery...
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
Let's not go this far
[The door opens with a click]
- It can't be
- (Kim Shin) Oh, no
[THE DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
Why? What did you come here for?
(Kim Shin)
Responsible actions
Efforts to become a better person
It's usually called an apology
Earlier I misspoke, I'm sorry
(The Grim Reaper)
Tch
Which of these is not true?
- Disobedience?
- Get out
You just misspoke again
I thought you would laugh
Get out!
(Kim Shin)
What does a past life matter?
I don't care at all what you were or what you did in your past life
- Really?
- (Kim Shin) Yeah
No matter what you did,
I consistently dislike you.
[THE GRIM REAPER'S LAUGHTER]
(Grim Reaper)
Ah
I shouldn't be laughing
(Deokhwa)
When we first met,
I thought you were Uncle in the last room,
I thought you would kick me out right away?
But surprisingly,
you two are getting along quite well.
One is tormented by forgetting their past life,
the other is tormented by not being able to forget their past life.
Those two beings rely on each other.
[SIGH]
We just
During the long lives of the two of you,
I’m just stopping by for a moment
Ah, I see
But did Grandpa know too?
Oh, the uncles are really
I’m worried if they’re doing well
without being found out outside,
You should worry about yourself
Stretch out your arms!
[PLAYFUL MUSIC]
(Chairman Yoo)
Straighten your back!
[DEOKHWA’S SIGH]
There’s no way I could be a biological grandson
He wouldn’t treat his biological grandson like this
- I will get my revenge
- (Chairman Yoo) You little rascal!
(Dukhwa)
As you know, Secretary Kim, this is the building I
received as a birthday present when I was eight years old.
(Secretary Kim)
I know, what did you receive when you were nine?
I was hated, it was all a phase, but now
that I’ve become quite a respectable adult...
(Secretary Kim) You know
that you are still hated, right?
Dukhwa is using cards quite
respectably, so you cut him off, Secretary Kim.
(Dukhwa)
That’s why I’m saying this, but I’m
planning to get some cash flow through this building.
Please clear out the good places first.
Cleanly and without noise.
First of all, this chicken place that has closed down.
(Secretary Kim)
Hmm, Deokhwa.
There’s something you need to know first.
First,
The sign on that chicken place says 'CLOSED'.
That means it’s not business hours,
not that they’ve closed up shop.
Second, um...
We’re not here together.
I’m following Deokhwa,
by the chairman's orders.
Why are you following me so openly...?
[Playful music]
[Embarrassed smile]
I thought we were here together.
Let’s do this:
There’s going to be a call to the secretary’s office soon.
A woman will ask if I work there.
Then, at that time,
just tell her that I do work there.
Then it will be fine.
But you don’t work there.
[AN AWKWARD SMILE]
(Deokhwa)
Secretary Kim, really,
You do your job very honestly.
My grandfather must be very proud of you.
I need to get a new card issued, right?
Please, just this once.
Hey...
Where are you going?
- (Grim Reaper) Super
- (Kim Shin) Super?
(Kim Shin)
The repertoire is getting more and more half-hearted
[Grim Reaper's snicker]
(Grim Reaper)
Can’t you see the shopping basket?
(Kim Shin)
I didn't know it was a shopping basket
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
How are you really following me?
Don't you trust me?
Did I make you trust me?
You were originally going to go to her
But since I followed you, didn't you turn to the super?
Last time, it was the cafe that picked her up.
I just caught her.
I'm not going to take her, you know?
I'm really rooting for her right now.
Why are you supporting her?
(The Grim Reaper)
I'm really on her side.
They say if the bride draws the sword, she dies.
Well, rather than leaving for overseas,
wouldn't it be better to leave forever?
Even if she can't see the sword for now,
there might come a day when she can.
[Mysterious sound effect]
I'm trying to believe in something like a miracle.
I placed my bet that day.
There are many people watching here.
[I EXHALE]
Okay, just make one promise.
What, suddenly? What promise?
I promise not to touch that kid when I leave.
Really?
- Is it real?
- (Kim Shin) Sure.
The moment you try to take her away, I’ll come back to that house right away.
So just leave her alone.
When are you leaving?
The day after tomorrow, is that good?
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[SIGH]
[INSECT SOUNDS]
(Euntaek)
Did you not get caught?
What if you come all the way to my house?
If my aunt finds out, I'm dead
Did you not get caught? Is our aunt sleeping?
I don't know
(Euntaek)
Ugh, what a surprise
But what brought you all the way to our house?
Did you come to see me?
Should I say that?
What did you say?
I guess I was thinking about you, just for a moment
(Kim Shin)
So it seems I came to see you
Why?
What am I, trying to be a bride
or trying to be pretty
(Euntak)
Every day, I have to save your life
and create trouble for you
Why did you come to see me?
I guess you wanted to see this
I've seen it, so I'm leaving
(Kim Shin)
Aunt has disappeared
Since the house is empty, come in
Are you saying Aunt is gone?
Really? When?
(Kim Shin)
But why did you come when you didn't know?
Oh, I left something behind, so I'm here to pick it up
(Kim Shin)
What?
Just, you know
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
[I CAN HEAR THE SOUND OF THE WAVES]
You don’t need to know, uncle
Sure, then
I'm going
(Samshin)
Excuse me, I, black older brother
Brother, don't you need a hairpin?
I don't prefer pins
Um, then buy one and give it to your girlfriend
I don't have a girlfriend
(Samshin)
A girlfriend can come and go
and can be nonexistent and then present
But this, if you buy it, will always be there, okay?
(Samshin)
Take a look in the mirror, brother
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
(Sunny)
How much is this?
(Samshin)
Um
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
(Sunny)
I picked it up first.
Oh, but what, are you crying?
(Grim Reaper)
Huh?
[A HOLLOW LAUGH]
(Sunny)
Can you give it up?
I don't want it for free.
If you give me your phone number
I don't have that kind of thing.
You don't have a cell phone?
Are you poor?
It's just that I don't really need a cell phone
It's not that I don't want to give my number?
Cancel the concession.
[A MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
(Grim Reaper)
Give me your phone number.
Write down the number and leave it here, with the ring.
Let's start with introductions.
You need to know my name
to make a call, right?
Nice to meet you
I'm Sunny.
[DREAMY MUSIC]
Seonhee?
If that's good, let's do it that way.
Since it's a stage name anyway, it doesn't really matter.
[CALM MUSIC]
(Three Gods)
Card?
Cash?
Ah, who's going to pay for the money?
[Rhythmic music]
(Three Gods)
It doesn't matter who's paying.
Either way, both of us
will end up paying a very high price.
[HEAVY MUSIC]
I am
It's late
[I'M WEEPING]
[KIM SHIN IS WEEPING]
[THE MUSIC IS BUILDING IN ATMOSPHERE]
(Kim Sun)
I'm
fine
(Kim Sun)
If this is the end
then this is also my fate
So go on
Don't stop, go to His Majesty, General
[SUNNY EXHALES A BREATH]
[SUNNY'S SIGH]
[A CHILLING SOUND EFFECT]
(Ghost)
Are you really going to do this?
You're not even a goblin bride
Just come with me, okay?
You bitch
Are you even listening to what I’m saying?
Yeah, I'm wandering around alone too
so why don't you try being alone for a while?
The people you know
I'm going to mess with every single one of them
[CREEPY SOUND EFFECTS]
I'm going to kill that woman first
[SUNNY'S ANGRY BREATHING]
[Creepy sound effects]
(Sunny)
This fucking watermelon is a hassle
Nephew's shoes
Scatter, shipl, bibl, apl
[IT'S HUFFING]
(Ghost)
Ah, I'm scared, damn
[Stuttering]
Hey, that woman is scary.
(Euntak)
Boss, are you okay?
Honestly, tell me
Am I in a beauty off-season these days?
(Sunny)
Damn, my size came out perfectly
There should have been a call by now
Why isn't there?
Oh, that ring, that guy?
- First, calm down...
- It's hard to calm down
(Sunny)
He's the most handsome guy I've ever seen
Can you see my effort?
The skin care stuff I drink every day?
[SUNNY'S SIGH]
But why isn’t he calling?
[SIGH]
Good-looking men are all about their looks from the start.
- Just forget it.
- How can I forget?
Among the men I've met,
he's the only one who didn't give way to me.
[SUNNY'S SIGH]
(Sunny)
The ring was pretty.
It seemed just like me.
[SIGH]
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
Do you have a pen?
No, just call me.
[SMIRKS]
That was a bit funny.
Are you a science major?
The completion of a phone number is lips.
[A KISS IS GIVEN]
[THE DOOR OPENS WITH A CLICK]
[PEOPLE ARE BUSY]
(Worker)
Oh, be careful
(Euntak)
Hello
What’s all this? Are we moving to a new house?
(Landlord)
Didn’t you contact your aunt?
Your aunt put the house up for rent
We're moving in the day after tomorrow, but
I haven't finished packing at all
I'm the one suffering right now
Oh my
(Euntak)
She put the house up for rent?
Then what should I do?
What am I supposed to do?
(Landlord)
Why are you asking me that?
You should ask your aunt.
Your aunt took all the deposit money.
If you have anything to gather, hurry up, sigh.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC]
[THE WAVES CRASH]
Lover
[THE WIND BLOWS FIERCELY]
(Teacher)
Ji Eun-tak
You, take out everything in that bag and your pockets.
Hurry up.
[EUN-TAK'S SIGH]
[EUN-TAK OPENS THE BAG ZIPPER DIRECTLY]
[SHE RUSTLES OUT THE ITEMS]
[A HOLLOW LAUGH]
Teacher, this...
Isn't it quiet?
(Teacher)
You really carry everything that can catch fire.
Cigarettes? Aren't you going to take out a cigarette?
Is it your last conscience?
No, teacher
I really have my reasons
I don't smoke
(Teacher)
The kids said they saw you smoking, tsk
Let's keep it short, short, okay?
Show me your hands
Quickly
Both hands
[THE TEACHER SNIFFS THE SMELL]
[THE TEACHER'S AMAZEMENT]
Look how thorough this kid is
Smart kids are scary for this reason
Ji Eun-tak
I’m most scared of kids like you
who study well
In front, you act nice and pitying
But behind, you’re just cracking seeds
Kids like you
cause trouble when they go out into society
Then, truly innocent people
end up suffering, Eun-tak
Huh?
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
(Kim Shin)
Thank you
[SIGH]
Why the sudden alcohol?
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
You
(Kim Shin)
Where did the alcohol suddenly come from?
The more drinks, women, and meat, the better it is.
[Ridiculous sigh]
[Cracks open a beer can]
I upheld my integrity plenty when I was a general.
Were you a general?
[SMIRKS SLIGHTLY]
Back in the day, you wouldn't even have dared to talk to me, how bold of you.
Tch, what did you think I was?
(Kim Shin)
What were you?
[A SIGH]
I am
just throwing it around, what, was I a king?
Did you pack everything?
(Kim Shin)
Ah, that I
Well, it was so simple.
[A SIGH]
Goodbye
I'll call you.
I don't have a phone.
(Kim Shin)
That's why I said it.
[A SIGH]
[KIM SHIN'S SIGH]
(Grim Reaper)
What are you doing? It's chaotic.
Really, can one can of beer do that?
I don't know where you are.
Who?
You're not calling me.
Since you're not calling, I can't find you.
[A SIGH]
(Kim Shin)
Even though I wasn't omnipotent,
there was nothing I couldn't do.
But I can't find that one kid.
[CALM MUSIC]
Everything I have
is of no use at all
(The Grim Reaper)
That's not true
It's only good for wasting time
So what did you do before that?
I searched, every time like this
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
(The Grim Reaper)
Just call
You have a cell phone, right?
Ah
But I don't know the number
[SIGH]
Now I have to not know
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
[A HOLLOW LAUGH]
I found it
[THE WAVES CRASH LOUDLY]
[SAD MUSIC]
Mom
Are you doing well?
Did you go to heaven?
What is heaven like?
Is it better than here?
[sniffling]
Mom, I
[SOB]
Mom, I...
I'm not doing well
Nobody asks about me
[THE SKY IS RUMBLING]
Again? I'm really sick of it
A rainy life
[SOBBING]
I'm like this because I'm depressed
What is it?
Rain
It will stop soon
If the uncle is depressed, does it rain?
Yeah
Then how depressed is it during a typhoon?
That's not me; it's the Earth's sadness.
Have you been well?
It seems like the rain is about to stop.
I just felt better.
[CALM MUSIC]
I didn't call you, mister.
(Kim Shin)
Yeah, you didn't call.
I was busy too, going here and there...
I had a lot of work as well.
This is a big problem.
Why?
(Eun Tak)
Because every time it rains,
it'll seem like you're feeling sad, I guess.
It's overwhelming to deal with the accident,
and now I'm just worried about you.
Aren't you cold? Why are you like this?
I'm unhappy.
Now it just feels like a cold.
What?
My unhappiness.
(Euntak)
It comes back just when I'm about to forget it.
It tends to catch me at the right time.
Well, that's not something I said to poke at you.
(Kim Shin)
You don't really know what you're talking about, do you?
(Euntak)
It seems like there is something that gets to you.
Don't say that.
The phrase I hate the most is 'it gets to me.'
Then I chose the right thing.
[EUNTAK'S LAUGH]
Go ahead, your story, keep going.
I can't listen without tears
I'll try to hold on
Do you know that story?
(Euntak)
They say humans have four lives
The life of sowing seeds, the life of watering the sown seeds
The life of harvesting the watered seeds
The life of using the harvested things
How do you know that?
That's something only a lion says to the deceased
(Euntak)
I've been a goblin's bride for 19 years
I've heard the stories the ghosts tell
So I'm very unfair
What kind of life is 1-1, 1-2?
It doesn't go over 2
Why
To that person
Then?
There are many
Pat on the shoulder, stroke the head, five hundred chin
Gee, what about your hands?
My hands have been working a lot
so they need to rest
(Euntak)
Well, it's important
I'm saving up for when I get something like a bouquet
(Kimshin)
What, why?
(Euntak)
It's fine
A gift
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
Isn't it pretty?
- It's pretty
- (Euntak) Right?
[LAUGHTER]
What are you doing?
Petting your head
A greeting to wish you well
I'm leaving tomorrow
What about the luggage?
I asked during the day
I want to hear it again
Because it makes me happy
[The grim reaper's sigh]
[The doorbell rings]
A text has arrived
No, it's the doorbell sound
It's the first time in 60 years
(Grim Reaper)
Oh
What?
[EXCITING MUSIC]
What did I just say?
None of us pressed the doorbell
Oh man, why is this happening, it’s scary
Can you see it?
I can't do it?
Oh, what are you bragging about?
How can a grim reaper not see?
You have a
[DOORBELL RINGING]
[KIM SHIN'S STARTLED BREATH]
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SURPRISED BREATH]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
Is this the home of
Mr. Goblin? Oh, is it not?
(Grim Reaper) This is my house Did
you come to find me? On your own?
Do you have a prior appointment with me?
No, I’m at the wrong place...
Did they even tell you the address?
(Kim Shin)
What are you? How did you know to come here?
[The grim reaper's sigh]
(Eun Tak)
I asked the ghosts
where the goblin's house is.
[In a small voice]
But why is the grim reaper at this house?
(The grim reaper)
It seems like a couple's quarrel is currently ongoing.
Make sure to reach a good conclusion.
I’m in a bad mood right now.
[THE DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
Are you two living together?
[The door creaks shut]
Until today, why did you come?
I have something I didn’t get to say.
You know that thing.
(Eun Tak)
You're asking me what I see, right?
What happens if you see it?
Why are you asking? It won’t show up anyway.
Who says it won’t show up?
If it shows up,
do we have to get married immediately?
(Eun Tak)
If it shows up, is that a sign of a promise?
If it shows up...
You won’t leave, right?
Please don’t go.
Just stay here, in Korea.
Is that not allowed?
You
Really see?
What if you see it?
Prove it.
(Eun-tak)
Let's start with your
answer, what will you choose among one, two, or three?
I can’t see you, but I can
really see you, really,
[REALLY SEE YOU GASPING FOR BREATH]
This sword has
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
[IT RUMBLES]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
(Kim-shin) She says she sees the sword She
says she’s my bride, I’m really going to die now!
(Deok-hwa) Is she
really our uncle's bride?
Why is she our uncle's bride?
By God's mischief (Eun-tak)
This is a
great house for raising kids, let’s have
our baby and try to live happily ever after.
(Grim Reaper)
Ah, is that why marriage is said to be
a grave
(Euntak)
Uncle, is this maybe a honeymoon?
(Grim Reaper)
Hello, have you been well all this time?
[A HOLLOW LAUGH]
(Kim Shin)
I have made up my mind
I need to disappear
Before I want to live more
Before I become happier
The choice I have to make for you
Is to end this life
You are the Goblin's bride
Subtitles: Choi Hye-ran