[THEME SONG]
How did you know?
(Sunny)
Why don't you know?!
I said it's Kim Sunny.
[NERVOUS MUSIC]
Oh, it must be really cold for you?
I'll just get my coat...
(Sunny)
I haven't finished my story yet.
[Nervous sound effect]
[NERVOUS SOUND EFFECT]
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
[REWIND SOUND EFFECT]
What's wrong?
Why...
(Sunny)
What?
[Heavy music]
Are you okay?
Your already pale face is even paler now?
(Kim Shin)
Who is the woman you saw?
The woman I know
is my sister.
(Eun Tak)
It'll be glaring, glaring.
Ji Eun Tak
It’s too late to suddenly look closely, you know?
What kind of person is your boss?
Oh, I feel like I’ve heard this question somewhere before.
From the Grim Reaper?
The next question is
‘What do you like to have done?’ it seems?
Can’t you tell just by looking?
She’s a beautiful person, really beautiful.
I am
I'm not looking for a pretty person.
I feel like I've heard this somewhere before.
Really, why are you like this?
What, what is it?
[A FLUSTERED BREATH]
Oh, well, it's not like it's the first time I've held a woman's hand...
[AN ABSURD BREATH]
The size is just right, I
Don't even have a phone number now
Really, you didn't even tell me your name
(Sunny)
Just because I held your hand, you're looking at me like that?
Are you married, by any chance?
[A SURPRISED BREATH]
No.
Then it's the last one.
Always in black clothes.
No wonder your face is so white.
Are you from the NIS, by any chance?
(Reaper)
No!
(Sunny)
Then are you the reaper?
[CALM MUSIC]
Not laughing, it's a joke
[SIGH]
For now, just a married man, if you’re not from the NIS, that's fine.
I'm going in, it's cold.
[SUNNY'S BREATH TREMBLES FROM THE COLD]
[THE DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES WITH A BANG]
And Miss Sunny is
Who are you?
(Eun-tak)
Would you like a drink?
(Sunny)
Uh, I'm really in the mood for chicken and beer.
You should have a drink too.
[SHE EXHALES]
[SHE EXHALES AGAIN]
Hey there, brother.
Why do you keep looking at me since earlier?
(Kim Shin)
It's because you have the same name as someone I know, so it's fascinating.
Is your real name Kim Sun?
What characters do you use for your name?
(Sunny)
I don't use characters; I write it in English.
S, U, N, N, Y
(Kim Shin)
Have we met somewhere before?
We saw each other a few days ago, in front of the previous store.
At that time and this time too
Why do you keep calling me "oppa"?
Should I have called you 'this, that, hey, you'?
What exactly is the relationship with this person?
Do you know what that person is before you meet them?
[SUNNY'S SIGH]
(Sunny)
Were we supposed to exchange rings?
(Eun-tak)
Was that ring
what it meant?
Part-timer, you asked a good question
(Sunny)
What did that ring mean?
Speaking of rings...
(Grim Reaper)
Could you please return that ring?
The café I saw before, tomorrow at 1 PM
What could this possibly mean?
(Grim Reaper)
In fact, one
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
The woman in the scroll and
Ms. Sunny's past life have the same face
[Writing quickly with a pen]
In fact, two
The woman in the scroll
The woman I know
(Kim Shin)
Is my sister
Kim Shin's sister
Then the question
Is Ms. Sunny
(Grim Reaper)
The reincarnation of Kim Shin's sister?
Not yet, well
(Grim Reaper)
One fact again
The moment I first saw the woman in the scroll
I cried.
[TEARS DROP]
Fact two
The moment I first saw Sunny
I cried.
Then a question
[SIGH]
Why did I cry?
(Grim Reaper)
What is the nature of my feelings?
Is it related to the history of those two
and my erased memories?
[SIGH]
This too, well
'How much for a chicken?'
(Eun-tak)
You were making a big
fuss about buying the whole
store, but in the end, the Grim
Reaper paid for the chicken, right?
I was so flustered about that part (Eun-tak)
Ah, why was I so flustered all the time?
No, even though you weren't going to pay, why are you curious
about what relationship our boss has with the Grim Reaper?
Why, 'Tell me everything you
see about me,' isn't it like that?
Anyway, all men are the
same, whether they are
[HUMANS, GOBLINS, OR GRIM REAPERS, THEY JUST SLAM THE CUP DOWN]
That’s not the genre you think it is.
Is that the kind of genre it is?
(Euntak)
You told me not to hide anything from you anymore, but me?
Ah, were you perhaps waiting for this day?
So is that why I put it on the chicken restaurant?
Because our boss is pretty?
Now that I think about it
How could I have hired a part-timer?
What does that even mean?
I just narrowed down the options
(Kim Shin)
If you narrow it down to chicken restaurant
I'll go all in on that
If I say I'll join, I'll do it with confidence
And someone who sees that will pick me
Ah, what kind of bullshit is that
What bullshit?
(Euntak)
Then I have two wishes left
A part-time job and a boyfriend
Why do you keep fixating on the boyfriend?
(Kim Shin)
Is it Taehee or something
Break a leg for real
So that you can see if I'm your boyfriend or not?
You have to break something first for you to
'Ah, my boyfriend'
'Had a quirky personality, like a goblin'
Right, totally!
Sigh
Ah, what, are you getting angry? Tsk
[KIM SHIN'S SIGH]
(Euntak)
Ah, what? I didn't say anything.
[SIGH]
(Kim Shin)
Seeing you working a part-time job earlier,
it broke my heart.
I saw you properly for the first time,
[WITH SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Good night.
[THE DOOR CLOSES WITH A CLICK]
[EUNTAK'S LAUGHTER]
[GENTLE MUSIC]
Are you doing well?
Brother seems to finally
be doing well.
[Gentle music flows out]
(Grim Reaper)
What about the ring?
I temporarily took the ring and then...
If you tell me the reason
I have something to investigate
Due to the nature of the investigation, it's a bit detailed...
(Grim Reaper)
But Sunny, why did you pick up this ring, of all things?
It just seemed like it was mine
When you tried on the ring
Did you not feel anything?
I did feel something, exactly
I picked it up to meet this man
A man who cried upon seeing me for the first time
(Sunny)
A man who does not compromise
A man whose meetings are short and waiting is long
But I didn't know that man would take the ring like this.
[SUNNY SMILES SLIGHTLY]
Goodnight.
Thank you.
I will return it soon.
I don't know what kind of investigation it is,
but
my personality is not to be underestimated either,
so let’s share the details once the investigation is over.
(Sunny)
I have a stake in that ring too,
I'm going now, I have to do business in the afternoon.
[SUNNY GRABS HER BAG]
[THE GRIM REAPER SIGHS]
[KIM SHIN RATTLES THE FRYING PAN]
I think you're saying that because you don't know,
but isn't that dressing for that meal a bit off?
(Grim Reaper)
Ah...
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
Get a grip and prepare lunch. [The
Grim Reaper slams the plate down.]
Did you fail to take the ring?
I just borrowed it for a moment,
calling it taking is...
(Kim Shin) Why borrow
something you were given?
I saw you holding hands
yesterday. [The Grim Reaper's sigh.]
Why, did you have a grudge in a past life?
Don't play around. (Grim
Reaper) It's a private matter.
Even if I saw it, I can't say it
out loud, due to regulations.
You've come out as a very conscientious lion.
How can someone like you hide the grim reaper
and meet a human?
[THE SIGH OF THE GRIM REAPER]
Do you really have to say it like that
in the same situation?
What's the same situation?
I'm fated love,
so stop pouring ketchup on tofu.
(Grim Reaper)
Oh
[SIGH]
My sister's name was Kim Sun.
[I HEAR THE SIZZLING SOUND]
So I was a bit restless all night,
not even knowing if I was reincarnated or not?
If you were born with another face
There would be no way to recognize you
Seeing the fortunes and misfortunes of humans is all there is
What if your sister was reincarnated and you finally met
(The Grim Reaper)
Then what would happen afterwards?
After all, your sister
Wouldn't have any memories
Of her previous life
Just
Well, whether she is at peace in this life
Whether she is living a long, healthy life
Whether she is receiving love
Those are the things I'm curious about, you know
[The door opens and closes with a click]
She was beautiful, our little fool.
(Grim Reaper)
Do a bit more, now that we're on the subject
(Kim Shin)
What?
(Grim Reaper)
Your story
How you lived, how you died
(Kim Shin)
I've told you once, I was a general
I was a military official of Goryeo
Did you die on the battlefield?
No
By the blade of the lord I served
[KIM SHIN CLICKS HIS TONGUE]
(Kim Shin)
Where should I start, how should I begin
It's a story I've never told before
- Some salt
- (Grim Reaper) Okay
[THE SEASONING IS SPRINKLED HAPHAZARDLY]
A child was born
When he was born
His father, who had been an emperor, was already dead
(Kim Shin)
His mother’s status was lowly
And she too fell ill and died
[HEAVY MUSIC]
His father’s older brother was the emperor
In the royal family, there was no one on the child’s side
Only Park Jung-heon, a doctor at the National University
And his mentor
"Confucianism"
(Kim Shin)
After meeting Park Jung-heon
Strange things began to happen around the child
The nephew who was to inherit the throne died.
The questioning grand princes also die.
Finally, the eldest brother, the emperor, dies.
All were soldiers due to the royal family's hereditary illness,
but in the future, a child will learn
that they were all poisoned.
[THE EMPEROR EXHALES HIS LAST BREATH]
[THE EMPEROR'S LABORED BREATHING]
[THE EMPEROR COUGHS]
[HEAVY MUSIC]
[THE EMPEROR'S LABORED BREATHING]
As the princes and grand princes scream,
only one woman remains.
If by any chance the woman ascends the throne,
marry her to you and your sister
and protect the woman.
(Emperor) To only
walk the right path.
The wrong choice is a scheme.
Above all
Don't let me die.
Neglecting
I cared for you, Your Majesty
And making such a request
to your lord
Forgive
the order
I will uphold it
Taking a long time to poison everyone
Is it true that you made a child the emperor?
Park Joong-heon, that guy?
Why on earth?
Without even a moment to reduce the royal robes
[heavy music]
The child has ascended the throne
(Joong-heon)
There is a separate lineage for kings and queens
If you say he cannot be the emperor
(ministers)
Long live the Emperor!
(I will) create and nurture the emperor
with my own hands [The ministers bow down]
This world will be under the feet of my Emperor.
That Emperor will be under my feet.
Thus, I shall place the entire world under my feet.
May you enjoy a long life.
(Minister)
By the command of His Majesty the Late Emperor,
the date for the royal wedding has been set, Your Majesty.
Is she not the sister of General Kim Shin?
(Minister)
The character of Kim Shin and the integrity of his family
are unmatched compared to any noble lineage.
(Jungheon)
A royal marriage with the sister of a mere warrior,
His Majesty the Late Emperor said...
[ tense music ]
I wish the last breath
could have been saved a bit more
(Instead)
the Late Emperor said that Kim Shin is a loyal subordinate
a steadfast comrade who shared life and death on the battlefield
and a trustworthy
friend
(Kim Shin)
The Late Emperor's last words
became a variable in Park Jung Heon's plan to strengthen the royal authority
[SOFT MUSIC]
[LAUGHTER OF THE SERVANTS]
[THE SERVANTS' GASP OF SURPRISE]
[TENSION-BUILDING SOUND EFFECTS]
[AWKWARD LAUGHTER]
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
[TENSION-INDUCING SOUND EFFECTS]
[KIM SHIN'S FOOTSTEPS ECHO]
[A SIGH]
I didn’t see you all morning
(Kim Sun)
I thought I was getting married without even seeing my brother's face
If that were the case
I wonder why I came to see this ugly face
[A HOLLOW LAUGH]
Since my brother treasures me so much
The path to the palace is truly a flower road
But brother
How did your Majesty come to be?
Why are you curious about appearance rather than character?
Don't worry.
The castle is very clear.
Is that true?
How about me? Am I pretty today?
You're ugly.
Then I must not be pretty to Your Majesty either?
In that case, I guess I should go home?
Your Majesty has already seen you.
Me?
[SOFT MUSIC]
Perhaps that face was shining...
[KIM SUN SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(Kim Sun)
You came to see me
What does Your Majesty say about me?
You say I'm ugly
Chhee
You should come see your ugly sister often
I am a brother wandering the battlefield
No news is considered good news
Who knows?
[Smiling slightly]
Don't worry about me
I will be happy, dear brother
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
(Court Lady)
Your Majesty, please.
[KIM SEON’S SURPRISED GROAN]
It's heavy
(Kim Seon)
Ah
There is someone unmerciful deeply in my heart
Why the rush...?
To see Your Majesty
I will go
It seems better to come together.
[SOFT MUSIC]
In the grip of the humble,
[heavy music]
(Refrain)
One must apply the right amount of force.
Once you hold it tightly,
that humble and precious thing
will surely perish
by that hand.
[A SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
(Refrain)
'An insignificant age, a humble maternal side'
'An in-law even more insignificant than the maternal side'
During several sessions with some officials
at the drinking party of Minister Shin Cheol-joo,
it is said that a conversation flowed.
Isn't it true that there is no wrong statement?
The more there are no wrong statements,
the more it is said to be wrong
(Jungheon)
Cut off the neck of Shin Cheol-ju, who disgraced the royal family,
and chastise saying it was wrong
Show your strength
[SIGH]
(Kim Seon)
Do not stir the heart any longer
Do not blind the emperor's eyes any longer
The death of the Minister of State
was an unjust act
Everyone says their own actions are just
Only the Empress says it is wrong
Are you truly...
(Jungheon)
Is it that my heart has blinded my eyes?
Did the emperor close his eyes
- You bastard!
- (Jungheon) You bitch!
(Jungheon)
Though the former emperor gave birth to her
I raised her
I cannot be other than her father
It was I who placed her on the throne
It was I who entrusted the world into her hands
Am I wrong?
So, a mere sister of some military ruffian
Shut your mouth about admonishing
The one who should admonish you
is not me, but your brother
From the grave, you were sent to the borders.
Yes, your brother repeatedly conveys news of victory.
Isn't his intention sinister?
They say there are two kings in one country.
They say there are two suns in one sky.
[TREMBLING BREATH]
If this is not treason,
what then is treason?
[HEAVY MUSIC]
With anger and concern, I draw my sword.
Go as far as you can,
and do not come back if possible.
Your Majesty, those words...
Your Majesty, how could it be...
It is your consideration, Your Majesty.
(Kim Shin)
Command to defend the borders,
I defended the borders
Command to annihilate the enemy,
I annihilated the enemy
My sister is here,
the people are here,
The emperor's worries
Now you are doing them
(Young King)
Proclaim that he died gloriously
It will be a sorrowful message to convey
It is a royal command
Please do not favor the civil officials
(Kim Sun)
And do not belittle the military officials
Please
Call General Kim Shin, who is patrolling the borders,
And have him guard your side.
Above all, please
keep your distance from Park Jung-heon
Did it eventually come to this?
[TENSE MUSIC]
(Young prince)
Is your insignificance
ultimately becoming greed?
You, the insignificant
the only hope of your insignificant family
is that your brother?!
Your Majesty
(Young prince)
The king protects the people
How can a mere subject protect the king?
Do you know what you are asking for
before you ask it?
That person you call your brother
(Young King)
In a battleground with no chance of victory
I return alive time and again
I am becoming the deity of the marketplace
[Cheers from the people]
I told you not to come back like this
With each triumphant return
You mock my incompetence
With that sword that your brother possesses
How do you know if it will protect me or slay me!
Your Majesty
(Young King)
No one
Can become the deity of my people
And thus, it is rebellion
Your Majesty
(Jeongheon)
A mere barbarian is in power,
the scholars' family is collapsing
The authority of the imperial family is also like a candle in the wind
Strike the neck of General Kim Shin,
rebuke him for his mistakes
Show your strength
(Kim Shin)
Ultimately, from Park Jeongheon's mouth,
my name, Kim Shin, came out
[A TREMBLING BREATH]
[A SIGH]
[THE DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
[AN ARROW FLIES SWIFTLY]
(Kim Shin)
That was
the last sight of my sister
She was the sister of a barbarian
and a dignified empress.
[The soldier swiftly cut with a sword]
The road to the emperor was too far.
I couldn't reach in the end.
Even knowing I couldn't reach
Knowing everything, I
had no choice but to keep moving forward.
That place was my last battlefield,
and I had to die there.
[SIGH]
Why on earth?
(Kim Shin)
I broke my orders and came back,
overlooked the jealousy and fear of the young king,
and couldn't forget the late emperor's request to protect the woman.
I had to save the innocent lives of the nobles,
and above all...
My sister's death
Because I was keeping that fool safe
[THE REAPER'S SIGH]
[CLICKING THE TONGUE]
In front of someone without memories of their past life
I talked too much
The food has gotten cold
I have one more thing I'm curious about
(Reaper)
Have you ever seen
a ring like this?
You didn’t take it to give it to me, did you?
[The reaper's sigh]
(Kim Shin)
I don’t want to be in that kind of relationship with you
Focus a little
Look closely, carefully, haven’t you seen it?
Do you really think
you’re my little sister?
[The grim reaper's annoyed groan] (Kim
Shin) Is that why you’re asking about my past?
Try putting on the ring, let’s see what
happens (grim reaper)
Don’t come, I said
don’t come, Seon-ah, so
right now Are you being loved?
[THE GRIM REAPER’S DENYING GROAN]
I’m sorry to interrupt your cozy
time, but it’s not cozy.
I’ll just step out for a
moment. Where are you going?
Let’s go together.
You have to team
up with me now (grim
reaper) Okay, let’s get
out together as a set.
I want to be alone right now.
Our Seon-i liked being alone too.
Go out, go out!
[THE DOOR CREAKS OPEN AND SHUT]
[THE SIGH OF THE GRIM REAPER]
(Euntak)
Buy flowers and make sure to come see me.
Jung-hyun said.
He's in Paju.
(Kim Shin)
It's closer and nicer than Canada.
Uncle, the flowers go really well with you.
Any flower is fine.
Uncle is totally my style.
Anytime is fine.
Uncle has a really good personality too.
Of course, everything.
(Kim Shin)
Did I do something wrong?
(Euntak)
No.
Then did you do something wrong?
Then what is this sudden confession?
Comfort? Support?
Yes, stuff like that.
Well, specifically how am I your style?
It's strange and beautiful.
[SOFT MUSIC]
(Euntak)
Here it is, Go Jung-hyun.
"Go, Go Jung-hyun"
[sighs]
I’m here.
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECTS]
[meaningful music]
Mom?
Mom
I think it's right
[A MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
(Eun-tak)
Mom, yes, it’s right?
Sir, door, door, open
Library, hurry up
[A MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
[EUN-TAK'S URGENT BREATHING]
(Jung-hyun)
Ah, be careful, you might fall
[EUN-TAK'S URGENT BREATHING]
(Eun-tak)
Was she a friend of my mom’s?
Really?
Do you know my mom?
[Tense music]
Do you know Ji Yeon-hee?
Why do you think I was next to you?
[Hee-tak's surprised breath]
(Jung-hyun)
Since she's Yeon-hee's daughter
Back in our days, we really
ironed and coated them
Yeon-hee helped me a lot, my things
[A SURPRISED BREATH]
(Jung-hyun)
We promised in high school
That if we had babies, we'd buy pretty clothes for them
I couldn't make the clothes
but I protected Yeon-hee's money
Open it, the password is 4, 8, 6
[A TREMBLING BREATH]
[EUN-TAK TURNS THE LOCK]
(Eun-tak)
These bankbooks, no way...
Oh, right
Your aunt
kept saying that the bankbook disappeared all the time
That's Yeonhee's insurance money
[sad music]
The one on top is the most recent one, so
find it and add it to the college tuition
Congratulations on your acceptance
(Euntak)
Is this why
you couldn't go and were wandering around?
Because of me?
Well, while I was wandering
I got a bit delayed because I enjoyed watching you grow up
I should go now and
chat with Yeonhee
Are you going?
Now?
I'll go and
make sure to tell your mom everything without missing a thing.
(Junghyun) Your
daughter is really nice.
You say you study well.
I heard you went to a good university.
Well then, goodbye
[sobbing]
Already?
[EUN-TAK SOBS]
Thank you
(Eun-tak)
I'm really grateful for everything
With my mom
Make sure you both
become friends over there too
Goodbye
Bye
Take care, Ko Jung-hyun
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[TREMBLING BREATHS]
(Eun-tak)
Mom
You really had a good friend, didn't you
No, actually
She was my friend
I liked everything mom did for me
(Euntak)
Rice cakes, the feast
Scarf too
Jung Hyun as well
Dayo
[A SIGH]
Uncle too
Thank you for opening the door
(Kim Shin)
Am I that big of a person?
[LAUGHTER]
Are you mocking me?
Ah, it hasn’t rained lately, has it?
I’m holding back
because I’m afraid they’ll take me away from NASA
[EUNTAK'S LAUGHTER]
(Euntak)
[smiling]
NASA
It's been a while
You haven't changed one bit
You're still speaking informally
(Secretary Kim)
Mr. Yoo Jae-shin
- I'm sorry
- (Secretary Kim) Hehe
As you know, it's a more complicated person
I have something I want to ask you
Yes
(Kim Shin)
There is an insurance money
It's left by a mother before her child died
The child will turn twenty in September next year
Therefore, currently this money
is difficult to withdraw without the consent of the legal guardian, the aunt
[SECRETARY KIM'S TROUBLED GROAN]
(Secretary Kim)
The insurance money should go to its rightful owner, right?
Legitimately
[closes the document folder with a thud]
You don't have to worry.
I will handle it right away.
Then I
[SECRETARY KIM'S COUGH]
(Kim Shin)
Ah, one more thing
(Secretary Kim)
Yes
Thank you for growing up well
I am grateful for everything
[THE DOOR CLOSES WITH A CLICK]
(Aunt Eun-tak)
Your sister is dead
The child is young, the insurance money has come out
But if there are debts
You can't be a guardian
So what should we do, kindness is also a disease
To become a guardian
I paid off all that debt, I did.
(Your aunt Euntak)
So I received
the insurance money, but I can't
deposit it into my account since I
used loan sharks to pay off the bank debt!
So for now
Euntak put it into that girl's account, but
(Your aunt Euntak)
that damn account keeps disappearing, so
you can imagine how happy I would be to have that account, right?
I wonder if you understand what I'm saying?
[MOBILE PHONE OPERATING SOUND]
(Secretary Kim) The law will understand. You
admitted to attempting to defraud the insurance money.
[Funny music] Hey, what are you?
(Aunt Euntak) What is this
nonsense? What kind of attitude is that?
If I call our Euntak,
will it go out?
If I hold it, huh? If I
hold it, will it get dirty?
Am I gold or jade? I raised it, really
[scoffing] Don't talk
nonsense (Secretary
Kim) I will suggest two
methods: one, simply
return the full amount
to Miss Jin Euntak and
get out, this is a
simple method; and the
second, claim child
support in a messy way and
[GET OUT, WHICH IS A COMPLICATED
METHOD. CHOOSE ONE FROM THESE, SCOFF]
(Aunt Euntak) You really
misjudged the person.
[Exciting Music]
I'm heading towards the dark side
There are acquaintances all around, right?
[SIGH]
The person is mistaken, ma'am
The dark side
I know it better, okay?
What about Nari?
(Secretary Kim)
I handled it well
Deokhwa also took action as instructed
One desk, one chair
I told the new store employees to learn calmly
Yeah
Mr. Yudeokhwa?
Yes, I am Yudeokhwa
The store is neat and nice
Get to work
[STRAINED MOAN]
(Employee)
Here is the product manual
Memorize it all by tomorrow
[SOUND OF DESK OPERATING]
(Deokhwa)
Oh, go up, go up
Oh, go down, go down
Oh, turn
Oh, still stand
Mr. Yudeokhwa!
(Deokhwa)
Uh, Manager Jang Il-ok?
If the manager finds out the truth
It'll be quite a surprise, you know, me
Someone who is already high up starting from the bottom
A truly amazing surprise for someone
I know he is the chairman's grandson
[Comic Music]
(Employee)
Just do it according to FM
The chairman gave instructions,
[YOU SEE, DEOK-HWA'S AWKWARD SMILE]
So, if I memorize all of this in one
day, the manager would be really
[SURPRISED, RIGHT? HE CHUCKLES SLIGHTLY]
[A SURPRISED GASP]
(Laundry owner) Ah, yes,
customer, how can I help you?
I'm here to pick up a hat I
dropped off for dry cleaning.
(Laundry owner) Ah, that hat,
wow, that fabric is
really nice, is it Italian?
It's made in heaven.
Ah, no wonder
[awkwardly smiling] the
fabric there is good, just a moment.
(Laundry owner)
Oh, but why is it suddenly so cold?
Oh, wait a minute
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
[AN ARROW FLIES BY SWIFTLY]
[CELL PHONE VIBRATION SOUND]
No...
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
Hello
Is the investigation still ongoing?
I wasn't slacking off
Yes, still
It must be a complicated investigation
What were you doing just now?
Should I hold Sunny's hand one more time or not?
(Grim Reaper)
I was contemplating
It's driving me crazy
Then can't we catch her today? When she's at least one year younger
Today?
(Grim Reaper)
I'll be going out
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
(Sunny)
Don't contact me anymore
(Kim Shin)
Is it today?
What?
Can't you not wear that outfit?
Why, is it strange?
No
I was wondering if my advice would be a variable for your today
(Kim Shin)
Wear comfortable shoes
It'll be a long way back
The clothes are weird
When the laundry's done spinning, you can hang it up.
Anyway, you don’t do housework at all, seriously, damn.
Oh, you lucky girl.
Some people are at home
eating chicken legs alone.
And you have a guy to date.
(Sunny's friend)
Oh, a date on December 31st.
Oh, I’m proud of you, friend.
Today's date concept is
sweet and warm.
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
Hmm, pretty?
So damn pretty.
You shouldn’t let it show that you’re a year older during the date, tsk.
[A CUTE MIXED MOAN]
(The Grim Reaper)
I'm sorry for being late
It's hard to walk with so many people
But I did come before getting any older
Shall we walk toward Bosingak?
(The Grim Reaper)
Before that,
I would like to hold your hand
(Sunny)
Huh?
Right away like this? Just like that?
I'm too curious to wait
[SUNNY CLEARS HER THROAT]
(Sunny)
People's hearts are really strange, aren't they?
I want to act all aloof for no reason
Do you want to hold my hand?
Yes
Me too
I also want to hold hands
and hug, with Kim Woobin
(Sunny)
But at least I need to know whose hand I'm holding
and whose arms I'm falling into
You still haven't answered my question
What is your true identity, Kim Woobin
You haven't answered how you know my real name either
[Meaningful music]
Getting away with being handsome
is only until this year
In two hours, it will be next year
[AWKWARD BREATH]
Is this request too unreasonable?
I'm sorry.
I understand.
Then shall we stop, us?
[CALM MUSIC]
(Sunny)
Pushing inward along the path
Solving math problems with a drafting pencil is cute
Everything is good
But it can't go on any longer
I'll just take a break
Please don't contact me anymore
Even if we run into each other by chance, don't say hello
Happy New Year
[Playful music]
[The clock ticks]
[A HOLLOW LAUGH]
[A SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
[Knocking]
Mister, mister
(Kim Shin)
Come in.
What’s going on? I was sleeping and
then what?
[The clock keeps ringing] (Kim Shin)
Oh, I normally sleep like this, why?
Ah, I got it Uncle, listen
[WELL, THE CLOCK KEEPS RINGING]
What?
[THE CLOCK SUDDENLY STOPS]
Uncle, it’s 12 o'clock!
January 1st, New Year, I
[JUST BECAME AN ADULT, HOORAY]
(Kim Shin) So what? Who
cares? Why did you dress up?
(Eun Tak)
I have a prior engagement, I’m
going out because I'm an
adult now (Kim Shin) You.
.. [Kim Shin's
ridiculous laughter]
What kind of prior engagement is this at this hour?
- (Kim Shin) What on earth is wrong with you...?
- It's a prior engagement with the uncle.
So I got dressed just right, and I've been waiting since earlier, huh?
(Eun Tak)
You fool, do I have to say it out loud?
Uh, let’s make sure to do it from now on. Don’t make me anxious.
(Kim Shin)
Are you saying we should go out?
What do you want to do?
Will you do it for me?
(Kim Shin)
Whatever it is, if you tell me to do it, I’ll do that too.
[EUN TAK SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(Eun Tak)
Uncle, alcohol, alcohol, alcohol! Buy me some alcohol.
Street vendor, soju, chicken gizzards, full of romance.
[SHE SMILES SLIGHTLY]
Why?
[Eun Tak lightly pokes Kim Shin]
Then let’s go into the romance.
[Bright music]
[Sigh]
[THE DOOR SWINGS OPEN WITH A CLICK]
(Eun Tak)
Alright, cheers to the adults.
(Kim Shin)
Are you going to be okay...?
[EUN TAK EXHALES]
It’s romantic.
Oh, it’s written.
[SHE CHUCKLES]
(Eun Tak)
Is soju really like this?
Alcohol is just like this.
(Kim Shin)
When it gets hot, you really become an adult
Then, one more drink
[slams the glass down]
Pour, pour
- (Eun Tak) Cheers
- (Kim Shin) Cheers
Oh, sweet...
(Eun Tak)
Sweet
[Kim Shin's laughter]
(Man 1)
The painting is nice?
What’s with this clichéd development?
[HE SNIFFS]
Did you set this up, uncle?
That’s not it, but it is familiar
(Man 1)
I thought you lived in this neighborhood
I searched for you everywhere.
That bastard, he made me like this.
My hand is all messed up like this
And he's just playing around with a girl?
You’re dead today.
Today? Seriously?
Tell me everything you see.
(Man 1)
What are you talking about, damn it?
I’m just trying to make it fun for you.
(Kim Shin)
I’m eating snacks, drinking with me
I’ll be there soon.
Our battlefield is outside.
Come with me.
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
(Man 2)
Hey, what’s going on? Where did you go?
(Male 1)
I told you that guy is strange
Me, me and
(Male 2)
Damn
(Street vendor)
Oh, is it okay for your boyfriend to go out like that?
Those guys are such a menace in our neighborhood!
Oh, it’s fine
He’s not the type to go around getting beaten up
Auntie, just one more bottle of soju
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Should I take a classic approach for a change?
I used to be a warrior, you know
[MALE 1 SCOFFS]
I’m currently unemployed, you bastard
Because of you.
The life of a man is therefore tough.
You guys are the same.
(Kim Shin)
That's the reason I'm not letting it slide today.
It's going to hurt, whether you endure it or not.
What the hell are you saying? Damn it.
Hey, just ruin it.
[THE ROAR OF MEN]
[THE GROANS OF MEN]
[The shout of Man 3]
[The groan of Man 3]
[EUN-TAK'S GASP]
[THEY FIGHT NOISILY]
[BREATHING OUT HEAVILY]
[STRAINED GROANS]
[Continues to fight noisily]
(Eun-tak)
Do it.
[POUR THE LIQUOR SMOOTHLY]
[THE SHOUT OF MAN 4]
[THE MOAN OF MAN 4]
[Deep thrust]
[Scream of man 1]
[Strained moan of man 1]
[Comedic sound effect]
[THE MOAN OF MAN 1]
(man 2)
Catch a taxi quickly
[Surprised moan of man 2]
[Hits the tree]
[Scream of man 1]
(man 4)
This way, this way
(Euntak)
Alright, let's start over
Let's begin the romance
[EUNTAK EXHALES]
Is it still romantic?
More than before
Dim light, simple snacks
(Eun-tak)
Bitter soju
Ruthless emotions
Romance is everywhere
If only there was one more thing, it would be perfect
What?
The first kiss
Back then, that was just a peck
No moving
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[KIM-SHIN'S SURPRISED BREATH]
[Kim-shin's sigh]
(Eun-tak)
That's unfair
(Kim-shin)
You, you...
Did you forget that I'm the goblin bride?
I won't get caught, I
[SIGH]
[A MIX OF AEGYO AND MOANS]
It means you absolutely can't escape.
But you didn't escape?
It was hard to escape just once.
Perfect.
[LAUGHTER]
Did she get dumped?
Did I get dumped?
[UPSET SIGH]
[SIGH]
[THE DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES WITH A CLICK]
(Grim Reaper)
What are you doing, other person?
(Kim Shin)
Right, what are you doing?
Good morning.
(Eun Tak)
Since it’s the New Year
And I have so much to be thankful to the uncles for
I was in the middle of making rice cake soup.
I also seasoned buckwheat jelly.
It's commendable from the new year.
I got money from my part-time job at the ski resort,
so I bought good beef.
[A SATISFYING MOAN]
(Grim Reaper)
Ah, please leave the beef out of my rice cake soup.
Yes
Ahh
On foggy nights, the uncles were coming
(Euntak)
It feels just like yesterday when they walked in a model-like way.
Already the new year, huh?
Back then, the uncles were really cool.
Even in the terrifying moments, they were super cool.
[EUNTAK SMILES SLIGHTLY]
Please wait a little longer.
Ah, I didn't buy green onions.
It's quite awkward if there's no green onion in the rice cake soup.
Green onions are important.
- Should we go?
- Should we try it?
[THE DOOR SWINGS OPEN]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
[MOTORCYCLE HORN]
(Man 5)
[Shouting]
Hey, you crazy guys, won't you move?
Seriously, don’t you walk on the sidewalk?
The author seems to be saying to walk on the sidewalk
like they're giving new year's wishes right now.
Since the new year's wishes are appreciated, I won't harass you.
Wishing you a lot of blessings in the new year.
We're cool.
Happy New Year
[WE LAUGH TOGETHER]
(Kim Shin)
What a righteous friend
(The Grim Reaper)
Even in these modern times, there are such friends
(Kim Shin)
How beautiful
Enjoy your meal
It needs to taste good to eat it happily
(Eun Tak)
I'm good at cooking
Happy New Year, uncles
Hope you receive lots of blessings too
I broke up with Sunny
What did you say to break up?
'I'll dump you'
[SIGH]
(Eun-tak)
That means 'I got dumped, so you contact me first.'
[I TAKE A BREATH]
They asked about my identity.
(Eun-tak)
Whoa, that's intense.
[The Grim Reaper's sigh]
But the Grim Reaper is a bit negative.
How about calling me an angel?
It's the same genre.
Cheer up, fighting.
[The Grim Reaper's sigh]
(Kim Shin)
That's how everyone grows up.
At 300 years old, it's the time to be particularly hurt and all.
It's okay.
[SIGH]
(Kim Shin)
Why?
Let me tell you another fact.
To obtain an answer, one must approach
those who are close to the answer.
What are you talking about?
[KIM SHIN'S SURPRISED GROAN]
(Kim Shin) Hey! What
are you doing, stop it!
[Kim Shin's straining groan]
(Grim Reaper)
As
expected, you can't see anything, it's just
warm, ah, clasp, clasp, it hurts, it hurts, clasp...
(Kim Shin) Hey, what are
you going to do with my hand?
I had a great time with the rice cake
soup (Kim Shin)
What about my hand,
this hand, ah, it's dirty!
[AH, IT'S DIRTY, IT HAS TO
BE CUT OFF, SOFT MUSIC]
[EUN TAK BLOWS AIR THROUGH HER LIPS]
Disinfection,
is this enough?
[THE DOOR CLICKS OPEN AND SHUT]
(Kim Shin)
Okay, got it, understood
It’s all done, the disinfection
It's okay now, don't worry
(Eun Tak)
So, pay for the rice cake soup, got it?
(Grim Reaper)
Why are you here? Weren't we going to the supermarket?
(Kim Shin)
Ah! It's sweet potato!
I've never had sweet potatoes before
Seriously, seriously, it’s my very first time
It's not just my first time eating sweet potatoes
It feels like it's my first time acting like I'm eating sweet potatoes
(Eun Tak)
Oh my goodness
As expected, living in the same neighborhood, it's a global village era
How could such a coincidence happen?
(Kim Shin)
What are you doing? In front of such a coincidence
Aren't you two going to greet each other?
We decided not to greet each other if we bump into each other by chance
(Kim Shin)
Did you decide not to greet each other?
[EUN TAK'S AWKWARD SMILE]
The two of them today overall
Are like the yolk and the white
Fried egg
[PLAYFUL MUSIC]
(Kim Shin)
Sorry
Oh...
(Kim Shin)
[smiling slightly]
Aha
It's the bean sprouts, the stem, the head
[grand music]
[displeased breath]
You like bean sprouts, right?
(Euntak)
Because of you, everything's ruined, it's ruined
(Kim Shin)
No, the two of you are...
(Euntak)
I'm sorry
This wasn't supposed to include this uncle in the operation
Forget it
But you saw Sunny, right?
[THE DOOR SHUTS WITH A CLICK]
And why would you eat sweet potatoes when you don't even have five thousand won?
(Euntak)
No, what if two perfectly normal-looking people
don’t even have five thousand won combined?
I can’t understand it sometimes
This was paid for by the boss, so
what are we going to do?
Five thousand won was an unexpected variable
From now on, I’ll definitely carry cash in advance...
(Euntak)
That’s enough
Today we failed the operation
with no income at all
Because of that guy
Hmm, we may have failed the operation, but
we still have income
(Euntak)
Ah, me, this person
[THE DOOR OPENS WITH A CLICK]
(Grim Reaper)
I’m going to work
Today's concept is
an angel
[KIM SHIN'S REALIZING GROAN]
It's all because of you
[The door swings open and closed]
(Eun-tak)
Wow, amazing
[BREATHING OUT WITH A PUFF]
[A SATISFYING GROAN]
[CALM MUSIC]
CEO, over here
[NERVOUS BREATHING SOUNDS]
(Eun-tak)
I’m really natural, right?
I don't seem like an illegal immigrant, do I?
I don’t seem like a kid who just came to a foreign country, right?
[English]
I'm doing well
[A SIGH]
In the end, you bought that, right?
Trying to meet the representative or something
[SNICKERS]
[A GROAN MIXED WITH IRRITATION]
[SMIRKS]
So that was something I was supposed to buy for you
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
(Grim Reaper)
It was her who said she was dumped
So why do I keep feeling like I'm the one who was dumped
I don't really know
(Doctor)
The time it takes for people to heal from emotional pain caused by a breakup
Varies for each person
Rather than focusing on quickly helping to recover
What am I recovering from?
Focus on that.
Ah, focus.
(Grim Reaper)
Thank you for the consultation, teacher.
[Significant music]
Have some tea.
It helps me forget the memories of this world.
[SIGH]
I feel like I wasted my studies.
(Doctor)
Why go as far as getting a doctorate?
You waste your youth.
You were my last patient.
Thank you for taking the time.
(Chairman Yoo)
Oh, here I am, darling.
Where have you been?
I'm just going to buy something for a moment.
I can't sleep and it's lonely.
(Chairman Yoo)
I came to play a game of Go.
These candlesticks and tableware,
I should set a date to clean them at some point.
I'll do it on a nice day, so don't worry.
So, shall we play a game of Go after a long time?
(Kim Shin)
You know, when you were a kid,
I taught you how to play Go,
but these days, I always lose.
(Chairman Yoo)
Well, I'm playing like it's a life-or-death situation.
[LAUGHTER]
Did you think I wouldn't?
[TENSE SOUND EFFECTS]
[HEAVY MUSIC]
It's Gonma, Nari
(Chairman Yoo)
I will never back down
[CHAIRMAN YOO'S LAUGHTER]
Where...
[CHAIRMAN YOO'S TROUBLED GROAN]
[CHAIRMAN YOO SLAMS DOWN THE GO STONE]
[CHAIRMAN YOO'S LAUGHTER]
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
(Shin)
Live immortally alone
Watch the deaths of those you love
No death will ever be forgotten
(The Barber)
You seem to be going somewhere nice, Chairman
Yes, I think so.
[LAUGHTER]
[SIGH]
[THE DOOR SWINGS OPEN]
[THE DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
I always like drinking
during the day.
It's cold to drink
during the day, now.
(Grim Reaper) What happened?
The list will come.
Jieun-tak's list?
No, Chairman Yoo
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
Did you tell Chairman Yoo
about it?
(Kim Shin)
Is there anything good for a human to know their own life and death
(Grim Reaper)
What about Deokhwa?
Isn't it better to know?
Wouldn't it be better to let them know
so there are no regrets?
In front of death, everything is a regret
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
Chairman Yoo asked about you
He said to ask how your friend who's visiting is doing
He must be asking while knowing everything, right?
What, did you get dumped?
[HE CHUCKLES]
(Kim Shin)
Have you tried contacting her?
I couldn't
If I do this time
I really have to come out and say what I am
The way you look
is definitely that of a grim reaper, what
Isn't that woman a bit slow?
Is that all?
- (Kim Shin) What?
- The feelings I get from Sunny
There's more
Is there?
That woman
I felt had an undeserved name
To have the same name as my sister
Good thing we broke up
Every time I saw you, there
was nothing about you that I liked.
And if you listen quietly,
there is no logic at all.
Ms. Sunny is being cursed.
I think I should stop.
Oh, it's comforting?
(The Grim Reaper) There's
something I haven't told you.
It's about what Sunny
saw in her past life.
- You said it's a secret?
- (Grim Reaper) Sunny.
It seems like your younger
sister has been reincarnated.
Is it you, Sunny? Not you?
Sunny's face in her past life
The face of the woman
in the scroll you have
It was the same.
Are you sure?
What did you see?
(The Grim Reaper)
The woman I saw was
I'm standing in the
middle of the palace.
(The Grim Reaper) Wearing
white clothes and looking dignified.
I was hit by an
arrow in the chest.
I collapsed, bleeding.
I told you that.
Even if it wasn't white clothing
I feel like I didn't even
talk about the bow.
(Kim Shin) Is there anything else?
Haven't you seen anything more?
I rode in a carriage and
smiled while looking at someone.
Through the small window
(The Grim Reaper)
Asked with a smile
I'm today...
(Kim Sun) Am I pretty today?
(The Grim Reaper)
Answering her question
There was a voice.
- 'Ugly...'
- (Kim Shin) It's ugly.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
Your younger sister
Is that right?
That's right.
[TENSION-INDUCING SOUND EFFECT]
[SOFT MUSIC]
(Kim Shin) All the time I
spent with you was dazzling.
The weather is nice.
Because the weather is not good
The weather is just right so
Every day was good.
Subtitles: Choi Hye-ran