[THEME SONG]
[Tense sound effects]
[Kim Shin's pained groan]
[TENSE MUSIC]
Why? Does it hurt?
[Kim Shin's labored breathing]
Is it because of the sword?
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[Kim Shin's labored breathing]
[Euntak's trembling breath]
[HEAVY SOUND EFFECTS]
[Kim Shin's labored breathing]
[Euntak's trembling breath]
[TENSE SOUND EFFECTS]
[HEAVY SOUND EFFECTS]
Uncle
[LABORED BREATHING]
The sword is grabbing me
[SURPRISED BREATH]
(Euntak)
Wait a moment
[ROUGH BREATHING]
Just wait a moment, I will pull it out
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[PAINFUL GROAN]
Ah, it’s moving
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[HEAVY MUSIC]
[THE ELECTRONIC BOARD CRACKLES]
[TIRE SCREECHING SOUNDS]
(Kim Shin)
The prophecy was right
The future I saw was right
Because of this child now I
Can end this immortal curse
And return to nothingness
Humans' lifespan is only a hundred years
Turning around to see once more
Is it my immortal life
Is it your face
Ah...
It seems to be your face
[EUNTAK'S TREMBLING BREATH]
[A STARTLED BREATH]
Huh? Uncle, are you okay?
It seems like the question has changed
[I SMILE SLIGHTLY]
Is that so?
Oh my, I'm going to die
I'm sorry, were you very surprised?
[A GROAN OF DENIAL]
You didn't know either, right?
That it would hurt this much
(Euntak)
Because until now, no one has ever caught me
But
Uncle, you can really fly?
I didn't ask you to show me like this
This is a piece of cake
Let's be determined
It seems like this isn't easy
(Eun-tak)
But to be honest,
I'm more surprised by the sword moving
[AND I SLIGHTLY SMILE]
It's such a relief
With this, I really prove that I'm a bride, right?
[SOFT MUSIC]
This is good
Is that not good?
It's good
See?
I'm really a bride, you know.
It was such a destiny
Destiny
Wonderful
[LAUGHTER]
(Deokhwa)
Ah, why isn't this uncle coming?
I need to complete this errand to get my allowance
What's going on today...
[THE DOOR OPENS WITH A CLICK]
[The door closes with a click]
It's here?
Uncle, were you on the second floor?
Ah, I was waiting the whole time
Uncle, quickly take a look at this
Is this perhaps you, uncle?
But what are we supposed to do like this? Solve it
Is it really you, uncle?
(Kim Shin)
I don't have the energy to explain, don't ask
There's no time, so hurry up
Ah, what on earth have I done?
Grandpa, from now on
please listen carefully to what I'm saying
Well, it's about uncle
No, not me, it's about uncle
Secretary Kim, from now on
please listen carefully to what I'm saying
As of now, the Cheonwoo Group
secretary's office and IT department are all mobilized...
No, not me
Ah, I'm not talking about me!
[SIGH]
Uncle in the back room, let's go somewhere together.
[With a sleepy voice]
Where?
(Deokhwa)
My uncle lacks social skills,
and has destroyed the whole society.
[EXCITING MUSIC]
(Secretary Kim)
From now on, I request that all the videos uploaded on the
portal and various SNS platforms that allow link sharing
be taken down.
Let's stop it before it becomes a bigger issue,
quickly and accurately.
You can use big data,
and when contacting the person in charge,
start with "We will remove all advertisements for
Cheonwoo Group's holding company and subsidiaries."
The work will be easy and quick.
So
Let’s start
(together)
Yes
[THE SOUND OF TYPING ON THE KEYBOARD IS LOUD]
[PEOPLE ARE ALL ON THEIR CALLS]
(Deokhwa)
Okay, everyone
[A STRAINED GROAN]
(Deokhwa)
Alright, alright, first of all
Owners of cars and property that have
been completely wrecked, please come this way.
Those who have witnessed something tremendous
and have had their mental state completely shattered,
please stand over there.
[Exciting music]
[Sigh]
The dented car
was damaged by an unexpected gust of wind, that’s all.
(The Grim Reaper)
Money is an unexpected fortune that falls from the sky, that’s all
You have not seen me today either
[Mysterious sound effect]
Now, next
(Man 1)
Me
But isn’t it too dark here?
I’m not feeling well
Could you please look at my eyes for a moment?
[Mysterious sound effect]
(The Grim Reaper)
The crushed car
Is damaged by an unexpected gust, that’s all
Money is an unexpected fortune that falls from the sky, that’s all
You have not seen me today either
Well, next, next, next example, yes,
that, quickly
Yes, come over here,
yes, yes, you can come closer, look
at the eyes, eyes, yes, look
(Deokhwa)
Yes, what kind of car
model does the next person driving this week have?
Just deleting this file will be the end
[Grim Reaper's sigh] [Exciting music]
(Grim Reaper) Could you please
take a look at my eyes for a moment?
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
(Deokhwa) No, how did you cause
a couple's fight to smash 30 cars?
Do you know how much my uncle went through with me?
He endured a lot, thank you
Don't thank me
It's just that I don't have the energy to fight
[KIM-SHIN'S SIGH]
(The Grim Reaper)
Let's postpone this fight
It's already a mess
Even if you feel uneasy, I'm worse
What do you know? Whether it's better or worse
Hey
I'm like this, just this much like this...
Ha, done
[Slaps knee]
Let's stop
(The Grim Reaper)
What, did you come back from the dead or something?
[THE GRIM REAPER'S DISPLEASED SIGH]
[THE DOOR OPENS WITH A CLICK]
Ha, why are you all like this, seriously?
[The door closes with a click]
[THE MEDICINE RATTLES AS IT'S TAKEN OUT]
[DEOK-HWA'S SIGH]
[SOFT MUSIC]
[MYSTICAL SOUND EFFECTS]
[THE ELECTRONIC BILLBOARD CRACKLES]
Buckwheat guy, we don't have to go out anymore
I've really confirmed as a bride
[LAUGHTER]
[EUN-TAK'S PAINFUL MOAN]
(Eun-tak)
Ah, my whole body aches
[EUN-TAK'S ARDUOUS GROAN]
[A SOUND OF SOMETHING CRASHING LOUDLY IS HEARD]
Huh?
Oh, sir, what's going on?
You’re not dead, are you?
It’s just the effects of the medicine, let him sleep
(Euntak)
If he sleeps like that, he’ll catch a cold
I’ll hold him like this and take him to the room...
(Reaper)
Yes, that’s fine
If you can, take good care of him
(Euntak)
What’s wrong?
Why did you take the medicine?
Are you still in pain?
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
(Reaper)
Who on earth are you
to be so concerned?
[SIGH]
"Closing time"
[SUNNY EXHALES]
[INHALES]
Our home is delicious
[CRUNCHING]
Thirty-seven
Thirty-eight
Let's go home after fifty people pass by
[A MATCH FLICKERS]
I overlooked it
I don't have a fever but
[CALM MUSIC]
[EUNTAK'S SIGH]
A grown adult
Can just collapse and sleep anywhere
Because I'm in pain
Did I wake you up?
Smell of a patch
[SMILES LIGHTLY]
Poking around here and there
(Euntak)
Does it hurt a lot for you too, uncle?
You said it was okay earlier.
It was a lie.
You're always lying.
(Euntak)
Get better soon.
I know where it hurts.
Where does it hurt?
First love is really painful.
What, was she really pretty?
(Euntak)
Well, there's something that was really copied.
A lot.
Every day.
You're pretty.
You're in a lot of pain.
You're critical right now.
Sleep well, so your mouth can move quickly.
[EUNTAK'S DISPLEASED BREATH]
[EUNTAK'S SIGH]
[A SIGH]
Don't go.
(Eun-tak)
Why me?
Someone who thinks of their first love
What’s so pretty about it?
Is that something you say to a bride?
If you look closely, there’s a pretty side
So don’t go
Did I say don’t do this 'chi-eut' thing or not?
Chi, how petty
Ah, me
[A FAINT BREATH]
Please add all the vegetables
and warm the bread
(Clerk)
Yes
(Eun-tak)
The bribe you ordered has arrived
Hmm, good
Where's the item?
(Eun-tak)
Can you really interpret it?
As a third-generation chaebol, you should start learning the Thousand Character Classic from the age of three...
But what is this?
It's my older brother's uncle's background check
Especially regarding first love
A secret between us
This girl
I really prefer this kind of background check
(Deok-hwa)
Let's see
(Eun-tak)
This character means 'to listen.'
Just in case you didn't know
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
You even had a sandwich
You can't not know, I don't like it
Yeon-seo's side
- Yeon-seo?
- (Deok-hwa) Oh
It's a sad love confession.
'Living for a hundred years, one day'
(Deokhwa)
'On a suitably nice day'
[EUNTAK HUFFS]
(Euntak)
I thought maybe, but it turns out it's true.
I know who it is.
[EUNTAK SLAMS THE NOTEBOOK SHUT]
Who is it?
I've heard everything.
[EUNTAK OPENS THE BAG WITH A JERK]
[CLOSES THE BAG WITH A JERK]
[EUNTAK'S ANGRY BREATHS]
Well, that's possible.
There could be one woman in nine hundred lives that you can't forget.
- Is it one person?
- Isn't it?
- I don't know.
- Ah, surprise, well,
anyway, it's about Kim Shin.
Who is Kim Shin?
It's my uncle. Is
our uncle Kim Shin?
Our uncle is Yoo Shin-jae.
Yes, well, to explain,
it's long, but anyway,
that uncle has a
sword stuck in his chest.
Does our uncle have a
sword stuck in his chest?
Ah, what do you know?
Ah, what's a sword?
(Deok-hwa) When you keep talking about swords
like this, it gives me a sword complex, you know?
If you keep doing it like this...
I won't tell you what I know
[A WELCOME BREATH]
What is it that only you know, Oppa?
[KIM SHIN'S PUZZLED BREATH]
(Kim Shin)
You cried after seeing this painting? That guy?
Yeah, I cried a lot
(Deokhwa)
I said I couldn't, I said I couldn't
But the uncle in the last room keeps saying to come, to come
Did you really cry? Why?
I wouldn't know, you should go and ask him, Uncle
(Deokhwa)
Let's get angry, hurry up
Huh? Huh? Huh?
Why did you see my painting?
She said she was stopped
You cried, right? Why are you crying?
I’m not crying
(The Grim Reaper)
I'm also perplexed, so I've thought about it from various angles
Isn't it Stendhal syndrome or something?
It was really moving
and my heart was overwhelmed
(The Grim Reaper)
But who is it?
[Tense music]
The woman in this painting
What are you going to do with that knowledge?
(The Grim Reaper)
It just feels like I've seen her somewhere
[AN ARROW SUDDENLY FLIES BY]
(Kim Shin) Who is
this woman you saw?
The woman I know is my
[SISTER, SUSPENSEFUL SOUND EFFECT]
(Deokhwa) Uncle,
did you have a sister?
Have you actually seen my sister?
(Kim Shin) Think
carefully, where
did you see her?
[AH, SISTER, SIGNIFICANT MUSIC]
I wonder if she’s one of my
deceased ones but that’s not
entirely accurate. Has this
child been reincarnated? When?
It’s not accurate; I've
taken dozens of souls
over the centuries. Do you
remember all their faces?
It just feels like I’ve seen her
somewhere, so I’m guessing like that.
There is no memory, only emotions.
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
I was just really sad.
My heart hurt so much.
(Deokhwa)
Uncles
I know.
I think I know.
Isn't the uncle in the last room the reincarnation of his sister?
Try saying "older brother" once, uncle in the last room.
(Together)
It dies!
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
[A DEEP SIGH]
[Clearing the throat]
Oh...
[A SIGH]
Older bro...
[LION 1 BREATHES OUT]
(Lion 1)
Did you hear that, senior?
The story of Kim Chasa from Janghang-dong?
Why about Kim Chasa from Janghang-dong?
(Lion 1)
He went to pick up a deceased person, and guess what?
That deceased was his wife in a past life.
So he dealt with that deceased and other omitted cases and ran away together.
So?
That's as far as it goes.
I don't know what happened afterwards.
They probably weren't caught?
How did they remember their past life?
I don't know.
So everyone is feeling uneasy.
(Lion 1)
I've been drinking every day lately.
I just end up thinking too much.
They say if you commit a great sin in your past life,
you become a grim reaper.
What kind of sin,
how great of a sin could it be?
Did they erase it completely so I wouldn't suffer?
Am I supposed to atone through this work?
It must be a divine consideration, right?
Whether I remember or not,
it must all be the will of God.
I'm just curious about what God's will is
in returning the memories I've lost.
In many ways.
[THE CHILDREN ARE CHATTERING]
[A SIGH]
(Woman 1)
Jinyoung
Let's go quickly
[WOMAN 1'S LAUGHTER]
- Was it fun?
- (Child 1) Yeah
What should we eat?
[WOMAN 1'S LAUGHTER]
[A SIGH]
I'm out
[HEAVY MUSIC]
(Grim Reaper)
Stop drinking too much
(Reaper 1)
Thank you for your hard work
Mom, where is this?
I think it's a tea house?
(Child 1)
Ah, what are we going to drink?
Mom, what are you going to order?
Mom
Ordered heaven
(Woman 1)
I’m trying to give it to Jin-young
Heaven?
The heaven you ordered has arrived
Thank you
Mom, why are you crying?
[WOMAN 1 SOBS]
[SLIGHTLY SMILES]
[A BIRD CHIRPS]
(Eun-tak)
What are you doing?
Oh, you startled me
What are you doing here right now?
(Eun-tak)
I was on my way to the library
[Kim-shin’s sigh]
What about you, sir? Do you know this house?
Who are you?
Step aside for a moment
[SYMBOLIC MUSIC]
(Kim Shin)
Open the window and ventilate
Lock the button
It'll be necessary
Let's go
(Child 2)
Dad
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
[THE SURPRISED GASP OF MAN 2]
How did you get here?
I took a taxi and showed the address
It cost 5,200 won
(Child 2)
We're going to here
(Samshin)
I know where it is
Put on your seatbelt
Dad, I'm hungry
Huh?
(Man 2)
Oh, here
(Child 2)
Dad, I missed you
[SMILES SLIGHTLY]
Dad too
[THE MAN IS SOBBING]
[A BIRD IS CHIRPING]
(Euntak)
Today is a bit nice too.
Sometimes parents, children, and siblings
become
guardians for each other.
I’m just handing over the sandwich.
It’s the author’s daughter who is saving the author.
Ah, that’s nice too.
The price of the sandwich isn’t cheap.
Thank goodness Chairman Yoo is doing well.
[EUNTAK'S SMILE]
But you know
the sword, I mean
Why did it suddenly move?
It wasn't even caught, right?
(The Grim Reaper)
Shouldn't there be something more powerful than a curse?
For example,
like true love?
[FUNNY MUSIC]
Don't you have anything to say to me?
- I don't
- You must have something
(Eun-tak)
Ah, that? I do have one thing
(Kim Shin)
See, you do
Don't hold back, just talk, it's all obvious
It's okay
No matter what you say, I know I'm someone who can accept it without prejudice
(Eun-tak)
I know you have a lot of money
Is it okay to just stay at home?
Is that all you wanted to talk about?
All you did during the Goryeo Dynasty was work for the country
Right?
Hey, have you said everything?
I had a job too, you know?
[Exciting music]
It may not be immortality
But you can really not get drunk for a long time
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
[INHALES DEEPLY]
It may not be immortality
But you can really stay fragrant for a long time
[A SATISFYING MOAN]
It's not immortality, but we can definitely enjoy a long time together (Woman 2)
But why are you speaking informally?
(Ah, Secretary Kim)
I'm
sorry, customer, Mr.
Yoo Jae-shin - I'm sorry -
(Ah, Secretary Kim) Oh, I'm
sorry about that too
(Eun-tak)
So you really stayed home, huh?
What do you mean by not staying?
What does it mean to not stay?
It means lacking [smiling] Ah, I...
(Kim Shin)
I've really never heard such a thing
before, really for the first time, really, yes, my
first love
Didn't give me this kind of criticism.
I can see you're hearing this for the first time.
Are you jealous right now?
[YOUR FLUSTERED BREATH]
(Euntak)
[smiling]
No, what
Ah, why would I be jealous?
I don't even know whether you're from Goryeo or Joseon
or when you lived.
Well, when did we meet? Goryeo? Joseon? Mid-Joseon? Late Joseon?
Well, I guess you must have been pretty elegant
But you know, first loves
are usually unattainable.
You should go in, don't wait
because you’ll be late.
[A SMIRK]
[CALM MUSIC]
Who says it's unattainable?
I don’t want that.
- Hey
- (Jeonghyun) Oh
(Euntak)
What?
[EUNTAK'S ANNOYED GROAN]
[COINS CLINKING SOFTLY]
What’s 'yay'?
[VENDING MACHINE OPERATING SOUND]
Is it not fun?
(Jeonghyun)
Everyone thought it was fun back in our day.
Lame.
[EUNTAK CLICKS OPEN THE COIN SLOT]
(Jeonghyun)
But have you gotten a lot dimmer lately?
[THE SLOT CLOSES WITH A THUD]
(Euntak)
Really? Is it because I'm getting older?
[EUNTAK PUTS THE COINS IN THE MACHINE WELL]
[VENDING MACHINE OPERATING SOUND]
(Jung-hyun)
But why do you
spend money on this when I can't even drink it?
It's a waste.
If not me, who will take care of your coffee?
[Significant music]
[Jung-hyun snickers]
Did you do well on the college entrance exam?
Yeah, I did well.
[JUNG-HYUN'S EXCLAMATION]
(Euntak)
So tell me before it's too late.
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
[FOOTSTEPS ECHO]
(Euntak)
Other ghosts...
Tell me your story
Let me unravel it, it’s a mess
Why aren’t you saying anything?
When I go to college
I won’t be able to come here often
(Jung-hyun)
Then will you come see me once?
Buy me pretty flowers?
I’m in Paju
Yeah, I’ll go
[CALM MUSIC]
(Eun-tak)
But
How did you die?
During the graduation ceremony
Car accident
Then I’ll wait
[GIVES A SLIGHT SMILE]
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
Ah, what the heck is going on?
[THE DOOR OPENS WITH A CLICK]
- (Eun-tak) Welcome -
(Grim Reaper) Excuse me...
[EUN-TAK'S SIGH]
(Eun-tak) How do you
keep knowing I'm here?
[THE DOOR CLOSES WITH A CLICK]
(Grim Reaper) I was more
surprised, why here of all places?
They said there are more
fried chicken places in
our country than the number of
McKeen Burger stores worldwide.
So why this place?
Because it's the
chicken shop the Goblin attached itself to (Grim
Reaper)
Anyway, you seem like someone who doesn't help in life.
What’s going on today?
(Euntak)
Are you really going to just drop by like this, making people's hearts race?
Why did you come to the chicken place?
You came to buy chicken, give me chicken
Don’t be ridiculous
Uncle, I know you’re a vegetarian.
Even if you know, give me chicken
(Reaper)
Look, a lot of radishes
Really?
[SOUNDS OF SURPRISE]
(Reaper)
Oh, oops
Was this meeting already promised?
[Euntak's flustered breaths]
Did I crash the scene of that promise?
By coincidence
[Euntak’s urgent breaths]
[Exciting music]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
(Reaper)
Ah, what are you doing?
You can’t just handle this carelessly!
You shouldn’t be so visible to people either,
you know?
(Euntak)
Please stay quietly in that corner
Then I’ll try to get you at least one more leg
[EUNTAK'S URGENT BREATHS]
(Euntak)
Oppa, come quickly
Have you been well?
Please take a seat comfortably.
Please sit down, so
what would you like to eat?
(Grim Reaper)
I've thought about it
How about chicken for dinner tonight?
[RESONANCE]
[MAJESTIC MUSIC]
For some reason, tonight
Don't you want to eat chicken?
There's no helping it
I guess we have to go with chicken for dinner
I'm sorry for being selfish
But chicken for dinner...
Shut up
Mr. Grim Reaper, please look at me for a moment
I'm eating first
Come back before the batter gets cold
(Kim Shin)
Oh, hey, I just want to go back to being a radish...
(Eun-tak) Mister, why do
you keep coming to our store?
It can't be me, and could it be
that you're interested in our boss?
It’s not like that, I’m just here to take a
look (Grim Reaper)
If you just don’t say
who I am,
I feel like we could all be at
peace, but don’t tell Tae-hee that
I saw
you come to the place where I work
part-time, and you smiled brightly when you
saw me, and you packed two more for the way
back—it’s a secret between us (Kim Shin)
A secret?
(Kim Shin) You came to visit while I was
working part-time? You came and smiled brightly?
(Grim Reaper)
No, but
You can say the bright smile is a secret,
but why is what you wrapped up a secret?
Honestly, tell me How many
coupons did you give him?
Hey, just hold on for a second
How many times did that guy come?
Let's say he came five times,
how many coupons should that be?
(Gong Shiin)
Just be quiet for a sec!
Hey, who do you think he is
because of that famous baseball...
I was his guardian deity back then
So all of that baseball was mine, okay?
You really don’t know anything, what?
Even if that’s the case Is it
really because of Uncle Soon?
(Euntak) It's all my first love Taehee
oppa's will, don't you know human will?
Look at me
Uncle grabs the
sword perfectly, in the end,
he makes it pretty, huh?
(Gong Shiin)
Ah, hey, hey, wow, wow!
[GONG SHIIN'S EXASPERATED BREATH]
Hey, what's the deal with
the scream and death system?
If you just tell me the basic principle
I can figure
something out, and I can sort out the chicken
coupon
I know a faster way
So why should I do it for you?
- (Grim Reaper) Euntak?
- (Gong Shiin) Hey
(Grim Reaper)
Ji Eun-tak
[KIM SHIN'S RIDICULOUS LAUGH]
(Kim Shin)
Ugh, these guys are really!
[Thunder rumbles]
[ROUGH BREATHING]
(Tae-hee's mom)
No
Who put this back without anyone knowing?
[Exciting music]
No, how could one person in the neighborhood not see
putting this big thing inside?
It's enough to drive a ghost crazy, drive a ghost crazy
(YoonA)
Hey, Ji Eun-tak
Are you okay for a sec? I have something I'm curious about
Did you do well on the CSAT?
I think so, why?
[LAUGHTER]
Looks like you did really well
That's so annoying, hey
You must've done well too
You study well
But you don't go to hagwon
That's cool, you
- Yayu?
- I mean it?
(YoonA)
Which early admission schools did you apply for?
I’m just worried we might overlap
Even if the universities are similar, we won’t overlap
I’m applying for the social consideration category
(YoonA)
Ah...
So you’re likely to get in?
What do you mean by that?
You said you see ghosts
(Yoona)
Don't the ghosts tell you that kind of stuff?
I'm curious about whether I will pass or not
So that was what you were really curious about?
(Eun-tak)
Still, it's good that you're healthy
No whispering from behind
I can't stand being curious about something
So I guess that's why you're good at studying
It's just what you see
They don't tell you anything
I'm off
We were in the same class for 3 years
(Yoona)
Having all the conversations we should have had in 3 years today
You have your interview for Suwon tomorrow, right?
Good luck with the interview!
You, you too
[SLIGHTLY SMILE]
[A BIRD CHIRPS]
[SOFT MUSIC]
[CLEARS THROAT]
You didn't care whether I went or not
Why did you come out?
- Did you leave something behind?
- What?
[Surprised]
Oh, my scarf
(Euntak)
The uncle keeps not accepting my greetings
and making me anxious...
Don't be scared
Don't tremble
Shall I go with you?
What am I, a kid?
Why isn't the bus coming?
Are you still sulking?
That's what I was trying to do.
I messed up because of the scarf.
You're definitely jealous.
So what if I am?
Does it make me happy that I'm jealous?
Oh, it actually feels good, all day long.
(Eun-tak)
Please go in.
Good luck with the interview.
Thank you for the scarf.
Oh, be careful of the person behind you.
(Eun-tak)
I'm sorry.
I was trying to avoid you.
Your eyes are really big and clear,
they reflect everything, really.
Oh, I got it, get in the car.
[Clatter]
[Woman 3's scream]
(Woman 3)
It's a thief! It's a pickpocket!
[TENSE SOUND EFFECTS]
[TENSE MUSIC]
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECTS]
[CAR HORN]
[TIRE SQUEALING]
[CAR HORNS ARE HONKING ONE AFTER ANOTHER]
[BUS HORN]
[TIRE SQUEALING]
[TENSE MUSIC]
[TRUCK HORN]
[A TRUCK CRASHES WITH A BANG]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC]
[BABY CRYING]
[STRAINED GROANS]
[A WOMAN’S STRAINED BREATHING]
[THE CLOCK TICKS]
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECTS]
[SIGNIFICANT MUSIC]
[THE CLOCK TICKS]
Goodbye
Why you?
[THE BUS DOORS CLOSE WITH A SNAP]
You're not in that scene
What did you say?
(Man 3)
Oh, if I mess up the interview again
I'll be killed by mom
I just hope I have an accident on the way
(Man 4)
Hey, don't say that
They say words become seeds
Ah, whether I die by mom's hands or in an accident
People die anyway
(Man 4)
Right
(Lion 2)
Oh my, oh my, I'm tired since the morning
(Lion 1)
Why don’t you at least have some coffee?
- (Grim Reaper) Uh
- (Lion 2) Oh my
(Lion 2)
Hey, I told you I was tired
Why are you only giving this to him?
I told you not to bring yours, didn't I?
(Lion 2)
Are you still sulking?
Who said that? That I'm sulking
Hmm, everyone says you’re still sulking
I see
Are there kids you haven't seen before?
The kids from Hannam-dong also came to support
(Lion 1)
It really seems like a big incident.
(Lion 2)
Well, I heard the support team also
received five each all at once
Isn’t that a bit much for you?
It's in my jurisdiction so
(Reaper)
Kim Hyun-jung, 34 years old
Park Soo-bin, 2 years old, accidental death
It seems to be a child and mother
Looks like I have to prepare for heaven again
(Lion 1)
What?
[RUSTLING THROUGH THE LIST]
[SIGH]
[TENSE MUSIC]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[THE DOOR CLOSES WITH A CLICK]
(Kim Sin)
Let’s close the shop for today
and head home early.
No, we haven't even started the business
and you're telling me to fold?
No, what do you mean by that?
From here to here
means I'm buying everything.
[LAUGHTER]
(Man 5)
Oh, young man
why are you in such a hurry?
No, do you even know what this is?
It's socks.
(Kim Shin)
What will you do?
Will you do that?
[THE CLOCK IS TICKING]
[MAN 5 RUSTLES THE BOX]
[TIRE FRICTION SOUND]
[MAN 6'S SURPRISED GROAN]
[MAN 6'S LABORED GROAN]
[THE GROANS OF MAN 6 IN PAIN]
(Man 6)
You crazy bastard, shit!
[HEAVY MUSIC]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
You were that bastard at the bus stop back then?
(Man 6)
What are you following me around for?
What do you think it is?
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[TENSION-BUILDING MUSIC]
[THE SURPRISED GROANS OF MAN 6]
[HEAVY MUSIC]
(Kim Shin)
The cash you stole is
just 23,000 won, 32,000 won
and three meal vouchers for 1,500 won.
Do you know how many people almost died today because of this?
What are you?
(Male 6)
Are you a police officer?
The owner of this wallet you just snatched
is going to receive a 3-week diagnosis for a fracture
and if he takes 3 weeks off, he will lose his job
so he’s not getting a cast and is going to work
For 3 weeks because of you
What the hell are you talking about?
Is this wallet yours?
(Kim Shin)
His salary will be spent on treatment again
and the fracture left untreated for 3 weeks
will cause shock, because of you
If you don’t want to die, shut up.
Who are you, bastard
(Kim Shin)
I don't like saving a person like you
but
it must be a side effect of interfering with human life and death
so just live
Don't think this punishment is over
Even in death
you will face this punishment again
An eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth
This is my way
It's going to hurt, just endure it
[THERE'S A CRACKLING SOUND]
[MAN 6'S SCREAM]
(Man 6)
Ah, my hand
[MAN 6'S GROAN]
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
[THE GROANS OF MAN 6]
[THE CLOCK TICKS]
(Reaper)
Get ready, work begins soon.
(Lion 2)
Oh, yes, yes.
Look, the target bus is coming in.
[THE BUS DOOR OPENS WITH A CREAK]
(Euntak)
Huh? It’s the grim reaper.
(Lion 1)
Did that girl just see our senior?
Can she see us right now?
(Lion 2)
Before they die, there are some kids like that, right?
It’s sad, the poor thing is still young.
[Tense music]
Why is she over there...
(Grim Reaper) Who has the
list of those who have died?
(Reaper 1) Who are
you talking about?
(Reaper 2) Oh, right It
seems like there's one more
person on the list; wasn't this
supposed to be all deceased?
Wait a minute, if one is left
What, what happens now?
I hope there won’t be an accident
[TODAY; THE BUS DOORS ARE CLOSING]
This is a bust
(Reaper 1) Yes? Why?
[TENSION-INDUCING SOUND EFFECT]
(Reaper 1) Oh, that
bus shouldn't just leave;
it can't go safely An
accident has to happen
now; the accident time
has been announced now.
(Lion 3)
What should we do?
Isn't it something we have to pay for, the accident?
(Lion 1)
The bus just left, and no one died
(Lion 2)
No, in over 300 years of being a grim reaper,
this is the first time I've encountered something like this
W-what do we really do about this?
(Lion 1)
I've never seen a case of missing paperwork like this before
This really must be a miracle
Miracles really do happen
- (Lion 1) Wow
- (Lion 2) 'Wow'
(Lion 2)
[Kicking Lion 1's knee]
Oh my!
[Lion 1's groan of pain]
Do you think this is a miracle just because of a few sheets of paper?
You better watch your mouth
I'm sorry, it's just so amazing
(Lion 1)
But how did you know, senior?
[LION 1'S SURPRISED GROAN]
(Lion 2)
Oh, you scared me
(Lion 1)
D-don't act like a goblin
Why, don’t I look like one?
Hold on, let me see you
(Kim Sin)
Why didn’t you say anything?
(Grim Reaper)
Why do you keep interfering in human life and death?
I almost died today.
If that is the child's predetermined fate,
there's nothing I can do.
Who says so?
The only thing I can't do is die.
Because of that child,
should I interfere with the life and death of all humans in this world?
Hey, you, coming to someone else's workplace...
(Kim Shin)
But
no matter how I think about today's accident, it's strange.
A few days ago, I already saw that accident.
But Eun-tak was not in that scene.
Before that
I saw the child's appearance 10 years later
But this was definitely a fatal accident
The scene of the accident you saw
is not the fate of the other missing persons
(Grim Reaper)
You just became a variable in that accident
Because you will save them
[Kim Shin's realization moan]
Thanks to the missing person whose boyfriend is a goblin
[Grinding teeth]
Those who were destined to die all survived
They caused the unfortunate Grim Reaper to get caught up in overtime
Do you want to eat chicken? For a late-night snack
Are you really just going back to nothing?
Have you thought about it carefully?
(Grim Reaper)
I was joking
If you look so serious, what am I supposed to do?
I wonder what it means to go back to nothing
(Kim Shin)
Will it be scattered like dust, wind, or rain?
Somewhere in the world
Why are you having such concerns?
Anyway, the other missing person can't even hold a sword
Euntak held the sword
[Soft music]
(Kim Shin)
The sword even started to move
So I...
I almost killed that kid.
It hurts a lot
[sighs]
It was a pain I've never felt before
Isn't it time to tell the truth even now?
What happens when I draw the sword
No
If possible, I’d like to hide it more
For about 80 years more
[SIGH]
Why?
Right at the human lifespan
A 19-year-old girl currently
can live at maximum
I want to do that
Will it really happen?
Won't it?
[sound of an approaching car engine]
[smiles slightly]
[SOUND OF TIRE FRICTION]
[LAUGHTER]
[THE CAR DOOR SLAMS OPEN]
[THE CAR DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
[I FASTEN MY SEATBELT WITH A CLICK]
Did you come to pick me up?
Tsk, you startled me
The lunch I had
just hasn’t settled, that’s why I stepped out
You know, right?
(Euntak)
You didn’t come to pick me up just to make me comfortable, did you?
[Crinkling the plastic]
Huh?
What is all this?
What’s with the socks?
Today I protected
someone’s twenty and thirty years
[I CHUCKLE]
Ah~
My twenties and thirties, I want to protect them.
Did you decide to sell socks starting today?
Why do you ask if I'm going to complain?
[LAUGH]
Do you want to do it together?
Sure
(Euntak)
And now that my interviews are all over,
I have some free time,
I’ll take care of the uncle.
What do you mean by take care?
[EUNTAK'S ROUGH BREATHING]
What are you doing?
I’m building up strength in my arms.
This time, I’ll definitely try to
not hurt you at all in one go.
(Euntak)
I realized last time that...
It seems that arm strength is important.
(Kim Shin)
Take it easy.
What is this exhausting cheer?
Can you move over a bit?
I have something to talk about for a moment.
(Eun Tak)
With whom?
Just for a moment, go in.
[CLINKING THE DUMBBELLS]
Come here, huh?
Just come down for a moment.
[Playful music]
Ah, I’ve already been punished this much, right?
(Kim Shin)
No, I’m just going to receive a little award.
Is that so unbearable?
The future, did you show it to me on purpose?
To make sure I can't do anything
Do you think I'd make that choice?
I won't, I won't do it even if I die, huh?
No, come down here, huh?
I'm telling you to come down, let's talk face to face
you bastard!
(Kim Shin)
Do you think I'm scared? Come down, down...
Ah, seriously, this guy
Is he still in pain?
I haven't seen it
It's real
I really don't like it
I, who like you
I can't believe I can be this foolish
(Euntak)
Right now
What have you done to me?
If you didn't hear it, then forget it
I heard everything
Then that's good
[THE DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES SOFTLY]
[SOFT MUSIC]
No, what I'm saying is
A moment ago, you said something to me...
Ah, this person is really
[EUNTAK'S LAUGHTER]
[WIPES HIS NOSE]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
[SETS THE GLASS DOWN WITH A THUD]
Tsk
(Sunny)
Forty-eight
Forty-nine
Fifty
[SOFT MUSIC]
[SUNNY'S SURPRISED BREATH]
[A FLUSTERED BREATH]
[A HURRIED BREATH]
(Sunny)
You haven't called at all, so
I didn't even take it out, right?
Scaring people!
[SUNNY'S ROUGH BREATH]
(Sunny)
I was surprised to get a call first
And ten missed calls at that
(Reaper)
I was working late and something came to mind
(Sunny)
It must be really important?
(Reaper)
Yes
Religion, non-religious
(Sunny)
Why are you so good at talking?
Do you have any religion?
So what else should there be?
Then let me know again when you’re ready...
Did you call ten times just to say that?
I thought I should let you know quickly
Ha, cute
Am I
cute?
Did you not know?
Did no other girls
say anything?
[A FLUSTERED BREATH]
(Grim Reaper)
There were no other girls...
(Sunny)
That’s a good thing, that
there are no other girls
Don’t prepare, no other girls
It's perfect right now, got it?
Ha, isn't that a male athlete?
(Sunny)
Honestly, really honestly
try answering just one thing
I'll tell you too
What do you mean?
My real name is a single character
Kim Sun
My parents
(Sunny)
said they named me with money from their meager living so I could do well
A fortune teller
said it had to be that name
But I like Sunny much more
I feel like I'm sparkling
[meaningful music]
I really hated that name.
(Sunny)
It seems like a pathetic
and story-laden name.
Kim Sun
"Kim Sun"
(Chairman Yoo)
Nari comes by there
around this time every year
and pays her respects.
Mr. Kim Woo-bin
What is your real name?
I know it's not your real name.
(Sunny)
Even if it's really old-fashioned
or doesn't suit you at all, I won't tease you.
Would you mind telling me now?
[Tense music]
[Sigh]
With anger and concern, I draw my sword.
I will go as far away as I can.
Do not come back as long as you can
Your Majesty, that word
Your Majesty, how could you...
It is Your Majesty's consideration
I was commanded to defend the borders
and I defended the borders
I was commanded to defeat the enemy and I defeated the enemy
My sister is here and
the people are here...
The emperor's worries
Now you are doing it
(Young king)
Announce that he died valiantly
It will be a poignant announcement
It is a royal command
[A SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
[THE PAINED GROAN OF THE GRIM REAPER]
[ tense music ]
(Sunny)
What's wrong? Are you in pain?
[THE GRIM REAPER'S PAINFUL GROAN]
[A PAINFUL GROAN]
"Wangyeong"
(Sunny)
Chest? Near the solar plexus?
What did you have for dinner?
Is your hand cold? Let me hold your hand
If I massage your hand, blood circulation will improve...
[In a strained voice]
I'm sorry but
Could you look into my eyes for a moment?
Yes?
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
Today, we did not meet
(The Grim Reaper)
I'm sorry I couldn't see you off.
I turn around and go home.
[THE GRIM REAPER'S PAINFUL GROAN]
[STRAINED BREATHS]
Where have you gone?
(Chairman Yoo)
From now on
You must serve me
You should remember this day well
Why are you doing this?
Who are they?
(Chairman Yoo)
They have long been
Those who were indebted to your heart
(Deokhwa)
Ah
But grandfather
I heard there's a sword stuck in uncle's chest, is that true?
How would I know that?
(Chairman Yoo)
In front of you
You must never
show any signs of it.
Why?
[HEAVY MUSIC]
"Kim Sun, Wang Ye"
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECTS]
(Chairman Yoo)
That black
Is both the image and the cause of the lily
The reason for the lily's existence
And the clue to its disappearance
(Kim Shin)
My life
My sign, you
I like you
So, I hold onto secrets
I try to ask for permission from the heavens
For even one more day without knowing
So, for just a hundred years without knowing
[TENSE SOUND EFFECTS]
[TENSE MUSIC]
[FOOTSTEPS CAN BE HEARD]
(Three Gods)
I know?
I have something to tell you
Is it alright if I take your time?
Would you like to get to the point?
Right now, I don't really want to face any gods
[HEAVY MUSIC]
(Grim Reaper)
Something went wrong
Maybe
It seems like it's you first
Where have you been, anyway?
I was worried this would happen
Even if you don't say you'll come, you should at least say you'll leave
Tsk
(Grim Reaper)
What are you curious about?
[CLEARS THROAT]
(Euntak)
Ah, yes, that...
(Kim Shin)
I think I've mentioned it once
When the bride appears,
you have to prepare to leave even further away.
It feels a bit strange.
(Euntak)
You know the sword in the goblin's chest, right?
[THE REAPER'S SIGH]
Specifically,
What happens when you draw the sword?
You kept saying you were going somewhere.
(Euntak)
So then, are you not leaving now, sir?
(Kim Shin)
For now,
I don't know if I should prepare to leave even further away.
Where is that?
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
Quickly draw that sword
(Samsin)
Draw the sword and return to nothingness
You suddenly appeared
and said I should die
You should at least give a reason...
(Samsin)
You’ve lived long enough
But that child hasn't
I was really happy when I blessed that child
So just make a decision now
[A HOLLOW LAUGH]
It's ironic
(Kim Shin)
I don’t even know what kind of decision
you want me to make.
When I was born as Kim Shin for the first time
You must have marked me
Am I not your child?
So I'm telling you
My child, whom I hoped would be happy
For Kim Shin
Because it must be what you want the most
What do I want?
(Samshin)
Don't you want that child to live?
If you don't return to nothing
Euntak will die
[A TENSE SOUND EFFECT]
(Euntak)
So
I want to die
You told me to become a bride
Are you saying that I should take out the sword?
[HEAVY MUSIC]
[TREMBLING BREATH]
So
if I take out that sword
the uncle dies?
So
if I take out that sword
the uncle disappears?
Completely from this world?
[SOBBING]
[STRAINED BREATH]
(Samshin)
He was destined to pull your sword
No, you made him be born with that fate
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
If you can't fulfill your role as a tool,
your value of existence will disappear
Because there’s no reason to exist
(Samshin)
So if you don’t draw the sword
death will keep approaching that child
It must have happened several times already?
[The moneylender screams]
[Eun-tak's scream]
(Moneylender)
Huh? You're really going to die
[AN OMINOUS SOUND EFFECT]
Goodbye
[TRUCK HORN]
(Samshin)
That's right, those accidents
There will be more from now on.
More often and more intensely than
the accidents that have happened so far.
You almost killed me once.
With your own hands
Move.
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[EUNGTAK'S STRAINED MOAN]
[TENSE SOUND EFFECTS]
[QUIVERING BREATH]
(Kim Shin)
After living for a hundred years, one day
On a day that felt just right
It was my first love
Wishing to confess
I ask the heavens for permission
Trying to find it
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
Subtitle: Choi Hyeran