[THEME SONG]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
(Un-tak) Uncle!
(Kim Shin) 'The magnitude of
mass does not correspond to volume'
[LAUGHTER]
[SOFT MUSIC]
'That girl, so small like a violet'
'That girl, fluttering like a petal'
'With a mass greater than the Earth
pulling me in'
'In an instant'
'I tumbled toward her'
'Like Newton's apple'
'With a thud'
[heartbeat sound effect]
'Thud thud'
[BLOOD DRIPS]
[EUNTAK'S RAPID BREATHING]
Red carpet, it was amazing, right?
It's totally fantastic
Mister
(Kim Shin)
'The heart continued a dizzying pendulum movement from the sky to the ground'
Sir, are you angry?
(Kim Shin)
'It was first love'
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
(Eun Tak)
Um...
I’ll walk
You can just stop in front of me
I’ve memorized all the roads near that hotel
- (Eun Tak) If I walk, I’ll be there soon...
- Okay, then
[TIRE FRICTION SOUND]
[GEAR SHIFT SOUND]
[UNBUCKLES THE SEATBELT]
Ah, goodbye
[HEARTBEAT SOUND EFFECT]
[HEAVY MUSIC]
[THE SUBORDINATE STABS DEEP WITH A KNIFE]
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECTS]
[KIM SHIN'S PAINFUL MOAN]
(Shin)
Only the Goblin bride
[Kim Shin's labored breathing]
will pull that sword
When the sword is drawn, it will return to nothing
and peace shall follow
[LABORED BREATHING]
[CALM MUSIC]
(Radio DJ)
In life, sometimes
strange genres creep in
What was your genre today?
Heart-thumping rom-com?
A strange and beautiful fantasy
A sad melodrama?
[THE RADIO BROADCAST CRACKLES]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[Mysterious sound effects]
[Euntak's surprised moan]
Please don't do this,
just talk to me normally.
If you do this, I'm also scared,
sorry for startling you, but I
have a favor to ask (ghost).
I'm really sorry, but could
you go to the boarding house where I used to live?
Could you fill up the
refrigerator a bit for me?
The refrigerator? Uh, since I just died not long ago, my mom hasn't
been able to come to my room yet because she's been busy with the funeral.
(Spirit)
If my mom finds out the fridge in my room is empty,
she'll be heartbroken
I'm begging you
But
I have no money
I didn't think that far, I'm sorry
[EUNTAK'S SIGH]
Ah, there's a way
[A SIGH]
(Spirit)
Thank you
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC]
[GENTLY SMILES]
[PRESSES THE SWITCH DOWN]
[TREMBLING BREATH]
[A SIGH]
[SOBBING]
[THE SCENERY RESONATES]
The car is cooling down
(Grim Reaper)
You've worked hard in this life
Be careful, and go to the next life
[SNIFFLES]
[SUNNY'S SURPRISED BREATH]
What is this? Is this a coincidence?
(Sunny)
It's not me
Why didn't you call? I was waiting
You said you'd do it
I will, I'm going, right now
[SUNNY'S UNBELIEVABLE BREATH]
(Sunny)
Where are you going?
What, are you going to look for a public phone or something?
There's a phone at home, at home
I’ll call home soon...
Ah, it's hilarious
Ha, what a coincidence that we met like this?
(Grim Reaper)
Ah
It’s nice to see you
[SUNNY’S ABSURD BREATHING]
I’m going crazy
How about coffee instead of a quick call?
(Sunny)
There are cafes everywhere in Seoul
and I have plenty of time
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC FLOWS OUT]
Excuse me
(Sunny)
Are we just going to keep drinking coffee like this?
It’s already sunset?
(Grim Reaper)
Oh, the day is really short, isn’t it?
It wasn’t short
You’ve been like this for an hour.
(Sunny)
Aren't we going to say hello?
Aren't we going to ask about how we are? Aren't we going to talk?
Ah
(Grim Reaper)
Hello
Have you been doing well all this time?
[ABSURD SIGH]
Yes, have you been doing well too?
Is my ring doing well?
Do you still not have a cellphone?
Yes, I have been doing well
The ring is well, I don't have a cellphone
[SIGH]
Honestly, tell me
You forgot my name, right?
It's Sunhee
No, it's Sunny...
[A HOLLOW LAUGH]
[ABSURD LAUGHTER]
He's really a funny guy.
[LAUGHTER]
(Sunny)
Is this a concept?
What are you looking at?
I can't help but look, because it's funny.
(Sunny)
But thinking about it,
I don't even know your name.
What’s your name?
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[KIM SHIN AND THE REAPER'S SIGH]
[THE REAPER'S SIGH]
[THE REAPER EXHALES]
He asked for my name.
But I don't know my name.
He asked how I was doing.
How can you ask about someone who is not alive?
[Kim Shin's Sigh]
[The Grim Reaper exhales]
[GENTLE MUSIC]
(Kim Shin)
In that child's laughter
In the sunniest sunshine of the day
In the moment when life shattered
[A SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
I made a resolution
I must disappear
Before I want to live more
Before I become happier
For you
The choice I must make
To end this life
(The Grim Reaper)
But
I can hear your voice
Are you really going to die?
(Kim Shin)
Yeah
Before the first snow falls
[A SIGH]
[BREATHING OUT TOGETHER]
"The fare"
[A DEEP SIGH]
[DEOKHWA'S IRRITATED MOAN]
[A SIGH]
(Deokhwa)
Are you drinking by any chance?
No
But you seemed to have drunk?
(Deokhwa)
The fridge was completely empty?
You ate everything without leaving a single piece, including chocolate, peanuts, and jerky?
Well, yeah, you can eat that
But why did you clean up all the bottles?
Did you think I wouldn’t find out if you cleaned up the bottles?
(Eun-tak)
I have a bit of a situation
At that time, the chairman said if there’s anything you need
to just say it
I’m sorry, but could you lend me some?
I don’t have any money
(Deok-hwa)
I don’t have money either, you little girl!
I don’t have money...
[sniffling]
I said I don’t have money
[THE DOORBELL RINGS]
(Eun-tak)
I was in the middle of calculating...
Ah, you scared me
Come in
Uncle, why are you here?
Did Deok-hwa oppa tell everything?
What?
(Eun-tak)
Ah, that...
Actually, I got scolded, you know, by Deok-hwa oppa
(Kim-shin)
He’s not the kind of kid who can scold someone
I completely emptied the refrigerator
Can we figure out how to settle this...
(Eun-tak)
I’ll pay you back little by little when I get my part-time job salary
Is that not possible?
(Eun-tak)
Actually, the alcohol was consumed by you, sir
I spent the rest on something nice
If you pretend you don’t know
I'm going to set this all ablaze and put it out.
You might find yourself going
back and forth all day today.
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
Don't summon me anymore
There's no need for that
I'll always be by your side
Let's go home
What kind of home?
The home I live in
Because you're a goblin bride
Sir
Do you love me?
If that's necessary, I'll do that too
I love you
[CALMING MUSIC]
[THE RAIN IS POURING DOWN]
Do you really hate me that much?
(Eun-tak)
What could possibly be so hateful
that it makes you this sad?
The rain is pouring down, so what
Well, it's fine.
Even if I dislike you or feel sad
I'm going to live at your house
It's not my place to be choosy between the cold and hot goblins right now
Anyway, all I need to do is draw the sword, right?
Uh, then that's fine
Please wait a moment, I'll pack my things and come out
[THE RAIN IS POURING DOWN]
(Euntak)
What is your name, uncle?
Well, it's not that I was too curious to ask
Even though we
are in an ambiguous relationship that's closer than cohabitation but farther than marriage
I am, after all, a goblin bride.
I think I should at least know the 이름
of the goblin that will be my husband.
We
Still not us
(Kim Shin)
It seems like it started
before you were born
We
(Kim Shin)
Once it was Yoo Jong-shin
Then at another time it was Yoo Jae-shin
Currently it's Yoo Shin-jae
The real name is
Kim Shin
Departure, green light
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
(Grim Reaper)
Today is the day to put out the trash
You're always refreshing to see
(Eun-tak)
Give it to me, I'll handle this now
What's wrong with him?
Why is he suddenly trying to get on my good side?
From today, we will be staying here together.
[KIM SHIN RUSTLES THROUGH HIS LUGGAGE]
[THE CAR DOOR SHUTS WITH A THUD]
(Kim Shin)
The choice I have to make for you
is to end this life.
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
(Grim Reaper)
I support you, your future
and what you will do from now on, let's go in
(Eun Tak)
Ah, yes, I look forward to working with you
So, is it true that the things I will be doing
will involve a lot of housework?
(Kim Shin)
It must be your place, right?
[PLAYFUL MUSIC]
(Grim Reaper)
It must be pressing the star at the end
You don't know the password?
Both of you?
(Kim Shin)
I've never entered by pressing a number
It really feels like that
Right before entering the
haunted house in the amusement park
(Eun Tak)
Scared and excited
Not knowing what's inside
When I go in
I wonder if I can come out safely again
Come in
[ABSURD BREATHING SOUNDS]
(Deok Hwa)
Huh?
Why are you here...
Why is this guy here When
and how did he get here?
(Grim Reaper)
He said we'll be
together starting today
(Euntak)
Please take good care of
me (Kim Shin)
Tell me the front
door password 1004 (Deokhwa)
But why is he living here?
Ah, why, I, I!
You should do a shot, or
[DRINK TO SOBERNESS, CHUCKLE]
(Euntak)
Wow (Kim Shin)
At this
point
It would be good to have a
baroque-style chair (Grim Reaper)
Is it a photo studio?
I like a pastel-toned daybed that calms the
mind and body (Kim Shin) Is this a kindergarten?
Here, a 19th-century Romantic painting is hung
Here would be nice for a fireplace
(Grim Reaper)
Is it a pension?
Over there, we apply Scandinavian-style
wallpaper...
(Kim Shin)
Is this a model house? It's my guest
- (Grim Reaper) It's my house
- (Eun Tak) It's my room!
[LIVELY MUSIC]
(Eun Tak)
I'm okay with everything
On this side, we apply 19th-century Romantic wallpaper
On this side, we place a pastel-toned fireplace, right, harmonious
Then, for today
Can I sleep on the living room sofa?
If it's uncomfortable for me to be in the living room
The outdoor flower bed is also okay
Right now, I’m not in a position to be picky about where I can lie down
(Grim Reaper)
So if you want to bring someone in
first buy a bed...
Sleep in my room today
With you, Uncle?
(Grim Reaper)
Sigh
No!
Then what about you?
[A FORCED LAUGH]
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
(Grim Reaper)
What does this mean?
Since I'm going to sleep in bed
Don't worry about me.
(Kim Shin)
Let me sleep comfortably on the sofa
(The Grim Reaper)
Wow, this goblin speaks so strangely
Absolutely not, it’s my bed, don’t pollute it
I know, even if you say not to worry
[Sighing]
There’s the living room sofa
I can’t sleep on the sofa
The kid will be running around
Then just go sleep at a hotel
(Kim Shin)
I can’t sleep at a hotel
The kid will be alone in that room
Where are you going?
I’m going to put the other missing person in the flower bed
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
Were you always this emotionless?
- (Grim Reaper) Yeah
- (Kim Shin) Then I'll use the sofa
Don't talk to me
You need to help me a lot
[SIGH]
(Eun Tak)
Oh my, this is comfortable
I wonder if I sat like this?
[STRAINING GROAN]
Huh?
My book
Didn't I say I was reading it, not just keeping it?
[SLAMS THE BOOK DOWN]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
You didn't throw it away
Tch, it's precious to keep
What kind of book is this?
I don't know Chinese characters.
[THE CANDLE FLICKERS]
[HEAVY MUSIC]
(Kim Shin)
War does not cease even in foreign lands
With swords and bows, they take land and grain
They take life
The gods of foreign lands and the gods of Goryeo
are all in cahoots
They left Goryeo together
I buried the grandson of the grandson of the grandson
I have spent several days
in the chair placed in the corner of a small room
My will
is not a message left before death
Oh God
[Thunder crashes]
My will
This is a petition asking you for death.
I have thought of this life as a reward,
but in the end, my life was a punishment.
No one’s death
has been forgotten.
Thus, I
want to end this life.
First,
God is still not listening,
have you ever seen God?
(Kim Shin)
Are you perhaps seeing God right now?
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
I told you not to talk to me,
(Grim Reaper)
How can someone like me see God?
(Kim Shin)
I've seen it before
What does it look like?
(Kim Shin)
It's just
[THE WIND BLOWING SOFTLY]
It was a butterfly
[SIGH]
It's always like that
Even a passing butterfly
can't be treated carelessly
If I could at least see its face
I could at least express my resentment specifically
[SIGH]
I know
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
If God only gives us
the trials that we can truly endure
I wonder if I've been overestimated
(Grim Reaper)
Is it hard?
(Kim Shin)
Don't worry
I won't cry while being held
[I CHUCKLE]
[A SIGH]
Humans see gods so easily
How come we have never seen them once
[THE CELL PHONE ALARM RINGS]
[I SMILE SOFTLY]
Ah, this is Goblin's place
[A REFRESHING GROAN]
What will the mornings be like?
Will there be some cold dishes?
There should be everything
But it feels a bit lonely
(Eun Tak)
Oh my
[EUN TAK'S JOYFUL BREATH]
How beautiful
(Eun-tak)
I wondered what it would be like for the guys to do housework
It's been a really long time since I've eaten a meal made by someone else
(Kim-shin)
I didn’t say I would make it
[THE MEAT IS SIZZLING ON THE GRILL]
It was delicious!
(Eun-tak)
I'll earn my own allowance and spend it
Starting tomorrow, I'll take care of my own meals
I'll also do the laundry myself
(Kim-shin)
We were originally supposed to do that
In this kind of rich house,
there are always people to help out and stuff...
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[SHARP SOUND EFFECTS]
[Kim Shin's Surprised Groan]
(The Grim Reaper)
What, did you practice without me knowing?
(Kim Shin)
Hey, you look to be in good condition today.
[KIM SHIN AND THE GRIM REAPER'S SPIRIT]
(Euntak)
Since you two are like this,
you can't handle people.
[GROAN OF EXERTION]
[KIM SHIN'S GROAN]
(Euntak)
Well, in a similar vein,
I wrote something down,
I hope you'll listen.
[Euntak rustles the paper]
[Euntak coughs lightly]
Appeal Letter
I hope it doesn't rain often.
Since it's inconvenient for the citizens
While I live in this house
Please, be happy
(Eun-tak)
If you have any complaints, please tell me
I hope there won’t be any attempts to take me away
Or any plans to take me away
If there's any urgent matter, please contact me
Please don't suddenly appear in front of me
Ji Eun-tak, 010-1234-1234
Just for reference, I'm unavailable during class
And I don’t want to be disturbed during my part-time job
Please turn it off in the library
That’s all
I’m off to school
[MAJESTIC MUSIC]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
(Kim Shin)
Is it telling me to make a call?
Does it know we don’t have phones
and is ignoring us?
Really?
(Deokhwa)
Okay
(Grim Reaper)
I like this, the chic black
Do you like this, the vibrant blue?
This person is excited
because it’s their first time seeing something like this
Explain it
(Deokhwa)
Okay, okay, just remember the numbers little by little
This is what they call a smartphone
I'm fine, so just explain it
to someone who has seen this for the first time
(Grim Reaper)
What you said is right, it only needs to be done for me
Uncle, can you really write it?
(Deokhwa)
This kid is really smart, huh?
Do you think I didn't write it because I didn't know?
- (Kim Shin) I didn't write it because I didn't need anything...
- (Grim Reaper) Well, since I watched the drama
(Grim Reaper)
I saw them talking while looking at each other's faces
Hey, if you were that urgent
you should have done it 300 years ago
[Grim Reaper's dissatisfied groan]
Ah, uncles, really
I'll let you know later
Now, for the time being
I'll go to the Play Store
Right now?
(Deokhwa)
Yes?
Why are you getting up?
You said let's go to the Play Store?
(Grim Reaper)
Oh
[DEOKHWA'S SIGH]
(Kim Shin)
Are you far away?
What are you doing? Get dressed and come
(Grim Reaper)
Oh, okay
[MOBILE PHONE VIBRATION SOUND]
[PLAYFUL MUSIC]
Hey, you said let's talk face to face?
(Grim Reaper)
So
I can't see your face?
Did you put it to your ear? Take it off.
What should I take off?
Your arm, move your arm away a bit!
(Kim Shin)
Like this?
Arm?
Oh
(The Grim Reaper)
Like this?
I can't see.
(Kim Shin)
Ah, tsk
What do I do with you?
(Eun Tak)
Sigh, if it's nothing
General?
Oh, national affairs
Hmm, stable
Sigh, but why is there so little data?
[Mouse click sound]
Is there no achievement?
[EUN TAK MUTTERS]
[MOBILE PHONE VIBRATION SOUND]
What is it? It's an unknown number.
Hello.
(Euntak)
Oh, you can use a smartphone too?
5.5 inch QHD display
Exynos 8890
With an octa-core processor and 4 gigabytes of RAM
Made of reinforced glass
boasting a lighter and slimmer body...
(Euntak)
What did you memorize?
(Kim Shin)
What do you need?
There's plenty of combs, toothbrushes, and towels at home
Uncle, you don't know what this is, right?
(Euntak)
Actually, he's my uncle.
Hey, your cheeks are rosy and pink.
What do you mean, mister?
Forget it.
(Euntak)
Actually, this guy is a goblin, but
because people are scared of him,
he covers himself with his favorite
buckwheat pudding
trying to pretend he's not a goblin.
Isn't that cute?
You know what I mean, right?
(Euntak)
Mister, this is something people use when they study at night.
Mister, this is...
(Kim Shin)
Don't you need anything else?
(Euntak)
Oh, I still have a lot now.
Thinking about bringing it out later
It's all a burden,
what does that mean?
(Euntak)
You don't know about the relationship between men and
women
I could go out (Kim Shin)
Wait, saying that you’ll bring it out
later
What are you talking about, who says they’ll give it when they go out?
[BARCODE SCANNING SOUND]
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
[SIGH]
(Sunny) But thinking about it I don’t
even know your name, what is it?
[SUNNY'S BEWILDERED GASP]
No, did I ask about the annual salary?
I asked about the extent of the assets Did
I ask about the existence of an inheritance?
(Sunny) I just
asked for your name.
Getting up suddenly
Is there any place to go?
I'm a bit sensitive about my name
I'm sorry, Sunhee
It's not Sunhee, it's Sunny!
[SUNNY'S SIGH]
Are we breaking up already?
Just for a moment, I said coffee, and I drank it all
Ha, unbelievable
Um, but you know
Earlier, you said you would refill the coffee
You didn't return the receipt you borrowed
Why did I refill the coffee?
Do you really like coffee?
The receipt is essential
Our company is very thorough
[AN ABSURD SIGH]
[SOFT MUSIC]
[A SIGH]
That's enough, this is enough
[A CONTEMPLATING BREATH]
Damn it
[SOUND OF MANIPULATING A MOBILE PHONE]
[AN ANNOYED GROAN]
[A PROUD GROAN]
Ah, that's enough
[A SIGH]
[PUTS THE MOBILE PHONE DOWN FORCEFULLY]
(Kim Shin)
Go to your room, I've done enough to live on
[EUNTAK'S EXCITED BREATH]
(Euntak)
Really? Ah, ah, it's heavy.
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
[THE BELL RINGS SOFTLY]
[EUNTAK'S SURPRISED MOAN]
[JOYFUL BREATHING]
[THE BELL RINGS SOFTLY]
Do you like it?
You were going to come up
Did you send all of this to me?
My hand needs to rest a bit
(Kimshin) This, this hand has
spent a lot of money, did this
hand, ah, did this hand spend it?
[SLIGHTLY SMILING]
Is this place heaven?
[I REALLY LIKE EUNTAK'S SMILE]
(Euntak) Did you do it
yourself? With those tiny hands?
I asked to do all of this
with heartfelt sincerity.
(Eun-tak)
Yeah, yeah
Then take a break
(Kim-shin)
Oh, don't nail it to the wall
The room below is mine
So walk on your tiptoes
Yes, please rest
[THERE'S A CLATTERING SOUND FROM ABOVE]
They're moving a flowerpot
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
It should be kept facing south
[THERE'S A CLATTERING SOUND FROM ABOVE]
They place it well
[PLEASANT BREATHING SOUNDS]
[THERE'S A THUMPING SOUND FROM ABOVE]
Seems like they like the bed
[THE PAPER CHIMES SOFTLY]
They're coming out of the room
I can't concentrate at all
(Eun-tak)
Th-that, is it your name?
Why do you ask about my name?
(Eun-tak)
Could it be that?
The grim reaper
is said to call a name three times before death
I'm married now
I'm a different person from before
I have a family
Since I'll be taking my husband’s last name
I'm not Eun-tak anymore
Well...
I'm not Eun-tak
(Grim Reaper)
Not your name
A name that women like for men
Huh?
I have no name, I
(Grim Reaper)
So, I was trying to hold back
What is that name called
(Euntak)
Don't you have a name, uncle?
The goblin uncle has one
What is it?
Kim Shin, it's really pretty, right?
(Grim Reaper)
Tch
What a drag
So, do you have a name in mind?
(Grim Reaper)
Hyuk
[SOFT MUSIC]
Jun
Min?
[EUNTAK'S SIGH]
If it's a name that women like
There are three representative ones
Hyun Bin, Won Bin, Kim Woo Bin
[Clapping hands]
Ah, Bin
[THE SOUND OF CONTEMPLATING BREATHS]
(Duk-hwa)
Could it be the real Hyun-bin, Won-bin, Kim Woo-bin
It can't be something like that, right?
The person's name is also Yu Duk-hwa
That has a very deep,
frustrating story behind it
Ah, why did Uncle have to get into Yu Duk-hwa in '92
Because of that, I still haven't seen 'Infernal Affairs'
It's a boycott
Even if I become the chairman of Cheonwoo Group
I’d still get overshadowed by that gentleman born in '61, right?
Well, I get overshadowed by you too.
What does that mean?
It means that something very important of mine
depends on your hands.
- What’s the important thing?
- (Deokhwa) My card.
That’s more important to me than my life.
(Euntak)
Wow.
(Deokhwa)
What do you mean by 'wow'?
I thought I was born with
nothing at all.
But it turns out I have a lot of
things in my hands.
It's fascinating to me.
Here, here.
(Euntak)
Please stop in front of the chicken place over there.
Is that the chicken place
where you’re working part-time?
Yes, why?
[DEOKHWA'S CLEAR THROAT]
(Deokhwa) Sigh,
while you're eating,
let me tell you
about that chicken
place issue I mentioned before.
Ha, let’s just say
there’s no unexpected
ambush, please cancel it.
[YOU’RE WORRYING TOO MUCH. I DIDN’T
EVEN WORK. DEOKHWA’S AWKWARD SMILE]
I guess this is what they
call a blessing in disguise?
(Deokhwa) So, I’m
asking, is there anything
your grandfather absolutely
wants me to convey?
There is.
(Secretary Kim)
Jieun Tak, the college entrance exam is just around the corner,
so please be especially careful with your conduct.
What?
Is it not a card to deliver?
First, do not speak to Jieun Tak.
(Secretary Kim)
Remember, silence is golden.
Third, be reticent.
Fourth, keep your mouth shut.
I sincerely hope that you will
successfully carry out these difficult tasks.
There was a message.
- Is it not a card?
- It is not.
[THE CHOPSTICKS SNAP LOUDLY]
[A SIGH]
[LIVELY MUSIC]
[THERE IS A KNOCK SOUND]
[THE PAPER CHIMES SOFTLY]
(Kim Shin)
When you're bored studying, could you...
[The door opens with a click]
[The paper chimes softly]
(Kim Shin)
I know you're busy studying,
but could you spare some time for me...
[THE PAPER CHIMES SOFTLY]
(Kim Shin)
I know it's tough with your studies,
but for just a moment, could you...
(The Grim Reaper)
I understand you're lonely from studying,
but when you have a moment, a word from the author...
My encouragement is a secret.
(Euntak)
Ah, you startled me!
Oh my gosh
(Kim Shin)
What's your dream?
What do you want to be?
While eating so much like this
without any kendo practice and just studying
What is your dream?
A radio producer
I applied for all the schools in that field?
[Kim Shin's frustrated groan]
[He puts the glass down with a thud]
(Kim Shin)
That's not what I'm talking about
With that reading comprehension, are you going to get into college?
Ah, why say such a curse
[SIGH]
I was just thinking
I've thought about it deeply...
(Eun-tak) Uncle, I'm going to
put being pretty on hold for a while.
On hold? You really
thought about it, right?
What if I lose my utility
and you kick me out?
(Eun-tak) Just thinking
about that stresses
me out, and I can't
study, and even though I
can't study, why do I
still eat snacks regularly?
Hey, hey, are you hesitant
to show your true colors?
(Eun-tak) So if you had
done it when I asked you to
help me with five hundred,
how great would that be?
Come on, no matter
how you look at it, huh?
I am, after all, something that is both water and
fire, and sometimes I am present, sometimes I am not.
How do you do a
cash headbutt, crudely?
(Eun-tak)
Ah, I'll accept it all in a classy way.
[KIM SHIN'S SIGH]
Hey, but why do you consistently get five hundred?
I mean, the amount is so vague that I'm asking.
It's an amount that's hard to find even for a month's rent in Seoul.
(Eun-tak)
I'm not even dreaming about finding a place to rent.
The money to bounce around jjimjilbangs until I become an adult,
and if I happen to get into college,
I have to pay tuition,
so I'll keep two hundred from there,
to cover student loans and various living expenses.
It is the amount
calculated accurately.
That ambiguous five hundred
For someone with nothing like me
It's as heavy as five hundred million
Is that enough?
(Grim Reaper)
Give me five hundred, how is it still not...
Cold-blooded
(Euntak)
I have a question
You’re not going to give me five hundred
Ah, you surprised me
I thought you said, 'You’re not going to confess'
Give me five hundred
Pronounce it properly, you startled me
You said, 'Give me five hundred' though
Go study
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
(Grim Reaper)
But is your name Kim Sin?
Oh, why?
Your name
is really cool
[KIM SIN'S PUZZLED GROAN]
[SIGH]
(Sunny)
Ha, seriously
Aren't you going to do it? Just do it
(Eun-tak)
Boss, are you busy?
I don't even know when I'm busy
(Eun-tak)
Then, can I call you sister for a moment?
I don't have a sister to discuss things with
If I call you sister, there's only one genre
Are you pregnant?
No.
- So?
- (Euntak) Just
What do you think about getting married early?
[SIGH]
(Sunny) How old is the guy? Nineteen? Twenty?
A little older.
(Sunny) [scoffing] As if that's a lot.
What about the kid?
(Euntak) Hmm
Ah, he always has books close by
He has a deep appreciation for art and music
Uh, he used to work for the country...
Not that stuff, how does he treat you? Is he good to you?
Ah.
Well, for now, I need it
(Sunny)
Then what about you? Do you like that guy?
No
(Sunny)
Then does that guy like you?
No
What the hell, then, neither of you do
Why are you getting married?
That's true
[AWKWARD LAUGHTER]
What is this marriage?
[SNIFFLES]
Watch it
(Euntak)
Mister
Do I love you?
If that's needed, I'll go that far
I love you
(Euntak)
I don't need that kind of love.
Don't say you need an uncle
It seems I'll make you look pretty
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[DOOR LOCK OPERATING SOUND]
[The door opens with a click]
(Euntak)
I'm back
Are you folding laundry? I'll do it too
[EUNTAK'S COUGH]
You did it alone every day, right? It seems so
I'm grateful you recognize me
[Kim Shin's incredulous breath sound]
(Euntak)
Ah, the bathroom towels
All made by the uncle from the afterlife
No wonder the angles are killer
I wish you would refrain from
using the expression "to kill."
Ah, I'm sorry
(Eun-tak)
I really like the towels in this house
They're fluffy, high-quality, and have a nice texture
Ah, thank you
[PROFOUND MUSIC]
(Kim-shin)
A representative painter of the 17th century Dutch
Golden Age
Rembrandt van Rijn
dramatically combined light and darkness
It's better known by the title 'Night Watch'
Hmm, actually the title of this painting is 'Captain Frans Banning Cocq and
Lieutenant Willem van Ruytenburch's Civil Militia'
Where would it be good to hang this painting?
(The Grim Reaper) That scarf of
mine I think I saw it when you were nine.
Is that scarf yours?
Yes, it is.
It's my mother's keepsake.
(Euntak)
My mom thought that my ability to see ghosts was because of the mole on my neck,
so she wrapped this around me, believing that if I cover it, I wouldn't be able to see ghosts.
She did that since I was very young,
but it didn't help at all.
But now it's become a habit,
and it feels like my mom is still with me.
[SIGH]
Give me five hundred.
Ah, why do you keep asking for some kind of confession from me?
(Kim Shin)
Hey, and you...
Hey, what, every time I ask, there's a
story, right? Would I ask if I was scared?
What's wrong with this kid?
(Eun-tak) You didn't
answer the uncle, did you?
(Grim Reaper) That's really not
great, your personality.
(Eun-tak) It must
have been tough, but have
you decided on a name?
(Kim Shin) Hey, senior,
aren't you studying?
If you do well, you'll
totally fail to get into college.
Why would you
fail if you do well?
If you do well, you'll succeed. Ah,
forget it, you go inside and study!
(Kim Shin) Are you even
going to be a radio PD with that?
Oh, are you going to be a radio PD? That's cool.
(Euntak)
Yes, I've liked radio since I was young.
I talked about radio, so why are you talking to him?
(Euntak)
Ha, people living together should mix words a bit...
People?
(Kim Shin)
Looks like there are people among those you live with.
Look at this sword here, huh?
Hey, sir, if you haven't decided on a name yet...
(Euntak)
How about Park Bo-gum, Park Bo-gum?
Park Bo-gum
What sword?
(Kim Shin)
You pampered me just because I said I want to see a sword!
(Euntak)
[huffing]
Geez
Who do you think caused me to feel this way and see ghosts?
(Kim Shin)
The brand? It's just pretty.
(Euntak)
Oh my
Sir, did you just hit my hair?
Ah, that's why the sword is stuck in my heart.
There's always a reason why something like this sticks in a person, you know?
(Kim Shin)
How can you so precisely poke at people’s painful spots?
Are you a psychopath?
(Euntak) Do you think I wasn't
like this from the beginning?
'You are not a goblin bride' 'Don't live
by rumors, live in reality' You think I
was just being gentle
and not poking at you, huh?
I talked about this
for you, for you!
If you’re going to care about
me, then just give me a boyfriend!
(Euntak)
Part-time job, auntie, boyfriend!
What kind of guardian deity is
this? It hasn’t happened, boyfriend!
I’m here, your boyfriend!
Where is here, where is here?
(Kim Shin)
Here, in front of you!
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
[SOFT MUSIC]
[THE REAPER'S SIGH]
[THE BELL RINGS GENTLY]
[ROUGH BREATHING]
Ah, I must be crazy, he said he's my boyfriend
Seriously, who decided that I like him? Huh
It's absurd
[A COUGH]
[ROUGH BREATHING]
That's a misstep after 900 years
(Kim Shin)
Technically, he's not my boyfriend but my husband
Should I go and clarify it
It's very awkward
[A BIRD IS CHIRPING]
Someone
Can't even make a call because they have no name
But they are very
[HEAVY SOUND EFFECTS]
(The reaper)
Someone
Can't even make a call because they have no name
[THE DOOR CLICKS OPEN]
They are very
[The door clicks shut]
[A switch is pressed]
(Deokhwa)
Oh, it's so dark I can't stand it
What are you doing?
(Kim Shin)
Are you still doing that?
Get out, both of you
(Deokhwa)
Why is Uncle in the end room like this? Is something wrong?
He has a face that clearly thinks of a woman
What about me? What’s wrong? Where?
(Dukhwa)
I guess this is that girl's phone number
Oh, the laughter
[OF DUKHWA'S LIPS]
Give it to me, when I say it (Dukhwa) Uncle,
have you ever kissed on these lip marks?
Honestly, you should follow
me a bit, it probably isn't
a good place [tense sound
effect]
[Call connecting sound]
- (Dukhwa) Yes, uncle - Oh, the signal is coming, the signal is coming
- Hey, don't do that - If you aren't going to answer, then why pick up?
I might call someday
to look human, so
maybe today is that
someday (Sunny)
Hello
(Kim Shin)
Uh, uh, like a human, hurry up
[The grim reaper's strained moan]
[Tense sound effect]
[TENSE MUSIC]
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
[THE SECOND HAND STOPS]
[A SIGH]
[Clears throat]
Hello, I am...
No, not really, not good
Should I go a bit rough?
[In a rough voice]
What are you doing? Don't you know my voice?
It's not an easily forgettable voice
Ah, this isn't it either
[Clears throat]
Hello
[In a high voice]
Oh my, hello
[In a low voice]
Hello
(Kim Shin)
I'm the third one
[Imitating the grim reaper]
Hello
(Grim Reaper)
Were you listening to everything?
Why aren't you caught by this?
Cool, right? Amazing, right? Just pick up the phone
(Kim Shin)
I can do this too
Ding
[DEOKHWA MUMBLES]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
[THE CLOCK TICKS]
- (Deokhwa) What is this?
- (Kim Shin) Eat, eat
(Kim Shin)
Ice
[Mysterious sound effect]
[A SIGH]
(Sunny)
Hello
[A NERVOUS BREATH]
[CLEARING THE THROAT]
Hello
[An absurd breath]
[Slamming the snack down]
So you can make a call?
I thought you couldn't
or maybe your finger is broken
Ah, yes
I learned, my finger is not broken
Thank you for your concern
(Sunny)
My number was indeed there
Yes, number was here well...
I've been waiting, for contact
Ah, yes
'Ah, yes' Is there nothing more after that?
(Sunny)
Don't you have more to say?
For example...
When would be the most convenient time to meet among morning, lunch, and dinner?
When is the most convenient time for you among morning, lunch, and dinner?
For me, meeting in the morning and parting in the evening is the most convenient.
[A BIRD IS CHIRPING]
(Grim Reaper)
We need to walk so we look like humans.
[SOUND OF A CAR REMOTE CONTROL ACTIVATING]
(Deokhwa)
Please get in.
If you're human, you can't walk all the way to Incheon
(Grim Reaper)
Ah
[DEOKHWA'S SIGH]
[THE DOOR OPENS SUDDENLY]
[Heartbeat sound effect]
[Euntak's startled breath]
(Kim Shin)
I'm right here, your boyfriend!
Where is this, where is this?
(Kim Shin)
I'm the one right in front of you!
(Euntak)
I was so surprised to see you in front of me...
Ah, I'm really thirsty
Um, I...
I have to go to my part-time job
Ji Euntak
(Euntak)
What?
(Kim Shin)
Huh?
You just called me
- (Kim Shin) Me?
- Yes
- Why?
- So, why?
It's awkward
Me too
[AWKWARD LAUGHTER]
(Euntak)
Then should I
naturally say I'm hungry?
Would you like that?
(Kim Shin)
Then I'll naturally
say 'Do you want to eat beef?'
I'll quickly put on my coat
Mister, please get dressed
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
I'm all dressed, let's go, let's go
[EUNTAK'S SURPRISED MOAN]
This is my second time at this house
At this rate, it will become my regular spot
(Euntak)
We sat over there back then
[A MEANINGFUL PIECE OF MUSIC]
[FOOTSTEPS ECHO]
[English]
Welcome to Quebec
Please take a seat
[FOOTSTEPS ECHO]
(Euntak)
[Korean]
So, well, I should have come to a foreign country
(Sunny)
So why is it that I have to go overseas at this age of nine?
I didn’t even go to the supermarket in front of my house when I was twenty-nine.
- (Eun-tak) Really?
- (Sunny) Yeah, I don't have any plans.
(Eun-tak)
Still, I don't look like a person who just came to a foreign country.
I'm getting around really well.
I got a bit lost, but I didn't skip meals.
I'll eat a big piece of beef too.
I went to a fancy restaurant with some guy.
(Sunny)
What if the restaurant is fancy? The guy has to be cool.
I’m sleepy, I’m hanging up.
Okay, sleep well.
[A PLEASANT BREATHING SOUND]
CEO, over here.
[SMILING SLIGHTLY]
[CLINKING SOUNDS]
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
(Kim Shin)
At twenty-nine, you
are still shining
But next to you
I am not here
My life ultimately
has ended immortality
After my death
You, sitting behind that time
Your life, which has lost me
has forgotten me and is perfectly completed
I must disappear
[A SPARKLING SOUND EFFECT]
For you, who smiles beautifully
The choice I have to make
is to end this life
[HEAVY MUSIC]
In the end, I
made that choice.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
(Sunny)
Still handsome and still strange
Even though it feels strange
I keep forgetting as soon as I see your face
(Euntak)
It's not like pushing your head down
It's more like gently patting you
(Kim Shin)
So then
Can you help me become a little prettier?
(Euntak)
Yes
(Samsin)
Shouldn't you stop hurting now?
It hurt a lot
(Kim Shin)
I placed the house documents in your room
It's really your house now
Please live well for a long time
And I have a request
If I disappear
the child's mark will disappear too
Then at that time
please erase the child's memories
so that they do not blame themselves
Subtitle: Choi Hye-ran