[THEME SONG]
Sunny's face in her past life
The woman's face in the scroll you have
[HEAVY MUSIC]
It was like that
Are you sure?
What did you see?
(Grim Reaper)
The woman I saw
is standing in the middle of the palace
(Grim Reaper)
Wearing white clothes and looks noble
She was shot in the chest
and fell, bleeding
I told you that
Even if it wasn't all white
I don't think I talked about the bow
(Kim Shin)
Anything else? Didn't you see anything more?
Riding in a palanquin
I smiled looking at someone
Through a small window
(The Grim Reaper)
smiling and asking
'Am I pretty today...'
(Kim Sun)
Am I pretty today?
(The Grim Reaper)
In response to her question
there was one voice
- 'Ugly...'
- (Kim Shin) Ugly
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
Is your younger sister
right?
Right
[A SIGH]
(The Grim Reaper)
Then
what happens now?
[THE DOOR SWINGS OPEN]
Welcome
[The door slams shut]
[CALM MUSIC]
The part-timer is currently delivering...
Right?
Why is Seon-A
using my name again...?
(Kim Shin) Seon-A
(Sunny) Oh my, are you crazy?
Are you just going to keep watching?
(Grim Reaper) It's not precise
yet, so please refrain from skinship...
(Kim Shin) [taking a rough
breath] Are you really Seon?
(Sunny) If I am, so what?
Why is this person like this?
That's a deep story...
(Sunny) What deep story
could there be with this brother?
(Kim Shin) Yeah, yeah, it's me.
I'm your brother.
I wanted to see you, Seon-ah.
I'm Sunny, you know!
And didn't we agree not to see each other?
(Sunny)
No, what kind of man
still hangs out after hearing about
fried eggs?
Because this guy
was Sunny's brother in a past life.
Ha, what, what did you say? What life?
(Sunny)
Ha, I'm going crazy
You came to see me after making up a ridiculous 'legend of hometown'?
Tch, I guess you really wanted to see me.
(Kim Shin)
Who am I talking to, Seon-ah?
Do you truly not remember anything?
You're looking fine
and your face is also good, really.
(Sunny)
Okay, well, let's hear it then.
What was my previous life?
You were the Empress of Goryeo.
I was a general.
Ah, Goryeo?
Do you remember something?
I remember it clearly.
(Sunny)
Give me exactly five thousand won for the roasted sweet potatoes.
Previous life? Empress?
Even if I want to believe it, it's unbelievable.
- Are you leaving or not?
- (Kim Shin) Seon-ah.
(Sunny)
You go out too
[The grim reaper's pained groan]
(Kim Shin)
Seon-a, Seon-a
[SUNNY IS HUFFING]
(Eun-tak)
Oh, when did you two come?
What's going on...?
What happened?
(Sunny)
Part-timer, sprinkle some salt
There should be a bag over there
(Grim Reaper)
Um, I’m not sure how to explain that
- (Sunny) If you don't know, just don't
- (Grim Reaper) Yes
Seon-a
No, what's going on?
[KIM SHIN'S SIGH]
[MAJESTIC MUSIC]
(Euntak)
Let's exchange some information?
What is the relationship between Mr. Kim Shin and our boss?
Is it an ex-girlfriend?
I don't think so
If it were an ex-girlfriend, the grim reaper wouldn't be
doing things like this
It should be all dark and stuff
Uh, not at all, not like that
- My question is...
- It's a secret
I haven't asked yet
'Is there maybe another guy
coming to see your boss?'
Well, you're going to ask something like that, right?
But why is it a secret?
I told you everything, so why is it a secret for you?
Loyalty!
[A SCOFF]
[Bright music] [A sigh]
(Kim Shin) This is
the ripe persimmon
you loved to eat, Seon Ah, these are the
flower shoes you wanted, Seon Ah, this is
[THE COLOR YOU LIKED, SEON AH, A DEEP SIGH]
I don't like this
color I’m not wearing
flower shoes, I'm not eating ripe
persimmons (Sunny)
As you can see, there's
only this one table
Left because business
is good, that’s why I
visited. [Customers are noisy]
I’m a disruptor,
[AN ABSURD BREATH]
I really was
about to
leave, came in early.
(Sunny) Ha, part-timer Can't you
be with anyone else but that guy?
Do we have to meet?
- (Euntak) What?
- If you really have to, go and tell them.
(Sunny)
If you're going to buy things like a persimmon, flower shoes, or silk,
Just come empty-handed
and bring a chicken in that hand.
That's the way for you.
[AWKWARD SMILE]
Well, right
Why is that guy acting like this?
[SIGH]
Oh, by the way
The fact that I’m imagining this
about our boss
makes me feel really guilty and unpleasant,
but you know, your uncle
is actually coming to our store to buy things.
I'm just nervously watching the Grim Reaper
It's because your boss
is our uncle's younger sister in the last life
(Euntak)
Huh?
[EXCITING MUSIC]
Why?
Last life? No way, that's ridiculous
But how does oppa know that?
Can I tell you a secret?
(Euntak)
Yes
When the Grim Reapers touch a human,
they can see that person's past life
- Oh, really?
- It's clear that the two of them held hands.
(Duk-hwa)
So that's what Uncle Kkeut told me
[A SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
[A SIGH OF REALIZATION]
(Eun-tak)
Oh, right, I saw the two of them hold hands
Oh, wow
[A SIGH]
[SHE GRABS THE BAG SHARPLY]
[THE GRIM REAPER RATTLES THE BAG]
Are you sure that woman is my sister?
Did you see anything else?
No
(Grim Reaper)
I actually tried once more
But I failed because I said, 'I'll take care of it'
(Grim Reaper)
[sighing]
Don't be so upset.
Sunny doesn't have memories of her past life.
(Kim Shin)
So,
even if that woman was a good person in her past life,
to me, she is just "the hometown of legends."
That woman has a life in the present,
and what has passed should be left as it has passed,
I wish I had done everything back then.
When my sister and I were in the same time,
she was such a modest, graceful,
and dignified child.
How can she have such a different character
[NOW?]
Sunny, what’s wrong with your character?
[Playful music] You suddenly called me 'Seon-ah' back
then, but now you say no? Or do you hope it’s not true?
(Kim Shin) Weren’t you broken
up? Why are you getting defensive?
Are you thinking
of meeting again?
If that’s the case, just forget it. How dare you linger around my
sister, you grim reaper?
I think the thought from earlier is good
(grim reaper)
Let’s leave the past in the past (Kim Shin)
Before
dirt gets in my eyes,
Absolutely don’t stay away from my sister!
If there’s water, you should throw it all at once.
[Mysterious sound effect]
I know this drama.
I watched it a lot in the morning.
[SUNNY'S SIGH]
Part-timer
(Sunny)
Do you believe in things like past lives?
(Euntak)
Yes
You believe it?
They say humans have four lives.
The life that sows seeds
The life that waters the sown seeds.
The life that harvests the watered seeds
The life that uses what has been harvested.
This means there are four lives
Doesn't that mean there are past lives
And also reincarnations?
(Euntak)
Whether it's the boss or me
I'm not sure which number life this is
[SUNNY’S AGREEING MOAN]
Sounds plausible, huh? Where did you hear that?
I usually pick up a lot of sayings.
(Sunny)
So, what else have you picked up?
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
(Kim Shin)
Even knowing it can't be reached
Knowing everything, I
Had no choice but to move forward.
That place was my last battlefield
Because I had to die there.
Why on earth?
(Kim Shin)
I returned against the royal order
I overlooked the jealousy and fear of the young king
I cannot forget the late emperor's request to protect the woman
I had to save the innocent lives of the nobles
Above all
Because my sister was protecting that fool with her death
That person called Kim Sun
Was very brave in the face of love
[CLINKING THE TEACUP]
(Sunny)
Lead the way, part-timer
To the house of that man who claims to be my brother from a past life
What?
[THE DOORBELL RINGS]
[THE DOOR SHUTS TIGHTLY]
(Euntak)
I’m back.
We have a guest, everyone.
Shall we live together, just the two of us?
(Kim Shin)
Like this, the three of us.
But what brings you here?
"Please have a seat" comes first.
(Euntak)
Please have a seat, sir.
What can I get you to drink?
Do you have alcohol? Soju.
- Yes?
- We have beer.
We only drink beer.
(Sunny)
You didn’t say I could talk to you.
(Grim Reaper)
I’m sorry.
[KIM SHIN CLICKS HIS TONGUE]
How can someone have such a personality...
[THE GRIM REAPER'S DISAPPROVING BREATH]
You said I'm your younger sister?
You said it's 'Legend of the Origin'?
Show me the evidence.
(Sunny)
Even I am being swayed here.
I thought it couldn't be that two grown men teamed up just to tease me.
(Sunny)
Is this the evidence?
[As she unrolls the scroll]
What's this? Where did you buy it? Insadong?
[SIGH]
[SIGNIFICANT MUSIC]
(Sunny)
Is this person the queen?
Your younger sister?
(Euntak)
Isn't it amazing?
The boss has been waiting for the king every day
Is there something that comes to mind?
Just
young
and
pretty?
(Sunny)
I was ugly at that age
So what happened to this queen?
[DID SHE LIVE HAPPILY EVER AFTER?]
Sigh.
[(EUNTAK)
YOU TWO CAN TALK
WE'LL STEP ASIDE]
The door creaks open and shut.
(Sunny)
Was she unhappy? This queen?
There were more days I saw her through letters than the days I saw her face.
(Kim Shin)
The only support that remained during
the busy days of simply surviving was the time
[SPENT READING THE LETTERS SENT BY MY SISTER: HEAVY MUSIC]
[TENSION-FILLED SOUND EFFECTS]
(Military)
Direct hit!
(Minister 1) The Kim Shin from the
frontier has brought the news of victory.
(Minister 2) The Kim Shin from the
border has brought the news of victory.
(Minister 3) The Kim Shin from
Yodong has brought the news of victory.
..
Kim Shin’s victory report, if only
I dropped
by the marketplace (Jung Heon)
The foolish
people are always playing around, and the
resentment of the scholars has reached its peak. How glorious!
'The dignity of the royal family
is exposed in the marketplace.'
"I am worried about your sister's well-being"
Please inform me.
[THE ARROW FLIES SWIFTLY]
[KIM SEON'S PAINFUL MOAN]
[THE BOWSTRING SNAPS]
[TENSE MUSIC]
[A PITIABLE GASP]
You seem to lack talent in martial arts.
[A BIRD CHIRPS]
[A SIGH]
It's already been one meal.
You are only looking in one direction.
(Seon-gung)
[Smiling slightly]
It seems you may lack talent in studying.
(Kim Seon)
No, it seems there is sorrow in my heart.
[A SIGH]
By the way, how come you
haven't come to see me even once?
[KIM SUN'S SIGH]
He is truly a person who makes a woman sick
[A SIGH]
[SOFT MUSIC]
(Court Lady)
Your Majesty, I bring you food
[KIM SUN'S SURPRISED MOAN]
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
It's heavy
(Kim Sun)
Ah
An unfeeling person resides in my heart
Why are you in such a hurry...
To see Your Majesty
I will go,
But it seems better if we come together
[Heavy music]
(Jungheon)
In hands that hold something humble,
One must apply just the right amount of strength.
It's precious, hold it tightly
That worthless yet precious thing
will surely die
(That's right)
By that hand
(Young king)
No, absolutely not
Do not bring any decoctions
to the empress's chambers
It is a royal order
The empress must not drink any decoctions
No matter who sends them, absolutely do not drink
(Lady in waiting)
How can they be like that
Your Majesty, how can this be so upsetting
(Subordinate)
Open the door!
It is General Kim Shin, the great general!
[LAUGHTER FROM THE SUBORDINATE]
[ANGRY BREATHING]
Your brother has improved again.
Which one of us would you like to live?
- Your Majesty
- (Young Prince) Answer me then.
[Tense music]
(Young Prince)
Or have you already calculated it?
Well, whether I live or my brother lives,
you have nothing to lose.
You are unworthy.
Do you want to die?
Why do you look like that?
[SNORT]
Your heart is already in mourning.
(Young Prince)
I can no longer understand.
Is the barbarian from the border the enemy
or is your brother the enemy...
(Kim Seon)
Park Joong-heon is the enemy
You will have to choose
whether to live as my woman
or to die as the sister of a heinous criminal
[A HOLLOW LAUGH]
(Kim Shin)
It wasn't for long
but it seems there were happy moments
Even at the last moment of closing my eyes
I was just looking at that fool
[A SIGH]
[A MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
[STRAINED BREATHING SOUNDS]
[A SIGNIFICANT PIECE OF MUSIC]
[SUNNY'S AGONIZED MOANS]
Then
What about the king?
Did that king also reincarnate?
I don't know
I want to see what his face looks like
Is he handsome?
[HE CHUCKLES]
If you were my sister
There is one thing that remains unchanged
But
Why do you always talk
(Sunny)
So affectionately and passionately?
As if life has been
Continuously connected since that time
I won’t believe it, but
I've lived with that memory intact
[SIGH]
I know you're not believing me, but this is what I have to say.
It's not because I believe in past lives,
I came because of the soft persimmons, flower shoes, and silk.
(Sunny)
I wonder if the things I couldn't do for you have left a grudge.
It's certain that you're crazy,
but it seems like you're beautifully crazy.
So I felt a bit sad.
At times like this, it feels like Sunyi is right.
(Sunny)
You suddenly drop the honorifics and say that you were my brother in a past life,
so don't do that.
Even brothers who live in the countryside feel awkward when they meet after a while.
A brother who claims to have crossed life
How can I suddenly be happy to see him?
So don't be too upset, okay?
I was rude, then
[SUNNY'S SIGH]
[A SIGH]
This man won’t even look at me
[THE DOOR OPENS WITH A CLICK]
[A BIRD CHIRPS]
[A SIGH]
[SUNNY'S LIGHT SIGH]
Why are you looking when you’re not going to catch me?
Can I catch you?
What if I catch you?
What happens to us then?
[A SIGH]
I'm really ugly.
[SUNNY'S SIGH]
Is it you
Or not
[THE APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS]
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
(Kim Shin)
Did you go well?
That woman
Always goes so well
Are you okay?
What?
[A FAINT SIGH]
I have something I'm curious about
About that scroll, who drew it?
Wang Ye
[SIGNIFICANT MUSIC]
It's the image of a sister
But it's the image he saw
(Kim Shin)
His sorrow, sin, and longing are contained
That scroll
Perhaps it is
I think it might have been his last move.
He killed everyone like that?
He killed everyone like that
[A FAINT SIGH]
[THE PAPER JINGLES]
Part-timer?
(Eun-tak)
Yes, it's me
[SUNNY'S PAINFUL GROAN]
I thought you would be doing this
[SUNNY'S SIGH]
I thought my past life was nothing
(Sunny)
I don't even believe it
But once I left that house
My whole body hurts like I've got a cold
If it’s hard for you, let me know; we can go to the hospital
No, at home.
[SUNNY'S LABORED BREATHING]
There's nothing here
(Sunny)
It keeps hurting here
No
[Emotional music]
It hurts deeper inside
Someone cruel
Walks through my heart
So it feels like my heart is sinking
[SUNNY'S LABORED MOAN]
Let's go
(Euntak)
It's cold outside
(Lion)
Huh?
(Sunny)
[In a labored voice]
Why?
Oh, it's someone living in the rooftop room
(Euntak)
Oh, okay
[SUNNY'S LABORED MOAN]
Be careful on the stairs
The woman from the apartment below
was a friend of the Goblin priest
The world is really small, isn't it?
(Sunny)
That person had it on their phone
What is it?
Goblin couple
The person claiming to be your brother?
Goblin couple?
You won't tell me, will you?
The identities of those people
I'm sorry
That person
won't say anything either?
Their true identity
I'm sorry
[SIGH]
Should we break up?
Are you just a human?
Yes
Got it
[SIGH]
[CALM MUSIC]
What are you doing?
I've come to meet you
Where should we start?
I walked every step you took
with you
[I CHUCKLE]
Hmm, look at how nicely you speak
(Euntak)
Your life, boss, really
Since I was born,
I was always Euntak from a strange land
Whether I saw a ghost or a goblin appeared
Whether I faced the grim reaper
there was nothing strange about it
But you, boss,
suddenly got mixed up in a really strange genre, right?
In a past life, the person who was my brother is a goblin.
The man I like is a grim reaper.
Part-time workers see ghosts
and sometimes there are more ghosts than customers
in the store.
What exactly is a past life?
It's just a life that has passed
(Euntak)
Did I also briefly stay
in Kim Shin's life
at some moment
I can't remember?
Well,
I really wish our boss
was actually an older sister.
Our boss is really a great person.
(Kim Shin)
I don't think so.
Siblings are indeed
Always bickering in this life or the last
I wish I had an older brother like Kim Shin
Ah, I do have an older brother? Taehee
(Kim Shin)
You just wait, okay?
The two of us will go to Canada
to that restaurant to buy some cows, right?
Ah, my regular place?
After going there twice,
what do you mean your regular place?
(Kim Shin)
I've been going there for 50 years, you know?
I'm not going with anyone else,
I’m only going with the uncle.
You're funny, aren't you?
[SCOFF]
(Euntak)
Me?
Really? When?
Oh, how do you know?
(Kim Sin) I came to pick you up for no reason, I came
to pick you up for no reason (Euntak) How do you know?
[Students are chattering]
- (Student 1) Hey, together,
together
- (Student 2) Hey, come in, come in, come in
[(STUDENT 3)
DON'T GO BACK, ONE, TWO, THREE CAMERA SHUTTER SOUND]
- (Student 4) One more time,
one more time - (Student 3) One...
[CAMERA SHUTTER SOUND]
[STUDENTS ARE CHATTERING]
- (Student 5) Take a picture for me, take a picture for me
- (Student 6) Please take a picture
(Student 5)
Model pose, model pose
[Mobile phone vibration sound]
[THE STUDENTS CONTINUE TO CHATTER]
(Euntak)
Hello
It's my number
(Euntak)
How did you know my number?
When a new semester starts, the class president is
given something called an emergency contact list?
(Yoona)
You probably haven't received it
Because I was the class president for three years
[SHE SMILES SLIGHTLY]
Congratulations on your graduation
Let's call each other occasionally
Yeah, congratulations to you too
(Teacher)
Okay, everyone, take a seat!
[THE STUDENTS ARE NOISY]
Wearing casual clothes makes you look mature
Everyone worked hard for three years
(Teacher)
The uniforms we pass down
will be well handed to the juniors
Well, there's no point in the homeroom teacher talking too long
because it will be boring, so I'll end it here
Congratulations on your graduation!
[THE STUDENTS CHEER]
(Teacher)
Ah, parents outside,
please come in and
hug your children, saying 'Congratulations, you worked hard,' okay?
(Male 1)
Hello, congratulations [Parents are
noisy]
(Female 1)
Our puppy
(teacher)
Su-jin's mother - (teacher) Yes,
how have you been?
- (Female 2) Hello (Female
2)
You've worked hard [The classroom is
bustling]
(Teacher)
Oh, Ji-soo's mother -
(Female 3) Teacher, how have you been?
- (Teacher) Have you been well?
(Female 3)
Yes, you've worked
hard
(Teacher)
[smiling]
Thank
you, oh, thank you for your hard work, yes, please come in, yes
[ Tense sound effect ]
[ Sad music ]
[FOOTSTEPS ECHO]
You went through a lot.
Mom will be so proud.
(Samshin)
Go home and share it with your family, for sure.
Why don't you hug me?
[SHE SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(Samshin)
Because you're pretty.
When you were chosen,
I was happy.
[SHE SMILES SLIGHTLY]
[Euntak's surprised breath]
Shh.
(Samshin)
Congratulations on your graduation.
[A SIGH]
My dear.
Couldn't you have been a better teacher?
[TREMBLING BREATH]
Couldn't you have been a shining teacher?
[SOBBING]
[KEEPS SOBBING]
(Teacher)
Ah, why is this happening?
[Sniffles]
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
[THE TEACHER SOBS]
[PEOPLE MURMUR]
[SHE SMILES SLIGHTLY]
[THE TEACHER SNIFFLES]
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECTS]
[Significant music]
(Innkeeper)
It's cold, oh my.
"Tavern"
Sleep now.
[THE INNKEEPER CLINKS THE DISHES DOWN]
Sleep well, everyone.
Thank you.
(Kim Shin)
There are those who are
born with the same face as in their
[PAST LIVES ONCE OR TWICE IN A HUNDRED YEARS]
[THE SOUND OF THE CAMERA SHUTTER]
The moan of the serving girl
straining. (Man 2) How is it, my lady?
Is something uncomfortable for you?
No, it’s just that after all this
time
I’m seeing the distant past
ahead of me, is it the distant past?
How distant is it, my lady?
Surely, we speak the language of
Joseon,
Yet there’s a mix of words (Kim
Shin)
I wonder if the world has become one
or not; I understand but don’t understand—it's not just that.
A piece of scrap metal the size of a inkstone
is caressed like a newborn baby shrimp
Like someone I long for
I cherish it
[A FLUSTERED BREATH]
(Man 2)
I don’t quite understand what you mean...
It's black and blue
[bright music]
It seems to be used very widely
Remember this
This is what it looks like
Click
If there's something to invest in, do it big
Yes, sir
[THE CLASSROOM IS NOISY]
(Woman 4)
It's pretty
[WOMAN 4'S LAUGHTER]
(Student 7)
Mom, can you hold this for a second?
[GIGGLES]
It stayed for a while
In a moment you didn't even know
[A SLIGHT SMILE]
What are you doing?
I'm curious
(Kim Shin)
How did I see you from that far away?
When? In the classroom earlier?
No, from much farther
There’s a strange and beautiful thing
Specifically, what?
In the 12th year of King Cheoljong in the late Joseon Dynasty, I met you
Who?
First love
Ha, I, this gentleman
What do you mean by not asking or being curious?
Where does that phrase come from?
It’s not from the 'Analects' or 'Mencius'
It comes from the gallery, the gallery
I said I didn’t ask, I’m not curious
I’m curious
(Kim Shin)
Where did this flower come from?
Is that kid, whatever his name is, Tae-hee...
(Eun-tak)
Tae-hee didn’t come, you know
If he had come, we would have been together, he wouldn’t have just sent me away
I also have acquaintances who give me stuff like herbs
So don’t mess around.
Please take a photo for me
- (Eun-tak) Okay, when you press this, it goes click...
- I know
Oh, that's unexpected?
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
(Eun-tak)
Wow, I don't even have one graduation photo
I should cherish it for a lifetime
Hey, for you, taking one photo
has a story...
So would you take a photo for me?
Don’t move
[CAMERA OPERATING SOUND]
[SLIGHT SMILE]
[Clears throat]
[Camera operating sound]
[CAMERA OPERATING SOUND]
[CAMERA SHUTTER SOUND]
[SIGH]
Hey, one, two, three, you have to take it.
(Euntak)
Is it really okay to just take it like this?
Even if you take it like that, it's pretty.
Chee
[SHE HANDS OVER THE BOUQUET]
Our school is really nice, right?
[CAMERA OPERATION SOUND]
[Camera shutter sound]
(Kim Shin)
It’s nice.
(Euntak)
There were a few things I really disliked though.
(Student 1)
No, it's the graduation ceremony.
[Camera shutter sound]
What, you’re not taking any photos and just using your phone?
(Male 3)
Mom, be a little more affectionate.
[Camera shutter sound]
(Eun-tak)
There were really good things.
Good things seem to come late originally.
Like an uncle.
I came early, but I didn’t know which class I was in.
Not that.
Don't feel sad about coming alone.
Deok-hwa has gone to work.
That guy from the underworld
is currently feeling very uncomfortable.
Everyone is congratulating.
Then who are those two?
(Kim Shin)
Those two didn’t come to the graduation ceremony.
It seems they came to see someone who will be at the graduation ceremony.
Amazing!
Then we, uncle, door, door, open
I guess you came to congratulate on the graduation
That's an excuse, I'm here to see someone else
Fortunately, you're standing in front of me
(Sunny)
Seeing your face makes me feel determined
So I came
Seeing your face
It's just nice
Did the investigation that was supposed to happen before finish?
(Sunny)
Why aren't you sharing the details?
I came here to hear that, you know?
Not yet
(Sunny)
Then next time,
After finishing the investigation, let's meet to return the ring.
[SUNNY RUSTLES THE BOUQUET]
(Sunny)
Please give this to our part-time worker.
That's why I bought it.
Why are you giving this to me?
(Reaper)
No matter who I am,
I wanted to give someone flowers at least once.
Who are you, Kim Woo-bin?
[A FAINT SIGH]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC]
You may not believe it,
but I don't know either.
[SIGH]
Who I am.
Those people
mostly say unbelievable things
Are they unbelievable beings?
(Sunny)
This relationship really has no answer
I hoped it wouldn't be like this
but the conclusion keeps heading towards tragedy
[SIGH]
[THE DOOR SWINGS SHUT WITH A THUD]
Gift
(Kim Shin)
Now that I've graduated and I'm an adult
use it where it's needed
I can't use this yet
(Eun Tak)
Legally
we need our aunt's permission
So I legally received it
Now it's yours.
Really?
Wow, how?
(Euntak)
Thank you
It's not me, it's my mom who's giving it
I'm just passing it on instead
Still, thank you
(Euntak)
Ha, what should I do
I don't think I can use this even a bit
It's too precious since mom gave it
I don't think I can use it at all
Use it where it's needed, I'm sure she'll want that
It must have been a desperate prayer left thinking of
her nine-year-old daughter living alone in this world without her.
[SHE SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(Euntak) But how is our aunt?
Is she doing well?
[THE SOUND OF GYEONGSIK
SHIVERING IN THE COLD]
(Gyeongsik) Oh, it's cold
(Gyeongmi) Oh,
my face is tightening
[Gyeongsik sniffs]
I used some terrible
lotion (Euntak's
aunt) Ah, why Ji
Eun-tak I can't remember,
where the heck can I find this year?
(Gyeongsik) You can't
find her now, she must have
graduated [Gyeongsik
sniffs] She probably got into
university, if you look in Seoul,
she'll show up She studied well.
[Playful music]
[Kyung-sik and Aunt Eun-tak's exclamations]
College!
Ah, after eating rice that’s like prison food,
your brain is finally working properly.
(Kyung-sik)
You really have the constitution for that prison food, you do.
(Aunt Eun-tak)
You need to eat it regularly, come on, let’s go.
(Kyung-mi)
But you didn’t spend all that money, right?
Hey, only someone who has spent money knows how to spend it.
(Aunt Eun-tak)
She absolutely can’t spend that money.
It reminds her of her mom.
Just look for it, that’s all you need.
(Kyung-sik)
Mom, I’m hungry, let’s eat something.
Do you want to have a beer?
Let’s sleep.
From your expression, it looks like it didn’t end well.
I moved my seat for you after all.
I’m me, and you’re you.
What do you mean?
The list has come.
Chairman Yoo?
No.
Other omissions.
[TENSE MUSIC]
(Grim Reaper)
It’s a fall death in two weeks.
You won’t see it, but
Thanks for letting me know.
(Grim Reaper)
Is that it? You’re not angry?
Aren’t you cursing the gods?
This kind of thing will come again and again, dozens of times.
You can't be surprised every time.
[SIGH]
That’s true.
(Samsin)
So draw the sword and return to the nothingness
into peace.
[Heavy music]
If not, death will keep approaching that child.
Can you stop all those moments?
Can you really stop them?
(Samsin)
Eventually, a moment will come that you can't stop.
Then Euntak will lose her life,
and you'll lose the chance to return to nothingness.
You have to live through that hell for another thousand years or maybe forever.
It's a foolish choice.
So pull out your sword and return to nothingness.
(Three gods)
It's sad, but that's the best option.
I don't want to seem like I'm not doing my best.
It's a bit sad.
(Euntak)
Is something wrong?
What is this?
The list of names.
Who?
Is it you, sir?
(Kim Shin)
No.
You.
Me?
Am I going to die?
Listen to me carefully from now on.
It's a story I've kept hidden from you all this time.
(Kim Shin)
I told you not to hide anything from you
But this is a story I hid
But
I think I can’t hide it anymore
So I’m going to tell you
You
If you don’t draw my sword, you will die
You have that fate
Since you were born as the goblin’s bride
If you don't draw the sword
Death will keep approaching you
Like this
[HEAVY MUSIC]
So
(Euntak)
If I don’t draw the uncle's sword
Until I die
Are you saying you're dying?
Continuously, continuously.
Then, what about all this time?
The accidents.
(Kim Shin) Uh
When I was kidnapped
[Loan Shark 1's Surprised Groan]
(Loan Shark 2)
Ah, I’m surprised, Lee
(Kim Shin)
When you collapsed at the ski resort
[THE SOUND OF BREATH IN SURPRISE]
The big accident on the interview day you didn't know about
[THE SOUND OF TIRE FRICTION]
And
When I almost killed you
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[A SIGH]
God
is too harsh
on both the uncle and me
[EUN-TAK'S SIGH]
What kind of fate is this, really
[INHALES DEEPLY]
(Eun-tak)
Uncle
I just want to die
Uncle will keep living on and on.
I'll be reborn and come to meet you.
I will definitely be here.
I'll find you.
I promise.
Shall we?
(Euntak)
Uncle, let's just draw the sword.
If I die,
you will have to live alone forever.
The bride might not show up.
I'll just draw the sword for you.
Isn't that better?
[KIM SHIN'S SIGH]
Shall we?
Uncle
Let's just die together.
(Euntak)
I think that's good, at the same time
So no one is left alone
So no one is heartbroken
[A TREMBLING BREATH]
Jieun-tak, look at me
(Kim Shin)
You're not going to die, I'm going to make sure of that
I'm going to stop it
I'm going to stop everything
[CRYING SOFTLY]
[SOFT MUSIC]
[EUNTAK IS CRYING SOFTLY]
I'm sorry
For getting you involved in this fate
(Kim Shin)
But we have to go through this
[EUNTAK CONTINUES TO CRY SOFTLY]
I don't know which door I'll be opening
But I won't let go of your hand, I promise
So trust me
I might be bigger than you think
[EUNTAK'S CRYING]
(Kim Shin)
Where are you going? You're in danger right now
Where am I going? I have to go to my part-time job
What did you hear from what I said?
I understood everything well
(Euntak)
But
I can't keep living locked up in this house
If I stay locked up in this house
trembling for a long time,
That's not living.
Even if I die tomorrow, I have to live today.
I go to my part-time job, prepare for college entrance exams,
walk the usual path,
and come back home like that.
That's
what life is.
So, uncle, please protect me with all your might.
I'm trying my best not to die.
I believe in you, uncle.
How could my mom have given birth to me?
What kind of university did I get into?
There's too many reasons to live.
Among them, it's the goblin that,
especially makes me want to live.
Alright, I got it.
If you think it's dangerous, make sure to summon me.
Don't ever go to high places, got it?
Oh, I said it's a fall death?
Yes, don't worry.
I'll be back.
[THE DOOR CLOSES WITH A CLICK]
[KIM SHIN'S SIGH]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
(Euntak)
No, the flickering streetlight
is too dangerous.
[THE STREETLIGHT CRACKLES]
[A SIGH OF RELIEF]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
No, that man is just too handsome.
(Eun-tak)
The handsome man is too dangerous
[EUN-TAK LETS OUT A PUFF OF AIR]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
No, that outfit is too dangerously beautiful
Pretty clothes are dangerous for my bank account
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
(Eun-tak)
No, I miss you too much,
I can't breathe
Too dangerous
Me too
[SOFT MUSIC]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
(Sunny)
Now I can see everything, huh?
Am I really looking at flowers blooming in midwinter?
Hey, are you crazy enough to want to die?
[SIGH]
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[SIGH]
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
[THE DOOR SWINGS OPEN AND SHUT]
[TENSE SOUND EFFECTS]
[THE RING DROPS WITH A THUD]
[TENSE MUSIC]
[APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[A breath of relief]
[The door swings open and shut]
[THE DOOR SWINGS OPEN AND SHUT]
[FOOTSTEPS ECHO]
(Sunny)
Approximately 184 in height.
If you include the shoe height of 2 centimeters
Is this about the height?
[TENSE SOUND EFFECTS]
[MYSTICAL SOUND EFFECTS]
[SAD MUSIC]
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECTS]
[SUNNY'S TREMBLING BREATH]
So this was the identity
[TREMBLING BREATH]
But
I still don't know
[SUNNY'S TREMBLING BREATH]
(Sunny)
You
What on earth is it?
[TREMBLING BREATH]
Ah, I’m going crazy
How can this nonsensical thing
Because it’s so nonsensical
Everything makes sense
How did you know my name?
Why was there no name?
Why was everything so wrong?
What did you do to me, back then?
Don't do it now, whatever it is
I won't
Just
I will get caught
[WITH TREMBLING BREATH]
What is it, what are you anyway?
I am
The Grim Reaper.
What did you say?
Knowing it wouldn't work
I dreamed of a happy ending
But as expected
It's a tragedy
[WITH TREMBLING BREATH]
(Death Angel)
Shall we stop now?
Shall we part ways?
[HEAVY MUSIC]
[A SIGH]
[SOUND OF A MOBILE PHONE OPERATION]
(Euntak)
The orientation ended a while ago
and the course registration just finished
Right now, we are on a campus tour
[Mysterious sound effect]
(Ghost 1)
'I miss you, yuyu' say it, heart, heart
'I love you, heart, heart' say it
Ah, how romantic
I also had a time like that, on a warm spring day
But now, wandering in the underworld,
it's endlessly deep and dark.
(Spirit1)
Every day, living in the cold
winter nights
I wish you could just meet that kid
just once
It would be nice if you could just ask
one thing that you're curious about
Curious about what? What?
'Did you ever love me?'
Something like that?
Ah, how romantic
Alright, let's finish that winter night
Let's go for revenge
What should we do to that kid?
[EXCITING MUSIC]
Are you going to sing?
Because preparation is key
[DRAMATIC BREATHING SOUNDS]
What is going on?
I have something to say regarding your late wife.
(Euntak)
Lee Jeong-hwa.
Is it a good time?
[THE ROAD IS NOISY]
(Man 4)
About my wife...
I'll keep it brief.
Lee Jeong-hwa has a message to pass on.
Yes, go ahead.
Have you been well?
'Have you been well?'
You looked good with Hee-jin.
'You looked good with Hee-jin.'
That's what she said.
[HEAVY MUSIC]
Who?
Your wife.
[EMBARRASSED LAUGHTER]
Heejin, how...
You brought me home.
'You brought me home.'
- (Ghost 1) The day we became 200 days
- (Euntak) 'The day we became 200 days'
(Ghost 1)
You bought me a hundred pretty things?
'You bought me a hundred pretty things?'
With my insurance money
'With my insurance money'
Oh, really?
(Euntak)
Oh, I really feel it at this point, seriously
(Ghost 1)
So that day I was on the roof
'So that day I was on the roof'
Did you push her?
'Pushed...'
[TENSE MUSIC]
[TENSE SOUND EFFECTS]
"Jieun Tak, 20 years old"
What are you making me do right now?
(Euntak)
This kind of development is troublesome.
Who are you?
(Ghost 1)
While you were on the phone with Heejin,
planning the crime
I recorded everything
and hid it in the shoe cabinet by the entrance.
No
If you hid the planning of the crime with Heejin
in the shoe cabinet,
you should take it to the police station
and resolve it like this and that.
You can't do this
(Man 4)
How did you know?
Where are you looking while you’re talking?
(Ghost 2)
Right
Why are you turning something that should be a sitcom
into a thriller?
Oh, your husband is so scary
If we keep going like this without a plan
we're all gonna die
I'm already dead
Oh my, sister, look at how selfish you are
Then what about me, what about me?
(Man 4)
Are you crazy?
What are you constantly looking at while talking?
Your wife, your wife that you killed
Ah
You want to die too, huh
[TENSE MUSIC]
Anyway, kids these days
really have no caution
They climb up that railing
Isn't that right?
(Eun-tak)
Ah...
Falling to death
I really didn't want to use the real boyfriend chance
[BREATH SOUNDS FILLED WITH FEAR]
I'm really worried about how much we'll get scolded by our boyfriend, ugh
[BLOWING AIR THROUGH MY LIPS]
[Kim Shin slashes with a knife]
[Moan of man 4]
[THE TENSION-RAISING MUSIC]
[MOANING]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[HEAVY MUSIC]
[SIGH]
I'm sorry
Go and receive the punishment of humanity
When I receive my punishment, you will die
(Man 4)
I killed someone
I killed my wife, my wife
(Ghost 1)
I'm sorry
[Sniffling]
I just wanted to talk so much
That I was wronged, that it hurt
That I wanted to be saved, that I wanted help
The words I couldn't say back then
I want to say all of them.
[EUNTAK'S SURPRISED BREATH]
(Euntak)
Ah, I'm sorry.
You really, you almost died just now.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Sister, please go somewhere good quickly.
I think I need to be scolded a bit.
Thank you for helping me.
[CALM MUSIC]
Thank you for listening.
(Ghost 1)
Take care, Euntak.
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
(Euntak)
Are you still angry?
You must be angry, right? You'll get mad, right?
[SIGH]
[Euntak's surprised breath]
[Kim Shin's sigh]
I wasn't angry, just worried
(Euntak)
But why do I feel like I'm being scolded?
My heart is prickling
It must not be as bad as mine?
In just an hour
I don’t know how many times I went through hell
Ha, really
We're really pitiful
[CALM MUSIC]
No
Ah, really
So, is it unhappy?
No
Then
(Euntak)
Has the uncle stopped scolding me
now?
No
Once I become a university student, I’ll go on many blind dates
(Euntak)
You should only wear an
extremely short skirt, right?!
[EUNTAK'S LAUGHTER]
(Saja) You look pale these
days. Are you working out?
[SAJA'S LAUGHTER]
Is it funny?
You look so gloomy
I just said that
to make you smile, but it's not funny
(Death God)
Why do you want to see me?
(Saja) Ah, yes, it's because there are two
missing documents for the seniors, right?
But only one was submitted They asked you to
submit a reason document [Death God's sigh]
Senior, you really don't check
your company email enough.
[SIGH]
What do I need to know to raise it?
What do you mean by that?
Has it been about 20 years?
I encountered some deceased person,
but they were a spirit with no information at all.
What kind of spirit was it?
It seemed like they had wandered in this world for a very long time,
and they didn't seem to be afraid at all.
It was strange to see a spirit that wasn't afraid of the reaper.
(Reaper)
Of course, I missed it.
I just submitted the paperwork for no reason and got the short end of the stick.
The remaining sheet is for that spirit.
(Ghost 2)
It's a new face.
I mentioned before
about the experience that has been wandering for ages.
(Euntak)
Ah, that...
(Ghost 2)
They say that 20 years ago,
they once met a reaper and ran away.
Really?
I also had a similar experience when I was nine...
[TENSE MUSIC]
[MUSIC THAT HEIGHTENS THE TENSION]
[TENSE SOUND EFFECTS]
[A CRUNCHING SOUND IS HEARD]
Nice to meet you.
You're that goblin bride.
[TENSE SOUND EFFECTS]
[A CRUNCHING SOUND IS HEARD]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
Aren't you curious about who you are?
(Grim Reaper)
Did you give the answer
or did you ask the question
I forget too
It must have been very lonely
Please forgive me
[FOOTSTEPS ECHO]
(Kim Shin)
He asked if that person is Wang Ye
Finally, it's here
I will do those things now
Subtitle: Choi Hyeran