[THEME SONG]
(Euntak)
Just a moment
[Significant sound effect]
(Euntak)
That story isn’t over yet...
[Kim Shin's surprised groan]
[IT’S BEING LIVELY]
(Kim Shin)
Did you just come in through that door?
Following me?
[CHEERFUL MUSIC]
But why is it like this here?
(Euntak)
What the heck happened?
Where is this place, really?
Canada
(Euntak)
If it’s Canada...
The, maple country?
And, the auroras are there?
Is this really, really foreign?
(Euntak)
Wow
Did you have this kind of ability, sir?
You have it too, what are you really?
(Euntak)
If this is really Canada
And if your ability is this much
I’ve made up my mind
- What?
- I’ve decided, I have
- (Kim Shin) What, what?
- I’m going to get married, to you, sir
(Euntak)
No matter how much I think about it
I really think you are a goblin
I love you
[LAUGHTER]
Oh, look at you pretending to be hearing it for the first time
Ha, don’t!
(Euntak)
Oh, look at you not actively refusing.
Now, let's go over there.
Think of it as a honeymoon.
(Kimshin)
Hey, hey.
[Bright music]
[CAMERA SHUTTER SOUND]
I look really natural, right?
Doesn't it look like I'm an illegal immigrant?
Doesn't it look like I'm a kid who's come abroad for the first time?
"Noel Boutique"
(Euntak)
Wow, wow!
[English]
Merry Christmas.
[LAUGHTER]
(Euntak)
[Korean]
Could you take a picture of me?
I want to leave myself behind in this landscape
If you look here, if you press this
- There's a click sound and...
- (Kim Shin) I know
Oh, that's unexpected?
Then count to one, two, three and take the picture
(Kim Shin)
No
[Camera shutter sound]
(Eun Tak)
Mom!
[The cell phone drops heavily]
Ah, seriously, where are you going?
Ah, let's go together
Wow, it really is a maple country
Is this the place? A red carpet for me
(Eun Tak)
It's an honor to walk together, right?
Phew, I'm glad
I was worried it might be 'Glory is a flounder'
But what is that sign?
(Kim Shin)
Fairy Appearance Area
Is this it?
Wow, does that mean fairies come out?
That's awesome, it's romantic
You must be happy, sir
(Kim Shin)
Why would I be happy?
(Eun Tak)
Fairy appearance
You met a fairy, Tinkerbell
Ha, I'm a bit upset that I got caught
How did you know I would come?
All, huh? This is to make
romantic memories. That's why they
made such things. Ah, but what's
the name of this neighborhood?
(Kim Shin) Quebec
(Eun Tak) Oh, the
name is cool, but do you know?
If you catch a falling maple leaf...
(Eun Tak) Huh?
[SOFT MUSIC]
Did you catch it now? Oh, hurry and throw
it away (Kim Shin) Why
do I have to do that?
If you catch a falling maple leaf with
the person you're
walking with, it means
[YOUR LOVE WILL COME TRUE, KIM SHIN SCOFFS]
Be honest with me, you
just made that up, right?
No, that's not true.
(Euntak)
If you catch a falling cherry blossom petal,
there's a saying that it means you'll be with your first love
It's in the same context
You love me, right?
- Are you a goblin, mister?
- No
(Euntak)
So, hurry up and throw it away
(Kim Shin)
Then why were you trying to catch it?
I think it's because I'm walking with that oppa.
(Kim Shin)
Oppa?
(Euntak)
If I get close to that handsome oppa,
I need to look carefully
[EUNTAK'S URGENT BREATHING]
Canadian ghost, Canadian ghost
(Euntak)
Ah, I'm scared
I made eye contact with a ghost
Ah, I feel nauseous
You said you see ghosts often,
what's so scary?
(Euntak)
They speak to me in English
Because the ghost speaks English,
I have to...
No, but this uncle
Isn't this a hotel?
No matter how foreign it is, isn't it a bit awkward to be here with a high schooler?
You said, this way, this way
You said you’d come marry me?
Are you a goblin, mister?
No, I'm just resting here.
[EUN-TAK'S URGENT MOAN]
- Where are you going?
- I have something to do.
What do you have to do?
Can't I go with you?
(Eun-tak)
It's my first time in a foreign country, so I'm really scared.
The really scared kid
is running around everywhere.
Ah, that's...
Since Uncle is next to me
I can trust him, right?
(Eun-tak)
Will it take a long time? Who are you meeting?
Ah, you're meeting a girl? That's right.
You came all the way to Canada,
so there must have been some kind of promise.
You told me I'm not a goblin bride
There must have been some context
I understand, have a good trip
I mean, I have no money, no passport
No one I know
My breathing is all unstable like this
I guess I'll have to wait alone
You know what I mean, right?
I don’t know
[PLAYFUL MUSIC]
I meant to ask if you could lend me about 10 dollars
The uncle might abandon me
Well, whether intentionally or by mistake
Then I would have to call the embassy...
(Kim Shin)
If I abandon you, summon me
That's faster than the embassy, you
[RIDICULOUS BREATHING SOUNDS]
It's not even 100 dollars, just saving 10 dollars
And they are that persuasive
(Eun Tak)
Don't give it to me, okay?
Don't give it
You can't give it, just keep giving it!
Really?
- (Grim Reaper) Change and receipt please
- (Grim Reaper) Uh
- (Grim Reaper) I will eat well
- (Grim Reaper) Oh
(Grim Reaper)
This is the missing documents you mentioned
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
You must write it by hand.
(The Grim Reaper)
[Sighing]
Yeah
[THE GRIM REAPER LAYS THE DOCUMENTS DOWN ON THE TABLE]
(Reaper)
But why do other omissions occur?
Ah, I've only heard that other omissions
exist
I've never actually dealt with it
It's like a whim of the divine
Humans call that a miracle
(The Grim Reaper)
We call that
other omissions
(Reaper)
Oh, then is your case a miracle too?
(Grim Reaper) It's a more
peculiar case; the name isn't on
either the death register
or the life register, so I don't
know on what basis to apply
it (Reaper) Just hearing about
it gives me a headache. When
will all the documents be submitted?
You're telling me
(Reaper) But, senior,
I heard you moved?
Aren't you having a housewarming party?
It's a lease [sighs]
I also have to
move, but I can't save any money
(Reaper) But the
female landlord seems
to have some supernatural abilities; she
keeps dreaming of the Grim
Reaper, it's driving me crazy.
[Heaving a sigh]
So, how many times did I tell you to pick a good spot for the house?
I really want to try living in an attic room
(Lion)
Ah, but isn’t it really strange?
I’m a Grim Reaper, but
I should have a place to live too
If I can’t sleep, I feel sleepy
and if I don’t eat, I get hungry
Ha, I’ve been working overtime these past few days
I’m so tired I could die
I’ve been carrying this around these days
[THE GRIM REAPER CHUCKLES]
Ah, right, among the 23rd generation,
there’s this really pretty girl who joined
Have you seen her...?
[The door swings open]
[A MAN’S HEAVY BREATHING]
[THE MAN BLOWS OUT AIR WITH IRRITATION]
[THE MAN’S ANNOYED BREATHING]
(Woman)
Where do you think you’re running off to after hitting a person?
(Man)
What the...? Damn
[THE WOMAN SNIFFS THE AIR]
(Woman)
[Laughing in disbelief]
Yeah, right?
You’ve been drinking, haven’t you?
[The man’s incredulous breathing]
Take it easy
(Woman)
It’s over
(Man)
Is this woman crazy? Who’s been drinking?
[Meaningful music]
Hey, as long as your limbs are intact, that's good enough
Why the hell are you acting like this, acting like this! Tsk
[tension sound effect]
(Woman)
Go to the police station, I said let's go to the police station!
- (Man) Are you not letting go?
Let go of this - (Woman) Let go?
(Man)
I said let go, this, let go!
- (Woman) Go ahead and kill me!
- (Man) Hey, are you not letting go?
(Grim Reaper) Park Young-hwan, Kim Hye-ryeong In the year of the idiot, the month of
martial arts, on the day of the pig, at 2:22 AM due to a traffic accident [Siren wails]
Is this you?
[THE GRIM REAPER FOLLOWS THE CAR CLOSELY]
(Grim Reaper) Eat, it will help you
forget the memories of the living world.
(Woman)
Really
Do I have to forget everything?
Even the resentment towards that person?
(Man)
This woman, it's all her fate
With everything dead
what are you looking at, looking at? Tsk
(Grim Reaper)
It's better to do so
Forgetting is also a divine consideration
(Man)
But why are you only giving this
to her and not to me?
You have to remember
what sin you committed
Killing someone
is not the first time
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
[CAR ENGINE SOUND]
[SOUND EFFECT OF REWINDING]
[Sobbing]
Please save me
(Grim Reaper)
At first, you'll regret this moment
when you couldn't even have a cup of tea
Next, you'll reflect on the reasons
why you couldn't have a cup of tea
And you'll realize
that no moment can be reversed
And that you are already
in hell
[SWALLOWING SALIVA]
Your whole body will be torn apart every day
Every moment writhing in pain
you will regret what you did but
That pain will never end
Forever
[SHAKY BREATH]
[THE MAN'S SHAKY BREATH]
(Man)
[stammering]
I'm sorry
Please forgive me
[A SIGH]
(Grim Reaper)
Well, you're just so neurotic
[A SOBBING BREATH]
Knowing every memory of your life
I know one person who is living in hell
He must have begged countless times
To be forgiven
(Grim Reaper)
Still, it was useless
He is still
standing in the midst of hell
[HEAVY MUSIC]
(Kim Shin)
Having left Goryeo together
Buried the hands of
the grandson of the grandson
I once thought this life was a reward
But in the end, my life was a punishment
No one's death
has been forgotten
[THE DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
[THUNDER CRASHES]
[KIM SHIN'S PAINFUL GROAN]
[THUNDER CONTINUES TO CRASH]
[ROUGH BREATHING]
[PAINFUL GROANS]
[KIM SHIN SOBS]
[A BIRD CHIRPS]
[A SIGH]
Have you been comfortable all this time?
"Yoo Geum-seon"
Are you innocent as well?
I have lived like this until now
and have not been at ease.
[KIM SHIN'S SIGH]
[CALM MUSIC]
"Quebec"
"Letter"
[A SHIP'S HORN SOUNDS FROM AFAR]
[EUN-TAK'S EXCLAMATION]
I found it
[SOFT MUSIC]
[SPARKLING SOUND EFFECTS]
[BLOWING AIR THROUGH THE MOUTH]
[THE SOUND OF A SHIP'S HORN IS HEARD FROM AFAR]
[THE BIRDS FLUTTER]
You were told to stay still, right?
I stayed still.
I didn't even know you were here.
Was this where you needed to be?
It's all over; I was about to leave.
(Eun-tak)
But uncle, you don't have an epitaph, do you?
Is it that every time I leave a place like this?
How many times?
I haven't counted.
Hello, I'm Ji Eun-tak.
(Eun-tak)
In about 200 years,
I'll be the bride for the uncle.
(Kim Shin)
No.
It seems not to be.
However, even after about 200
years, uncle, you are still cool.
(Eun-tak)
Sometimes I was a bit bad, but
I'm growing up well and properly, so
don't worry too much
Then I'll take my leave
Okay
Have you lived here for a long time?
(Kim-sin)
The cabin in the unmanned mountains
will take as long as that hotel to become
Leaving and coming back, coming back again
The first place I settled after leaving my hometown
was here, you see
(Eun-tak)
What a waste, I should have bought that cabin back then
Then that hotel would belong to you, sir
Could it be that hotel...
What does that gaze mean?
Do you want to eat this?
Where did you get this? You don't have money.
So I stole it.
(Euntak)
Hurry up and eat it, we need to get rid of it quickly.
(Kim Shin)
What?
[Euntak's laughter]
(Euntak)
[smiling]
I believe that.
No, I was just staring because it was fascinating
and it looked so pitiful that they gave it to me.
But is that hotel really yours, uncle?
Isn't it too late?
- (Euntak) Where to?
- (Kim Shin) School
What time is it in Korea now?
(Kim Shin)
10 AM
[EUNTAK'S PAINFUL MOANS]
[LIVELY MUSIC]
(Euntak)
Oh, I'm dead, from the homeroom teacher
Should I just live here?
Being an illegal resident is better than being late, right?
[CANDY CRINKLES]
I think that would be better
"Gwanghwamun"
Ah, I slept well
It feels like I woke up from a dream
I never imagined I would go on a trip abroad
(Euntak)
Thanks to that, I got to visit foreign places
and I was thankful today.
Then I'll take my leave
Since I woke up from my dream, I have to go to school now.
I'm sorry if I caused any trouble today,
please let it go just this once.
I was just really excited,
that must be why.
(Teacher)
Jin Eun-tak
What time is it? What time is it right now?
I'm sorry.
(Teacher)
You're a senior in high school.
How does a senior in high school come to school at the third period?
Do you come to school just to eat lunch?
Or do you not want to go to school?
You've submitted for early admissions,
it's the end of high school, right?
You got into college, didn't you?
You said you don't have tuition, right?
- I'm sorry
- (Teacher) Why are you late?
(Teacher)
I know you don’t have your parents and are struggling under your aunt
You're not the only one having a hard time
Everyone is struggling, everyone
It's the end of the college entrance exam season
You can't just ruin it for other kids because you won't get into college
I'm going to college
Oh my, look at that gaze
(Teacher)
Who said you can't go?
Even when you say something nice, you're like this
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING SOUND]
(Teacher)
Wait a moment
Oh, hello, Jisoo's mother?
Ah, yes, yes
[THE TEACHER'S SMILE]
Oh my, you flatter me
[THE RAIN POURS DOWN]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
(Radio DJ)
An evening after getting rained on
What becomes your umbrella?
A voice that answers when called
Memories of seeing the same thing at the same time
Moments like the first time we walked in sync
Does someone come to mind?
That's right, it's that person
I'll send you the first song now.
[THE SOUND OF THE TV IS FLOWING OUT]
(Kim Shin)
Are you busy?
Yeah, I’m busy
Then come out with me for a bit
Follow closely, but don’t stick too close
(Reaper)
As much as you follow closely
It must be something important
Otherwise, you’ll die
I’m checking that too
My life and death status
[Mysterious sound effect]
[Cheerful music]
What’s that sound?
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
Why are you coming out there?
Isn't it amazing?
The Grim Reaper just found it fascinating
That kid said it
(Grim Reaper)
What, who? Who did what?
Do it again
Get closer?
[Kim Shin's astonished moan]
[Playful music]
[Kim Shin's surprised breath]
- What are you doing?
- Why, what? It's competitive spirit
Where are you going?
I'm just cursing, go away
Go far away, far
(Kim Shin)
Get lost!
If you go in like that, what happens to me!
What is it? What can't I do?
(Dukhwa)
Tenant?
(Grim Reaper)
Oh, surprised me
(Dukhwa) Oh, our tenant,
why are you outside?
[IT'S COLD OUTSIDE, SNIFFING]
What about uncle?
- (Grim Reaper) Inside - (Dukhwa) No, no
(Dukhwa) Actually, I came to see our tenant...
Stand there (Dukhwa)
[awkwardly
laughing]
Ah, yes, you really
dislike physical contact, ah, well,
it's not very important, but is
there anything uncomfortable in your
daily life, like suddenly getting damp or something?
The outside is suddenly getting bright
(the grim reaper)
I just wish that your uncle
would suddenly just leave the house?
[snaps fingers]
Right?
Ah, actually, I also hope my uncle
can go international soon
You know, he’s actually a really big deal
and I wonder why he’s just hanging around in Korea
You can feel it, right?
- No
- You can’t feel it
(Deokhwa)
But I think I’ll be coming by often in the future
so I’m wondering
what should I call you...
If I keep saying 'tenant, tenant' it sounds too formal
Is 'uncle'
too friendly?
Hah, let me be straightforward
Uncle in the last room, please spare me just this once
If any grandfather comes by and asks
who I am
could you just say I’m here for a visit?
If he finds out that I’m
staying with uncle in the last room
I’d seriously be dead
(the grim reaper)
Who is that grandfather?
He’s my grandfather.
[SHE SMILES SLIGHTLY]
I will stand by Uncle Kkeutbang until the very end
I really will
(The Grim Reaper)
Oh dear, oh dear
Oh dear
(Deokhwa)
I really will
[The door slams shut]
[She smiles slightly]
[PLAYFUL MUSIC]
If you open this door
It's Canada
[DRAMATIC SIGH]
(Samsin)
Are you going to write, student?
(Euntak)
No, please write
(Samsin)
Are you a senior?
[Samsin creaks the faucet shut]
How do you know?
When you wear a school uniform and look dazed,
most of them are in their third year of high school.
(Euntak)
Ah, my eyes...
[EXCITING MUSIC]
(Samsin)
Where do you live?
I, uh, I live around here.
(Samsin)
That's great.
Take this and eat it.
(Euntak)
It's spinach, right?
(Samsin)
Don't feel burdened,
I got it from a guy.
Spinach?
[SHE’S MUMBLING]
(Samsin)
[Closing the lipstick]
Go home and share it with your family, okay?
(Euntak)
I’m back.
(Eun-tak Aunt)
Hey, why have you been wandering around until now?
I just got here right after school, you know
(Eun-tak Aunt)
Are you going to keep talking back to me?
(Kyung-sik)
Mom, I’m hungry
I’m hungry too, you little brat
Oh, kids from other houses
run around just fine, oh my
Hurry up and make rice
There are people waiting for you right now,
you little girl
(Eun-tak)
Yes, yes
Just answer once, okay?
(Three gods)
Go home and share it with your family, for sure
[THE DOOR SWINGS OPEN]
Mom, mom, mom, look at this
(Kyung-mi)
Looks like she's getting ready to run away overseas
I searched, and it's Canada here
What? Let me see
(Aunt Eun-tak)
Oh, I knew this girl would do something like this
[Eun-tak's urgent breathing]
Is she really planning to run off overseas with the insurance money?
You don’t even have a bank account after all this? Huh!
Please, I was just going to keep it as a memento
(Euntak Aunt) Why is this a commemoration?
What is being commemorated?
When have you ever
been to a place like this that
it's a commemoration, huh?
Yeah, you really did well today.
You repay the grace I
raised you with like this?
Like this, like this, like
this! [Euntak's pained moan]
[EUNTAK AUNT IS GRUNTING]
[BREATHLESS PANTING]
Please, it's mine so please (Euntak
Aunt) This, this is just,
this is just... [Euntak's moan]
[Euntak Aunt scolds Euntak] (Kyungmi) You're
all excited about the thought of running away.
Looking at the kimbap - (Euntak
Aunt) Where's the bank book.
.. Show it to me, huh?
- (Kyungmi) That looks
delicious (Euntak Aunt)
Where is it, you little brat, huh?
[Kyungmi's pained groan] (Euntak
[AUNT) JUST, DAMN, EXCITING MUSIC]
[TREMBLING BREATH]
(Kyungmi) Oh, blood! Ah,
blood [Kyungmi collapses weakly]
(Kyungsik) What could be delicious,
your hands? Idiot... [Kyungmi whines]
[Coughs]
(Kyungmi)
Blood!
Why are those things making a
fuss in pairs? [Kyungmi whimpers]
(Kyungmi) Ah, ah, blood
[Kyungsik's strained groan]
Mom, here, here, here, here,
[BLOOD, KYUNGSIK'S STRAINED GROAN]
[Kyungsik coughs] (Kyungmi) Ah,
[BLOOD, KYUNGMI'S WHIMPERING GROAN]
[Euntak Aunt pats Kyungsik's
back] [Kyungsik coughs]
(Kyungmi)
Blood...
(Euntak Aunt) Hey, you girl, where are
you running away to? Don't stand there!
[The door creaks open and
shut] [Kyungsik's strained groan]
[CALM MUSIC]
[SOBBING BREATH]
[SNIFFLING]
[SOBBING GROAN]
[SIGH]
[EUNTAK SNIFFLES]
She summons and follows the door in,
but I can't see black.
What on earth does that mean, you?
[Exciting music]
(Euntak)
I'm going to be a priest in 200 years.
I love you.
[LAUGHTER]
(Kim Shin)
Above all, if that statement is sincere,
that's quite awkward.
[TEETH CLATTER]
[SIGH]
Curiosity always overcomes dignity.
I'm very curious, I need to go and ask.
[KIM SHIN'S URGENT BREATHING]
Huh?
[KIM SHIN'S INCREDULOUS BREATHING]
Hey, how long has it been since you called me out
at this time of night?
(Kim Shin)
What do you expect me to do, I'm busy
with something important?
I didn’t call you.
You did.
No, really, this time it's true.
You just thought of me, didn't you?
(Euntak)
Ah, that's...
See, I was right, you were thinking of me?
Because you think of me that way,
I keep getting called out even though I'm this busy.
Ah, I'm tired.
Just thinking about you, uncle
does that summon you?
It's not exactly that
But I'm delicate and sensitive
so let's be careful with each other
Oh, I'm sorry
What was I thinking? What kind?
Well...
Canada was beautiful
[Soft music]
I would be happy living here
But still, I was happy for a moment
Thinking about that
Made me naturally think of you, uncle
The clothes look expensive
and the watch looks even more expensive
(Eun-tak)
It feels like the hotel is hers
and she has everything good
Why does she look sad?
That's what led to this thought
Well, anyway
Why are you spinning around like this?
In the middle of the night, it's suspicious
How do you know that?
I wish I didn't know anything too
Important to wait for my aunt to fall asleep
Once she falls asleep, she wouldn’t even know if I carried her
(Eun-tak)
I’m trying to sleep quickly and come out early in the morning
I usually fall asleep around 12.
So you’re going to keep hanging around here like this
until midnight?
[IN THE DISTANCE, A DOG BARKS]
(Kim Shin)
I’m walking because I can’t digest what I ate
(Eun Tak)
I know, I said it earlier
You must have eaten very well
(Kim Shin)
Don’t get me wrong
(Eun Tak)
I’ve said that three times
You can go if you want
(Kim Shin)
I’ve said that three times too
[EUN TAK’S SIGH]
[Mobile phone operation sound]
(Student 1)
Wow, I found Ji Eun Tak at her first relationship site
(Student 2)
[Playful music]
[Student 1's surprised moan]
[STUDENT 1'S PAINED MOAN]
(Student 1)
What the heck
Oh, why did you open the door?
[TENSE SOUND EFFECT]
[Choking up]
Mom
(Eun-tak)
Excuse me
[THE DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
[CHEERFUL MUSIC]
Welcome
For takeout?
Oh, I'm not a customer
I saw the sign that you're looking for a part-timer
Is the boss not here?
They're here, right here
High schooler?
( Eun-tak )
Ah, yes
Ah, you were the boss
I thought you were a customer because you're so pretty
( Sunny )
Right? The customers are pretty, tsk
But I don't remember the last time I saw a customer
[SUNNY CRUNCHES ON A SNACK]
[SUNNY RUSTLES A SNACK]
If you have any questions, feel free to ask
( Eun-tak )
By the way, I can meet all the boss's conditions
I don't have any more places to retreat to
When I was nine years old
Orphaned and without a guardian
all alone...
Ah, radish
Our house’s radish is delicious
(Sunny)
I don’t remember when the guest asked for radish
[SUNNY CRUNCHES THE SNACK]
Would you like to eat?
(Euntak)
Thank you
(Sunny)
Are you poor?
[SUNNY RUSTLES THE SNACK]
(Euntak)
Ah...
It’s somewhat like that
Don’t you go to school?
I do, I’m in my third year of high school
How nice, you’re young
- (Euntak) Huh?
- Do you have plans later?
[SUNNY CHEWS THE SNACK LOUDLY]
- (Euntak) No
- Then from today, we are together for 1 day
Work hard
Really? Wow, thank you!
I will really do my best, really really!
[EUNTAK'S JOYFUL BREATH]
[Rustling the snack]
Yeah, you do it as you like
Yes, I will do it smoothly and well
The chicken the uncle talked about is chicken
That's right, chicken is chicken
[SIGH]
But I don’t know when the customer asked for chicken.
[Cheerful music]
[Crunching on snacks]
(Euntak)
Ah, ah, hey mister, what are you doing?
Can you hear my thoughts?
What's up?
Even if I think about it, nothing comes to mind, what
[I BLOW ON MY MOUTH]
(Euntak)
I finally got a part-time job
The boss is a total beauty...
[A DOG BARKS FROM AFAR]
Oh, you only eat really expensive stuff
But they don't pay me five hundred like that
Hey, do you have any plans to call and meet up?
(Kim Shin)
As a civilized person
(Euntak)
I’m okay like this
(Kim Shin)
I’m not okay
Aren’t you thinking about me?
Even if I think about it, it doesn’t come to me, you know
Ah, I’m thinking about meeting with a promise for the future
I love you
[Sniffing the smell]
Ah, ha, the smell of steak
I’m hungry
[THE DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
[THE SOUND OF THE TV COMES OUT]
[KIM SHIN’S IRRITATED MOAN]
[THE DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
[MAGNIFICENT MUSIC]
[EXHALES]
(Death Angel)
Mom
This outfit is better, right?
(Grim Reaper) What clothes?
The clothes I wore earlier, honestly
[Playful music]
[The Grim Reaper's sigh]
(The Grim Reaper)
Did you
change clothes?
(Kim Shin)
Oh, then do these clothes and this book match?
It seems like I'm going to keep singing
I want to look intellectual and flawless
(The Grim Reaper)
For whom?
(Kim Shin)
Oh, please focus a little!
Think of it as the clothes I'll wear when I leave this house, then it will be easy
(The Grim Reaper)
Awesome, just dazzling.
The best
(Kim Shin)
So, this isn’t the right outfit.
Which is better, this LP or this CD?
It’s a setting that listens to everything from classical to K-pop
without prejudice.
These days, kids just listen to files.
(Kim Shin)
Hey, is this painting better, or is this painting better?
(Grim Reaper)
Just leave.
(Kim Shin)
It’s a setting that encompasses post-modernism
and impressionism.
[A BREATH OF SURPRISE]
Do you sleep like this?
[Majestic music]
(Grim Reaper)
Why? I have to sleep like this to be comfortable.
(Kim Shin)
Don't do it
[The Grim Reaper's sigh]
Is this a room? It's a morgue
Do we not need a wreath?
[SOBBING]
[Sobbing]
Just sleep a little
[A SIGH]
I will break it
[KIM SHIN HUMS]
[LAUGHTER]
[TAKES A DEEP BREATH]
[KIM SHIN’S SATISFIED MOAN]
[KIM SHIN HUMS]
What are you doing?
(Grim Reaper)
The laundry is all dry
(Kim Shin)
Do your best
(Grim Reaper)
♪ Goblin's pants are sturdy ♪
♪ It's tough and sturdy ♪
(Gim Shin)
Don't do it
(The Grim Reaper)
Oh, this was your song? I didn't know,
No wonder I was really absorbed in it
[Playful music]
(The Grim Reaper)
♪ The goblin's underwear is dirty ♪
♪ It smells and it's filthy ♪
I warned you
What on earth did you do to your underwear
No way
(The Grim Reaper)
Sigh, if this is something that remains as a song...
It's not true
What could you possibly do to your underwear
that it becomes a song?
[Kim Shin stomps his foot]
Very
[KIM SHIN'S SURPRISED BREATH]
Was it manly?
Don't do it!
[KIM SHIN'S SIGH]
[THUNDER CRASHES LOUDLY]
(News anchor)
In the Seongbuk-dong area, an unexpected
downpour accompanied by thunder and lightning fell
Citizens experienced inconvenience
(Deokhwa)
Is everything okay, uncle?
They say an unexpected downpour, you know
Only fell in Seongbuk-dong
(Deokhwa)
No, uncle, why are you all crumpled up?
[KIM SHIN'S SIGH]
Deokhwa.
(Duk-hwa)
Uh, tell me, is there something bad going on?
To talk about something bad
I have something to say to you before that
It's about your family's secrets and
my tragic fate
Don't be surprised
The truth is...
(Duk-hwa)
A goblin?
Is that what you're talking about?
When did you find out?
Well, I found out when I was eight
Actually, I had some doubts since I was six
[SPARKLING SOUND EFFECT]
[Funny Music] (Deokhwa)
Whenever uncle gets
drunk, he would say 'Gold, come out, bang'
and brag about gold to me
like that, don’t you remember?
(Young Deokhwa) Wow,
are you giving this to me?
(Kim Shin) No [Young Deokhwa's
astonished breath]
[Kim Shin's laughter]
(Young Deokhwa) So annoying
(Deokhwa) At that
moment, I was sure
he wasn’t a real
uncle [Mysterious
sound effect] Hmm,
even now, look,
it’s always like this, how
could I not know? Be careful.
The uncle who leaks at home I'm really
worried that he might not leak outside.
(Shin Kim) So you
knew I was a goblin, huh?
Since I was six years old, all along
(Deokhwa)
Oh
But still, you called me
'Oh'
(Kim Shin)
Since I was six years old, all along
(Deokhwa)
Oh
No
[THUNDER IS RUMBLING]
(News anchor)
Today, localized heavy rain accompanied by thunderstorms
Were you surprised?
The Seoul Meteorological Administration has issued
[The sky is rumbling]
A heavy rain advisory for some areas of Seoul and Gyeonggi Province
The roads are getting slippery, raising concerns about traffic congestion on the way home.
This is reporter Lee Min-soo.
(Reporter in the news)
In the Seongbuk-dong area,
heavy rain that is greater than during the day has poured down
Citizens on their way home have been stranded
A police official said
to minimize traffic chaos
[Crushing snacks]
that they hope people will use public transportation as much as possible
[SUNNY'S SIGH]
It's raining
That's good
What's so good about it?
When it rains, there are no customers
Even if it doesn't rain, there are no customers
Anyway, if they aren't coming, it's better that it rains
I don't have an umbrella.
I have a lot, take one.
I didn't take it because it's a
hassle every day.
Since it's a hassle, don't
bring it back. Really?
I got an umbrella.
Is this your first time
seeing an umbrella?
Thank you. Oh my, in my life I
should have an umbrella too, tsk.
[Chewing on
snacks] Ah, it's soggy.
(Euntak) Should I
give you a new one?
(Sunny) No thanks,
I know this flavor.
It's a hassle to chew on a
new one. Where are you going?
That kind of line
is for the boss only.
You, the part-timer, can slack off
and have fun when I'm not around.
Hey, what to do if the boss isn't here
and the part-timer skips work?
You should work harder when they're not around
(Sunny)
If you work harder when they're not around
the boss won't know, part-timer
Just play
Oh man, that's cool
[The door opens and closes with a click]
Take care
(Sunny)
Huh?
(Fortune-teller)
Ah, triplets
I'm the youngest
[THE FORTUNE-TELLER SMILES SLIGHTLY]
Let's see, let's see
What brought you here?
Isn't that something you need to guess?
What isn't going well?
(Sunny)
If things were going well, I wouldn't be here
I’d be sitting in the store counting money
[EXCITING MUSIC]
(Fortune-teller)
Oh dear, for your fortune
you have no luck with kids at all
With misfortune and bad luck, sigh
So every kind of trouble has come my way
even the trouble of aging
I need to lose weight, right?
Yikes, this fate is really cold
An orphan all alone in this world
How can that not change?
A life like a small sailing boat adrift
in the vast ocean.
I wish there was a handsome man on that boat
Oh, I see him, the man
Be careful of the man with the hat, the pitch-black hat
I hope that man with the hat is handsome
(Kim Shin)
Where are you going?
(The Grim Reaper)
The laundromat
It's dry cleaning only, this is
I feel this every time
That hat is really a great concept
Making the dead look silly on their last journey
[SIGH]
'Do not seek death
for death will seek you'
It's based on that item
You have to write this for the deceased to recognize.
It's not visible to the eyes of humans.
(Kim Shin)
Oh, it's a relief that it's not visible to human eyes.
It would be so embarrassing.
Have a good trip.
[LIVELY MUSIC]
[A BREATH MIXED WITH IRRITATION]
Don’t you have to iron it?
When are you from?
These days, it sticks well just like this.
And you,
who coats the leaves these days?
It's fine since the person receiving this is a bit older.
(Jung Hyun)
Who? Did you get a boyfriend?
Hey!
What about my boyfriend?
I'm just grateful because he helped me find a part-time job.
But what if he misunderstands this?
Saying I like him
He’s someone who denies my very existence
I guess he wouldn’t think that way
[HE BLOWS HOT AIR]
Mister, I brought you a gift...
[TENSE MUSIC]
(Euntak)
Ah, I left my scarf, my scarf
(Reaper)
As expected
You can see me
Even 10 years ago, and now
The lines are the same
What if the boss locked the door?
(Euntak)
Ah, fool
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
(Grim Reaper)
It's useless, I know everything that's visible
Now there's no one left to protect you
[SIGH]
I know I've been caught too
(Grim Reaper)
You moved, right?
Thanks to that, I've been looking for you for 10 years
and today I finally see you
Then why not just stop looking?
(Euntak)
At this point, in the living world
they would call me a stalker, you know?
I'm going to sue!
My name isn't even on the list
But I'm on the list of other omissions.
(Grim Reaper)
It must be a headache due to the 19 years' worth of evidence documents
Then
What happens to me now?
Am I going to die?
(Euntak)
I'm only nineteen now?
You can die at nine and ten
[HEAVY MUSIC]
That's death
(Grim Reaper)
But
This time, who are you with, anyway?
[EUNTAK'S SURPRISED BREATH]
(Euntak)
Close your eyes, we can't make eye contact.
[In a small voice]
That person is a grim reaper.
(Euntak)
No, we can't make eye contact.
It's okay, we know each other.
(Kim Shin)
Are you working?
(Grim Reaper)
I am, but I don't know what you're doing.
I'm involved in the life and death of humans.
(Grim Reaper)
So it seems like you're making a big mistake.
This child has already been...
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
Do I look like I want to hear an explanation?
[TENSE MUSIC]
(Kim Shin)
When the goblin is serious,
didn't you learn not to listen carelessly?
Be careful, because I might want to get involved
even in your life and death
For now, run away
If you run, there's a way, this way
It's okay, just stay
because I can't take you away
Just a while ago, you said you
were looking for me for 10 years...
Still
Even if I had been looking for you for 100 years, still
No lion can take away
a girl who wants to marry a goblin
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
Right in front of the goblin
(Grim Reaper)
Oh, then could it be that guy...
Yes, that's right, that's me
The goblin bride with a lot of rumors
(Eun-tak)
So what are you going to do now?
Are you still going to take me away?
[THE SIREN WAILS]
Given the atmosphere
it seems I'm the bad guy
I'm in a hurry too, so
let's talk in detail later
We'll meet again
(Grim Reaper)
Coincidences like today are nice
or feel free to make a plan with me
[A SIGH OF RELIEF]
Speak
You have so much to say on your face
See
You're a goblin, right?
I knew it
But why did you lie and say you’re not a goblin?
At first, I didn't think I would see you again
[CALM MUSIC]
(Kim Shin)
Did you think you would come in?
Into my door, where no one has ever
followed me in before
And then what?
I asked several times after that
Then there was no need to correct it.
(Kim Shin)
From the beginning until now
Maybe in the future you
are not a goblin bride
Then what am I
? What is this?
The ghosts every day
keep talking about that 'goblin'
and come to talk to me
If I don't see them, they bother me
and if I do see them, they cling to me
I'm living like this
but the afterlife agents
say I shouldn't be alive
So what am I
? I told you, it's something you have to bear
It doesn't seem like something you should argue with me about
Ha, that's petty.
[Sniffling]
It's so pathetic
[I AM SOBBING]
What? If I met a goblin
Would I really be trying to get married?
(Euntak)
Honestly, tell me, is there another reason?
Is it because I'm not pretty
That you said I'm not a goblin?
That I'm too far from your ideal type?
[Kim Shin's absurd breath]
That's right!
- No
- (Euntak) What? You always say no!
(Euntak)
You said I wasn't a goblin, but you were right
You're pretty
[SURPRISED BREATH]
I've lived for over 900 years.
I'm not looking for a pretty person.
I'm looking for someone who can discover something
in me.
(Kim Shin)
That's why
you, who can't discover anything,
are not the goblin bride
That's just how it is.
The fact that you have no utility value
is also what it means.
[SIGH]
It's so sharp that it hurts.
There's nothing to be hurt by.
Rather, consider it a blessing.
(Kim Shin)
If you had discovered something in me,
You must have really blamed me a lot
Then why do you say you're not a goblin until the end?
Why are you bringing it up now?
For the same reason you said it wasn't true
(Kim Shin)
Don't call me out with pointless false hopes
I'm about to leave here soon
Where to?
No, don't answer that
[I’M SNIFFLING]
Not curious at all
Who says you're an uncle priest?
Did I go mad at the beautiful age of nineteen?
I won't call you out again
So live with a peaceful mind.
I don't need an uncle either.
Just thinking, 'Oh, so that's what a goblin looks like'
[SNIFF]
(grim reaper)
Are you finally dying?
Rumor has it that when a bride appears
you die.
Unfortunately, you can't die
he can't see the sword.
Well, he might still not be able to see it.
Sigh, or maybe you have to be completely naked to see it.
(grim reaper)
The kid is still young.
Since the kid is still young, don't even think about it.
(grim reaper)
Why are you protecting him? You said he can't even see the sword.
Just congratulations
Because you've lived longer
Go live long somewhere else
(Grim Reaper)
I can't live with a goblin that interferes with my life and death
There's a very easy way for you to leave
The exit is over there
[SIGH]
[THE DOOR CLOSES WITH A CLICK]
[KIM SHIN'S SIGH]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
(Kid)
Why is my older sister, who's all grown up, watching something like this?
It's like investigating a boyfriend
It's similar to checking Facebook.
When you grow up later,
you have to try all these things, got it?
Does your sister's boyfriend appear in a fairy tale?
Is he a prince?
Yeah, if he's going to appear in a fairy tale,
it would be great if he were a prince on a white horse.
(Eun-tak)
What is this, this?
This is more fun, look at this.
Thank you.
(Eun-tak)
What happens next?
I asked several times about what comes next.
There was no need to correct anything after that.
(Kim Shin)
From the beginning until now,
you probably will in the future.
It's not the goblin bride.
Seriously, I was just a broom.
I won't do it; I will get rid of it too.
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
[EUNTAK'S SIGH]
[A BIRD CHIRPS]
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC]
(Kim Shin)
Deokhwa, you!
[DEOKHWA'S SURPRISED BREATH]
Uncle, were you there?
(Deokhwa)
Oh, uncle also smoked and quit, right?
What year are you talking about?
It was 350 years ago, 350 years.
(Deokhwa)
Wow.
Sorry.
[A SIGH]
(The Grim Reaper)
Why is he like that?
[A SIGH]
(Dukhwa)
It's been three hours, it's so humid I'm about to lose my mind...
[SIGH]
Why is Uncle in the last room like that, seriously
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
[IT RUMBLES]
[THE GRIM REAPER'S COUGH]
(Grim Reaper)
Is this a cumulus cloud?
I rushed here to ask that
What?
[A DEEP SIGH]
[IT RUMBLES]
Uncle
It can't rain
Ah, who’s going to clean that up?
(Grim Reaper)
Tsk, just looking at it, you have the face of someone thinking about a woman.
It's been almost 300
years I talked to a
woman for more than three sentences, and
what kind of face hurts a
woman? What? Where?
(The Grim Reaper) The conclusion
of the couple's fight Doesn't
seem to have ended well 'See
you in 4 weeks' Is that how it is?
(Deokhwa) Wow, amazing, uncle,
do you have a girlfriend? Is she pretty?
(The Grim Reaper) She's nineteen
(Deokhwa) Wow,
amazing, is she pretty?
I wasn't thinking about her I was
thinking about stock trends (Kim
Shin) The Grim Reaper says all
sorts of things in front of the kid
[Suspenseful music]
I hope you don't underestimate the reaper's foresight
(Reaper)
A goblin thinking about a woman in front of a child
[SIGH]
Why?
What?
What, as long as you weren't aware, it's fine
(Deokhwa)
No, but
If you hurt someone, you should say 'I hurt you, I'm sorry'
You can just sincerely apologize like a man
Why are you doing this
(Kim Shin)
Deokhwa, you're still young
You don't know what you're doing
- It's noisy
- I said it quietly
Ah, this conversation is pathetic
(Deokhwa)
Uncle from the end room understands
He's an uncle who's embarrassing no matter where you put him
So I'm really sorry
Ah, just apologize, like a man, okay?
Like a man, just do it firmly, ring firmly, bag firmly, card
[CLICKS HIS TONGUE]
[RUMBLES]
[STRAINED GROAN]
- (Reaper) Where are you going?
- Supermarket, and you?
Laundry, I often
Only dry cleaning here
- I'll go ahead
- (Kim Shin) Take care
[THE DOOR SWINGS OPEN]
(Grim Reaper)
You said you were going to the supermarket?
Is this the supermarket?
(Kim Shin)
You said you were going to the laundromat, is this the laundromat?
So you followed me? There's no kid
None? Did you kill him?
[ABSURD BREATHING SOUNDS]
[FUNNY MUSIC]
That's a really rude expression
Careless goblin
It's even ruder to enter someone else's house with shoes on
(Kim Shin)
Inconsiderate Grim Reaper
- What happened to the kid?
- Didn't you kill him?
[SIGH]
Did you tell him to move?
I came to tell you to move
but you moved on your own
(Reaper)
Do you think I wouldn't be able to find you because you moved?
Yeah, you couldn't find me for 10 years
(Kim Shin)
From what I see, even if he didn't move,
you wouldn't find him anyway?
(Reaper)
So where did you move to?
You know, right? Where is it?
[SIGH]
It's okay
Well, I was just sleeping anyway
It wasn't really our home
[SIGH]
[EXCITING MUSIC]
(Eun Tak)
Excuse me
There's no one here
There isn't any
[The stone is rolling along]
[A surprised groan]
(Ghost 1)
Hey
You can see me, right?
Yes, I can see you!
(Euntak)
I can see everything clearly
Let's talk about us
Huh?
Where did you go?
(Ghost 1)
Hey
[Stammering]
You're scary
Why are you acting like this all of a sudden?
Last time, you told me
I was a goblin bride
Why did you say that?
Oh, that?
I heard it from a grandma who speaks in dialect?
(Ghost 2)
From what I see, you
Just looking at your face, I
saved you, your mom, right?
The appearance was good, right?
Like this. The
breath that had been
stumbling came back all
at once. [Mysterious music]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[SOFT MOANS]
(Ghost 2) It's midwinter,
and the cherry blossoms, huh?
The cherry blossoms
are falling down slowly.
Wasn't it so amazing that the
goblin saved me and my mom?
(Ghost 2) Uh, I don’t
know, but you and your
mom were probably
destined to die that day.
A little later, the grim reaper
came looking for that spot
He left empty-handed
[Ghost 2's laughter]
(Ghost 1)
So, in the end, he saved his bride
Ah! How romantic
[Ghost 1's laughter]
(Ghost 2)
Yeah, that's right
What that man said was all true
I had no right to hate from the start
If it weren't for the goblin
I wouldn't have been born
Then I wouldn't have memories of living with my mom
until I was nine
(Ghost 1)
Did you get mad? At the goblin?
Severely?
What should I do now?
(Ghost 1)
Well, in that case
Do you want to follow me?
[GHOST 1’S GROAN]
(Ghost 2)
What should I do? I have to marry the goblin
[OMINOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
(Ghost 2)
A bit...
[GHOST 2'S ANNOYED GROAN]
[GHOST 2'S SIGH]
[HEAVY MUSIC]
[A SNORT]
Excuse me
(Aunt Euntak)
There's a girl named Euntak working here...
[SHIMMERING SOUND EFFECTS]
Oh my, you scared me
Welcome, please take a seat comfortably
(Aunt Euntak)
No, I'm not a guest
Tell the boss to come out, not the young lady
Hurry, it’s urgent
Please speak, quickly
This young lady is the boss here
Oh, the young lady is the boss here?
(Aunt Euntak)
Ah, I’m Euntak's aunt
Hey, you
Who gave you permission
to make someone else's precious niece
work in a place like this?
She didn’t look precious
- (Aunt Euntak) What is it?
- Do you know the phrase "sako mutak"?
That’s her.
What are you talking about? What is this탁?
(Aunt Euntak)
That's Ji Euntak, right? Is she that person?
It's okay
I didn't know either, so I searched online
(Aunt Euntak)
No, but this woman
Why are you speaking informally all of a sudden?
Isn’t that right?
I also hate people who order half a chicken
It's one whole chicken, right?
No, I mean, what kind of crazy thing is this...
(Sunny)
But, Aunt Euntak
Your precious niece
should be in school right now?
Why are you here doing this?
(Aunt Euntak)
Ah, I've tried several times at school
There are a lot of people, that's why I'm here
so please cooperate
I mean, I'm worried because the kid left home
(Aunt Euntak)
Hey! If the kid goes off the rails, are you going to take responsibility?
[Mobile phone manipulation sound]
It's probably there without being noticeable, so don't worry about it
(Sunny)
Um, big brother, it's been a while
I'm doing okay, more or less
Well, there's a lady who
[Smiling slightly] Does my beautiful appearance
know that my heart is also lovely? Aside
from making me extremely displeased, it's not
bad at all. [Euntak aunt is crunching on snacks]
(Euntak aunt)
That over there, Lee
(Sunny) Hey, are
you still hitting people?
Do you feel no guilt
even when hitting women?
Gender equality?
So, you shouldn't
live like that, right?
You say you're coming now?
Oh, what's your address...
(Euntak aunt) Ah, I'm going, I'm
going I'm actually
on my way now,
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going right now.
(Sunny's friend)
What are you talking about? What are you doing?
[The door swings open and shut]
Your dialect is totally awful
I know
I know, but I at least tried this
Are you doing well? Let's hang up
[Phone operation sounds]
[Tosses the phone down]
[SIGH]
[CHEWS ON SNACKS LOUDLY]
(Euntak's aunt)
Oh, I'm really seeing some crazy girls, seriously
Anyway, this girl
Just wait until she gets caught, really, just
(Euntak's aunt)
Oh, why come all the way to my house?
I was just about to call...
(Loan shark 1)
Hey, hey, huh?
The person who borrowed the money lives more comfortably than the person who lent it
What, did I come all the way to your house because I'm having extra oil to spare?
Oh, once I find the bankbook
I’ll pay it back right away
Oh, this girl ran away from home and
I'm really in trouble now!
(Loan shark 1)
I
The lady isn’t answering my calls, so
I’m really in trouble right now
I even brought the car with me
Let's go see some scenic hills together, ma'am.
[Stuttering]
What will happen to me
if you can't even get that money?
I'm the legal guardian right here!
[LOAN SHARK 1'S LAUGHTER]
(Loan shark 1)
Oh my, huh?
This ma'am just
has her mouth alive
[Slapping Euntak aunt's mouth]
just has her mouth alive
How many months has it been since you started talking about that insurance money?
Is there really insurance money?
(Euntak aunt)
There is, I tell you.
Her mom acts like she knows the day she's going to die.
She put into fetal insurance and her life insurance too.
She’s been pouring in for a full 8 years.
It came out to about 150 million won.
(Aunt Euntaek)
But this bankbook keeps disappearing.
Even when I get it reissued, it keeps disappearing,
I’m gonna lose my mind...
It's true.
It's in that girl's hands.
[Tapping Loan Shark 1]
I'm sure.
What school did she say she attends?
"Jungang High School"
[VIBRATION SOUND OF A MOBILE PHONE]
(Gyeongmi)
Hey, I just need 30,000 won, I’m in a hurry
I’ll pay you back next week, just reply
[MOBILE PHONE VIBRATING SOUND]
[TENSION-FILLED MUSIC]
(Loan Shark 2)
Student
Where are you going, huh?
(Euntak)
Who are you?
(Loan Shark 1)
What will happen if the student leaves the house?
Dangerous, huh?
(Euntak)
No, um, why are you doing this?
[The car door slams shut]
No, um, um, why are you doing this?
[Euntak's scream]
(Loan Shark 1)
Your aunt is really worried, get in quickly!
(Kim Shin)
I have something I'm curious about
If this house is 20 years of rent, that's no small amount of money
Where did that huge sum come from?
[EXCITING MUSIC]
The deceased offer
the funeral money on the coffin or the ritual table
So that the dead person can pay the fare to cross the river into the afterlife
I’ve been saving that for 300 years
[Kim Shin's exclamation]
So do you think I could give up this house?
Wow, I haven't heard the expression about saving money in a long time
I have a lot of gold and a lot of money, so
Don't you need pepper?
Why don't you learn anything?
[SIGH]
[THE PLATE SHATTERS]
[KIM-SHIN'S LAUGHTER]
That was a plate from the time of Louis XIV.
[LAUGHTER]
(Loan shark 1)
Damn it.
[HE SLASHES THE BAG WITH A KNIFE]
[TENSE MUSIC]
[EUN-TAK BLOWS AIR THROUGH HER LIPS]
- (Loan shark 2) Damn it.
- (Loan shark 1) Seriously, damn, huh?
[Tire screeching sound]
(Loan shark 2)
Whoa, damn, oh my, damn.
[Tire screeching sound]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
Put down the fork.
Put down your knife;
[THE THINGS ARE RATTLING]
(Eun-tak) [sniffling]
I really don’t know;
I genuinely don’t
have a bank account.
It’s with my aunt. (Loan
shark 1) Yeah, your aunt
says she has it, And
you say it’s with your
aunt, so, ah, then one of
you must be lying, right?
I'm really about to die, damn it.
[Eun-tak's frightened whimper]
[significant music]
[significant sound effect]
What is this?
Let’s do this properly; is this it?
(Loan shark 1) Damn it.
[Heavy music]
[Euntak's frightened breathing]
(Loan shark 1)
Student, we're in a hurry
Do you know where this car is headed?
When a female student goes to such a
remote place,
you must have seen a lot on TV
about what can happen, right?
[Euntak's pained groan]
Did you hide the bankbook? Did you hide the bankbook?
(Euntak)
I really don't know
Why are you blaming me for my aunt's debt?
- (Loan shark 1) Huh?
- (Euntak) Please let me go
If you don't let me go, I'm going to report you!
(Loan shark 1)
Report? You little bitch
I’m going to report you right now
Just this...
[Tire screeching sound]
[LOAN SHARK 1'S SURPRISED GROAN]
(Loan shark 1)
Hey, you bastard
Are you not driving properly?
- (Loan shark 2) Bro
- (Loan shark 1) Huh?
(Loan shark 2)
Over there
[Streetlights flicker off]
(Loan shark 1)
Huh?
[THE STREETLIGHT EXPLODES]
[TENSE SOUND EFFECT]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
[THE SOUND OF FOOTSTEPS ECHOES]
(Euntak)
Thank you for saving me, sir
Please let the Grim Reaper know as well
(Euntak)
So what exactly am I supposed to see?
(Kim Shin)
I don’t know where it is, don’t call me
[The Grim Reaper's sigh]
I can’t find it because you’re not calling
(Kim Shin)
I guess I was thinking about you, wait a minute
- Just promise me one thing
- What promise?
"Ji Euntak"
(Kim Shin)
If I leave, don’t touch that child
A goodbye wish to take care
I'm leaving tomorrow
Subtitles: Choi Hye-ran