[THEME SONG]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[Heavy music]
[A sword is swiftly drawn]
[SHARP SOUND EFFECTS]
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECTS]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[SHARP SOUND EFFECTS]
[TREMBLING BREATH]
Please forgive me
[SOBBING]
Dying gloriously
Only now do I inform you
[EUNTAK'S SURPRISED BREATH]
(Euntak)
No!
No
[Sorrowful music]
[Euntak is sobbing]
[EUNTAK CONTINUES TO SOB]
No, no
No
[EUNTAK CONTINUES TO SOB]
[KIM SHIN'S SHALLOW BREATH]
[KIM SHIN'S LABORED BREATH]
[EUNTAK'S TREMBLING BREATH]
[EUNTAK CONTINUES TO SOB]
[KIM SHIN'S LABORED BREATH]
(Kim Shin)
Meeting you was
my life
I don't want to
Please
[TREMBLING BREATH]
You said you wouldn't let go of my hand
You promised
I'll come when it rains
I'll come with the first snow
Please let me do just that
I'll pray to God
[Weeping]
Don't do that
Don't go like that!
(Euntak)
I love you
Uncle, I love you
Me too
I love you
That much
I've already done it
[EUNTAK'S TREMBLING BREATH]
[EUNTAK SOBS]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[EUNTAK CHOKES UP]
[SAD MUSIC]
[EUNTAK WAILS]
(Euntak)
[Weeping]
No
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
[SIGNIFICANT MUSIC]
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECTS]
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
[SOBBING]
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECTS]
[A GASP OF SURPRISE]
[FOOTSTEPS ECHO]
[TENSE MUSIC]
[SHAKING BREATH]
Remember
(Euntak)
You have to remember
[Sobbing]
That person's name is
Kim Shin.
Tall
(Euntak)
Sad when smiling.
[TREMBLING BREATH]
It will rain.
It will come with
the first snow.
I will keep the promise.
Remember.
You have to remember.
(Euntak)
You are
that person's
bride.
[CRYING]
[GRAND MUSIC]
[IT RESOUNDS]
(Samsin)
The god said
(God)
You have been erased
from the memories of all those who know you.
That is their peace
and
my consideration.
(Samsin)
And
your punishment is over.
Now forget everything and sleep,
be at peace.
But
in the goblin's eyes,
tears welled up.
(Kim Shin)
Now I understand
What choice I make
In the end, I
Made that choice
(Kim Shin)
Here
[THE MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
I will remain
Staying here
I will become rain
I will become wind
I will become the first snow
[MUSIC THAT RAISES THE ATMOSPHERE]
Just that one thing
I seek permission from the heavens
(Samshin)
It couldn't have been a foolish choice
(Shin)
I was always with you in your life.
Now, there is no one here
Not even me
[A SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
(Samshin)
Alone like this, the goblin
In the space between death and life
Between light and darkness
In that place where even the gods have left
It got trapped in eternal immortality
Ah, what to do
So?
What happened to the goblin?
Well
Memories will soon be forgotten
Only splendid emptiness will remain
(Samshin)
In that emptiness
It will walk and walk
[The wind blows fiercely]
(Samshin)
Walking like that
What will happen?
Where will it reach?
[WOOSIK'S SIGH]
That's a very sad story.
[WOOSIK SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(Woosik)
How much is this?
[HEAVY MUSIC]
[THE WIND BLOWS FIERCELY]
(Radio host)
Ah, ah, a reasonable weekend
[CLEARS THE THROAT]
Have a reasonable weekend
(Staff 1)
10 minutes before the broadcast
- (Staff 2) PD, over here
- (Euntak) Uh
[EUNTAK CRUMPLES THE PAPER]
- (Writer) Director Ji
- (Euntak) Yeah
It's raining, and it's getting heavier?
(Writer)
Isn't this Southeast Asia?
What's the weather forecast?
Did they say today would be perfectly sunny?
Right, and I don't even have an umbrella
(Writer)
Is the umbrella the problem right now? What about the opening?
What about it?
I can't just stop the rain
Then I'll just have to rewrite it
(Euntak)
Today, just write about it being a clear day, keep it
For now, the first song is fine
The gloomier the day, the brighter the feeling to start with.
Only comments that don't match the weather and issues...
[The writer swiftly taps the keyboard]
I'm rewriting
(Writer)
Oh, my fate
(Staff 1)
It's 8 minutes before live broadcast
[CELL PHONE VIBRATION SOUND]
(Kyung-mi)
Just 300,000 won, it’s urgent, reply
I'm going to choose the music
(Writer)
Okay
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
(Young Euntak)
Mister, who are you?
[Tension-inducing sound effect]
Did I see it wrong?
Well
It was 20 years ago
Is it mom's belongings?
Since when has it been here?
This necklace is
[SOFT MUSIC]
[DREAMY MUSIC]
(Kim Shin)
'In that desert, he was so lonely'
'Sometimes he walked backward'
'To see the footprints printed in front of him'
[EUNTAK RUSTLES THE PAGES OF A BOOK]
[HEAVY MUSIC]
(Euntak)
How
did it only burn right here?
(Sunny)
Welcome
[SPARKLING SOUND EFFECTS]
The boss is really consistently pretty
Please give me soju
[EUNTAK'S TIRED BREATHING]
(Sunny)
The broadcast was good today, why?
Did the CP have another fit?
What good is it if it’s good?
We’re at risk of getting cut since no ads are coming in
Suddenly it started raining and put on a show
Ah, the side dishes are half and half
Half and half!
Take out the soju
(Euntak)
Um, for the guests
[YOONA’S SIGH]
(Euntak)
Uh, class president, over there
(Sunny)
How long are you going to be class president?
What, are you going to keep being class president?
Kim Byeon, welcome
The side dishes were ordered by the PD
(Yoona)
Yes
I want beer
[YOONA'S SIGH]
(Euntak)
Did you win the lawsuit?
(YoonA)
If I lost, I wouldn't have been able to leave work.
Do you want to go on a blind date?
I don't like lawyers.
This time it's a chef.
(YoonA)
He appears often on cooking channels.
He looks like a puppy when he smiles, so cute.
Why should I care about your taste?
Why should I be a fan of your show?
(YoonA)
He always plays your show during his lunch at his store.
Aren't I the only friend you have to sell?
[I CHUCKLE]
(Sunny)
When you sell me, I get sold, sigh.
Look at me, being someone’s first love
was
the easiest thing in the world for me, but
how come there isn't even one
guy who
[CASUALLY ASKS FOR A CUP OF COFFEE? THE RAIN POURS DOWN]
(Yoona) Yeah, let’s not let it go this way
(Sunny) Kim Byun, what does that mean?
(Yoona) It was appropriate to
help Ji Eun-tak understand, but why?
(Sunny) PD Ji, do you only
have stories about friends?
(Yoona)
Is this the only place to drink?
[EUN-TAK POURS THE DRINK]
[YOONA SIGHS]
[YOONA EXHALES]
[EXHALES]
(Euntak)
It's raining and the alcohol is bitter
I have two friends who worry about me
[I SMILE FAINTLY]
[EUNTAK POURS THE ALCOHOL QUIETLY]
The weather is really nice
[TENSE SOUND EFFECTS]
(Ghost 1)
They say she's a goblin bride
But why can't we see her?
(Ghost 2)
She was a goblin bride back in the day
But she's twenty-nine
And if a goblin hasn't shown up yet
She's actually no different from a widow
(Ghost 2)
But she used to see me back then
[EUNTAK SOBS]
[EUNTAK'S PAINFUL GROAN]
[Sobbing]
Why am I like this?
What's so sad?
[TREMBLING BREATH]
Why do I keep doing this
[EUNTAK CONTINUES TO SOB]
[EUNTAK'S CRYING]
[HEAVY MUSIC]
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECTS]
[THE SKY RUMBLES]
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
(Man 1)
Wow, it's the first snow?
(Woman 1)
[Surprised]
I know
It's a bit early this year, isn't it?
(Man 1)
But it's nice that it's the first snow, right?
(Girl 1)
Yeah
[Guy 1 smiles slightly]
[HEAVY MUSIC]
(Euntak)
What have I forgotten?
Who
have I forgotten?
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECTS]
(Euntak)
What face have I forgotten
What promise have I forgotten
Is it only this deep, unknown sadness that remains?
(Euntak)
Can someone
Anyone, please, help me...
Save me
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
[BLOWING AIR THROUGH MY LIPS]
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECTS]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[SAD MUSIC]
Me?
(Kim Shin)
Oh, you
Is that you?
(Eun Tak)
[Sobbing]
Don't do that
Don't do that, don't go like this!
[EUN TAK SOBS]
(Eun Tak)
Uncle, I love you, I love you
[GASPING BREATHS]
[SOBBING]
[SOBBING TOGETHER]
[SURPRISED BREATH]
(Eun Tak)
Ah, I'm sorry
I have a bit of emotional ups and downs
I'm sorry...
What am I doing right now?
[Absurd breath]
[Sniff]
Ah, why should I apologize?
[EUNTAK'S SIGH]
What are you doing right now?
Why did you hug me?
Do you know me? Who are you?
Eul
Eul?
Are you perhaps an actor?
- (Euntak) Is the drama department...
- (Kim Sin) Did you achieve your dream?
What do you mean?
In the midst of that, it's admirable
[ABSURD BREATH]
Yes, well, thank you
But why didn’t you hug me earlier?
Then why are you still
using informal language?
(Shin)
You have been erased
from the memories of everyone who knows you
That is their peace
And my consideration
[HEAVY MUSIC]
It was enough to be at peace
That was sufficient
Is it an act, or what?
[A SIGH]
The drama department is not in this building
You need to go to the annex behind
[SOFT MUSIC]
But how did you get in here?
Without an access pass
Someone called me
(Eun-tak)
Ah...
[THE DOOR CLOSES SHARPLY]
(Secretary Kim)
Deok-hwa.
(Dukhwa)
Go ahead and speak.
(Secretary Kim)
I am the president.
Dukhwa is the team leader of the subsidiary.
Let's return to our positions.
[DUKHWA'S AWKWARD SMILE]
(Dukhwa)
I thought it was natural.
(Kimshin)
Dukhwa.
(Guard)
You cannot enter.
I'm sorry.
(Dukhwa)
That person just called me, right?
'Dukhwa.'
- (Kimshin) Dukhwa.
- (Guard) Please leave, quickly.
(Secretary Kim)
Let it be.
Let's listen to the story.
(Kim Shin)
I thought I would never see you again
It’s nice to see you like this
(Deokhwa)
Please say that over there, over there
Who are you? Do you know me?
[SIGH]
I was your uncle and then
your brother...
Aren't you crazy?
I'm not crazy
(Deokhwa)
Ha, I'm hungry, let's go, what would you like to eat?
I've made a reservation at a place Deokhwa likes
(Kim Shin)
Deokhwa
[SIGH]
Something feels off
(Deokhwa)
Earlier you clearly said 'uncle'
[SECRETARY KIM SLURPS IT DOWN]
Uncle's existence is a top
secret of our Chunwoo Group.
It's a secret that only my grandfather
and I know in South Korea, and I just
found out one more person who knows. Who is it?
[KIM'S SIGH]
(Kim)
Sigh, um...
Is your uncle's name Kim Shin?
[Smiling]
Come on,
CEO Kim, he's our
uncle, so why is it Kim?
It's
[YOO]
Who is Kim Shin again?
(Kim) Please eat, puzzled sigh.
Since it's a secret of
birth, it's only natural
for a chaebol heir to have a
tragedy like this one (Deokhwa).
CEO Kim, don’t worry,
I've risen from the bottom.
It's been several years of just eating various
rice dishes with seollongtang during lunch.
I will eat this and protect my company.
Like a chaebol, bam!
[Clearing throat]
Deok-hwa.
It's not 'my company'
(Secretary Kim)
It's the company of all employees.
They are doing well to protect it,
so please set aside your excessive worries.
Lunchtime is over, and I enjoyed the meal.
(Deok-hwa)
I'm still not done, I...
(Employee 1)
Please take the gift set with you.
(Secretary Kim)
Yes.
(Employee 1)
Thank you.
(Sunny)
Enjoy your meal.
[SIGNIFICANT MUSIC]
(Guest 1) Excuse me
(Sunny) Yes
Just a moment
[THE TEACUP RATTLES]
(Kim Shin)
I didn’t recognize you even with you so close
You are
Wang Ye.
(Kim Shin)
You couldn’t protect not even your woman, your loyal subjects, or Goryeo
Not even you
Just a single thing.
(Kim Shin)
The value of this sword ultimately
was that
[THE SHARP SOUND EFFECT]
(Kim Shin)
Cutting down Park Jung Heon
[THE TREMBLING BREATH]
(Kim Shin)
Please forgive me
I die gloriously
I’m only now sending this message.
You’re wearing a very vulgar hat, still
Is it that goblin that’s rumored to have returned to nothingness?
There’s a lot of fluff in my rumors
[AS I WIPE THE TEACUP]
(Grim Reaper)
Was it dust or wind
that scattered in the rain?
[A SIGNIFICANT PIECE OF MUSIC]
Of course
It didn’t become a radish to eat
What happened?
(Kim Shin)
I thought I wouldn’t remember
Everything must have returned to nothingness
(Grim Reaper)
Everyone was like that
But my memories were intact.
I'm not sure, but
there's one thing I can say
(Deokhwa)
I will stand by Uncle Kkeutbang until the very end
Really
(Shin)
I was weak-hearted back then, really
(Samsin)
If you're going to take sides anyway, just leave Yeoui's memories
(Shin)
Why?
(Samsin)
Shin-i and Tak-i are so sad
A whole world has closed
I feel like at least someone who isn't us
should remember all the history of that love
But you know,
(Shin)
Why do I feel like
I've only discovered the door to that closed world?
Did I not close it enough?
[THE ABSURD BREATH OF THE THREE GODS]
What happened to you?
How did you come back?
With the tyranny of the powerful
You came well
Really
It's nice to be welcomed
Without any speed
[SAD MUSIC]
It's too late but
It's very late but
(Grim Reaper)
It should have been said 9 years ago
It should have been said 900 years ago
Only now am I saying this
I hope you will forgive me.
My destiny.
(The Grim Reaper) You
who protected my Goryeo
Forgive me for the
sins I could not keep.
Though loved
The sin of not loving anyone.
Forgive me
[I SMILE SLIGHTLY]
I should start with a haircut
[I CHUCKLE]
[KIM SHIN EXHALES]
Finally, I've returned to my home
It's my home
I still have 10 years left on the rent
[KIM SHIN CHUCKLES]
What about your sister?
I haven't seen her
(Reaper)
It's been 9 years
I’m being punished by longing
After all, I am eternally a sinner
(Reaper)
Did you see any of the others?
(Kim Shin)
Yeah
You don't remember, do you?
(Kim Shin)
Uh
You became a radio PD.
It's nice.
I listen sometimes.
Let me know too, so I can listen.
[DOOR LOCK OPERATION SOUND]
(Grim Reaper)
Deokhwa, Deokhwa, Deokhwa, Deokhwa, Deokhwa
[Door lock operation sound]
[The door opens and closes with a click]
(Grim Reaper)
Hide, hide, here, here.
[THE DOOR OPENS WITH A CLICK]
(Deokhwa)
Uncle in the end room.
[THE DOOR CLOSES WITH A CLICK]
(Grim Reaper)
Oh, you came? What brings you here?
(Dukhwa)
I met a strange person at
work, and my heart is all unsettled, so
[I THOUGHT I'D CHECK ON UNCLE AT THE END ROOM]
The grim reaper smiles slightly. (Dukhwa)
But Uncle at the end room (grim reaper) Huh?
If it's Uncle, then it's Uncle Why do
we call him Uncle at the end room?
(Dukhwa) Now that I think about it, Uncle at the
end room How long has he been living in our house?
You can tell by looking at the real
estate contract (Dukhwa)
Oh, but
why are there two bottles of liquor?
Who came?
[THE GRIM REAPER RATTLES THE LIQUOR BOTTLES]
I prefer to hold a bottle in each hand and drink.
(Deok-hwa)
Then what about those heels behind the sofa?
[THE GRIM REAPER IS SPITTING OUT BEER]
[THE GRIM REAPER IS COUGHING]
(Kim Shin)
Wow, this sofa is really pretty.
The owner has a good eye.
(Grim Reaper)
The finishing is nice, really.
(Deok-hwa)
Huh? That strange, peculiar one from earlier...
You got a haircut?
Your hair looks nice.
(Kim Shin)
I’m a friend of the author, just came to visit...
(Grim Reaper)
I’m going, was about to go.
It was fun, go.
Oh, okay.
(Grim Reaper)
Yeah, go.
(Kim Shin)
Nice to meet you.
- (Deok-hwa) Yes, um...
- (Kim Shin) You're wearing a vulgar outfit.
(Deok-hwa)
What is it? Is it a secret of birth?
[The door opens with a click]
Is Uncle in the last room also in on it?
[The upstairs door closes with a click]
(Deok-hwa)
Oh my.
Did you not hear any noise from the 2nd floor just now?
- I didn't hear anything.
- You did, didn't you?
- It didn't happen
- It happened, it happened
(Grim Reaper)
It didn't happen, Deokhwa, Deokhwa
Do you want to see my eyes?
[SOFT MUSIC]
(Radio Host)
The temperature has dropped to 22 degrees above zero,
and it has become quite chilly, right?
I'll play the last song for you
Please be careful of the cold
(Staff 3)
Oh, what should I do?
It wasn't 2 degrees above zero,
but they said it was 22 degrees in the broadcast
I wrote it wrong
This is how a day without the writer shows like this.
(Staff 3)
Ah, CP-nim is also on the way, Staff
[3'S AWKWARD MOAN]
(Euntak) Don't worry,
[I'LL TAKE RESPONSIBILITY]
The door opens with a
click. (CP) Is it 22 degrees?
[The door closes with a click]
[CP's incredulous breathing]
'The weather has dropped to 22 degrees, so it's
gotten quite chilly, right?' 'Be careful of
catching a cold.' Does this even make sense, huh?
I’m sorry, Producer Ji,
are you in a relationship?
(CP) My heart is a perfect spring day
At this rate, flowers might bloom, huh?
I’m sorry (Staff 4)
Wow, what is this?
Ji PD, what kind of wizard are you?
It just popped up on social media
in front of our broadcasting station.
Right now, it's exactly 22 degrees in the video.
[Calm music]
(Staff 4)
They say flowers are blooming brightly this winter.
(Anchor)
Today, the temperature in Sangam-dong soared
to 22 degrees.
It's an abnormal temperature for the first time in 9 years.
(Video Anchor)
Off-season cherry blossoms are in full bloom,
captivating the citizens.
(Woman 2)
What the heck is this?
It's so amazing, right?
(Man 2)
Is this even possible?
(Euntak)
They say listeners drop off the most
during the reorganization.
So we need to maintain the atmosphere
before the reorganization
to keep existing listeners engaged.
(Euntak)
Yes, I understand.
I'll send you the reorganization plan,
so please take a look.
[HE BLOWS AIR THROUGH HIS LIPS]
[HE TAPS THE KEYBOARD]
[HEAVY MUSIC]
What on earth is that man?
(Euntak)
Oh, oh, what's going on?
[EUNTAK CLEARS HIS THROAT]
Even with medication, it’s only temporary.
So what I'm saying is
What the hell is this?
What do you mean?
Why are you sitting there?
Someone called me
That's your concern
I won't be joining you
That person
Hasn't come?
They came
They came but don't recognize me
Yes
(Euntak)
I heard your story well
But I have an appointment, so it's a bit uncomfortable
My boyfriend is coming
It seems like you don't have a boyfriend
(Euntak)
Ah, did the email go through? It's urgent
You got a haircut, I almost didn't recognize you
I still don't recognize you
I did figure it out?
[I CHUCKLE]
But
You were there earlier, right?
(Kim Shin)
I'm everywhere and yet nowhere
(Eun Tak)
Earlier, there was a video at 22 degrees, in front of the broadcasting station
[gentle music]
I'm trying to see someone
I’ve missed you, a lot
When I see you, it feels like you'll come running to me
As if you'll hug me at any moment
(Kim Shin)
But knowing that things like that
don't happen
My heart aches and so on.
But why are you telling me that?
You asked me
But aren't you going to order anything?
- (Employee 2) Enjoy your meal
- (Kimshin) Yes
[EUNTAK'S FORCED SMILE]
- (Kimshin) Ah, I...
- (Euntak) No
(Euntak)
How could I not have five thousand won...
Why did you come to the cafe?
Ah, my wallet was in my coat
I was brought here without thinking to grab my coat
(Kimshin)
I'm sorry, I'll drink well
I will definitely pay off this debt next time...
(Euntak)
I won't see you next time
Which way are you going?
(Kim Shin)
Ah, me, ah, this, this way
Oh...
[KIM SHIN'S SIGH]
Just a little more
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
Let me pay back just five thousand won
[GASPING BREATHS]
[SIGH]
[THE GRIM REAPER RUMMAGES THROUGH HIS POCKETS]
[HE PULLS OUT A BILL]
[SIGH]
Close the door and go!
(Grim Reaper)
How am I supposed to fix this, something like this
Let me pay just ten thousand won, to buy a book
[SIGH]
[THE GRIM REAPER CRUMPLES THE BANKNOTE]
[Tapping the machine]
No, it's been a while since I called for AS
and they haven't come?
[KIM SHIN'S URGENT BREATH]
(Kim Shin)
I just need one hundred thousand won, to buy meat
Please
(Grim Reaper)
There must be a divine intention to keep you in my memory
It's quite difficult to say it like that
I have no choice but to use my last method
Thinking back to the old days
'Gold come out, click' doesn't work
Since there’s a unique number
I can’t even sell it, that.
(Kim Shin)
It's confusing
So is that the only way?
What is it?
[GRAND MUSIC]
[DEOKHWA'S SURPRISED GROAN]
(Deokhwa)
Our home's security is amazing, it's really safe
How on earth...
Who on earth are you?
I am
(Kim Shin)
Water and fire, light and darkness
To you, I'm Yoo Shin-jae, to you, I'm Kim Shin
The uncle grandpa talked about?
The person mentioned in the chairman's will
That person
(Deokhwa)
Is it grandpa's will?
(Secretary Kim)
It is both the chairman's will
and a will passed down
since the time of Deokhwa-gun's ancestors
(Chairman Yoo)
One day, a person who writes 'trustworthy god' on the Kim family name will come
And if he says, 'I have come to find my belongings'
you should give them to him
Everything I left behind belongs to that person
[The heavens roar]
That person walks through the rain
[The rain pours down]
and will go with blue flames
Then know that it is Kim Sin
(Kim Sin)
It is a night that reminds me of Chairman Yoo.
I don't need a company.
(Kim Shin)
The Yoo family has worked hard, so
there's no way it doesn't belong to Deokhwa.
I just need my house, my status,
a card, and a nephew.
I will uphold the chairman's will.
(Secretary Kim)
I will prepare the house, status, and card.
You are the nephew.
No, that's not it.
Ha, if you weren't self-aware, that's fine.
What are you talking about?
(CP)
Ji Eun-tak!
What on earth did you do to receive the call?
Because of you handling the call,
the listener bulletin board is in complete chaos!
[DISPLEASED SIGH]
They gave it as a set of kitchen knives,
but they keep calling to ask us to exchange it
for clothing vouchers, making it impossible
for the writers to work. What should we do then?
We're not a clothing company,
so what are we supposed to do?
(CP) What about the broadcasting station? Are
you guys paying your salaries by digging in the dirt?
Clothing companies and
kitchen knife companies say
they’re pulling all their ads,
what are we going to do?
Here, we have to take
responsibility for sponsorships
and advertisements and fill them;
[IF WE CAN'T, IT’S A
DISMISSAL—EUNTAK'S SIGH]
Manager!
- Why!
- (Euntak) I'll do my best
(Euntak)
This isn't easy
I'll give it a try
Ah, damn, tsk
Ugh, that, that weirdo
[The door opens with a click]
[EUNTAK RUSTLES THE PAPERS]
[KIM SHIN FLIPS THROUGH THE PAGES OF THE BOOK]
[SOFT MUSIC]
[SLIGHTLY SMILES]
(Student 1)
I got confessed to by Seonghun yesterday
- (Student 2) Really?
- (Student 1) By Seonghun from the next class
[STUDENTS CHEER]
[STUDENTS CHATTER]
(Euntak)
It's a good time
[KIM SHIN'S LAUGHTER]
Why are you laughing?
(Kim Shin)
Oh, it's cute
(Euntak)
That's true
(Kim Shin)
Not that
But
Aren't you going to give me my five thousand won?
(Kim Shin)
If I don't give it, will we meet again?
Would you like to come and get it?
[EUNTAK SIGHS]
I have to go get it, it's my punishment
You know what I mean, right?
I don't know
(Euntak)
If there's another time
I'm saying I will report it then
Why do our paths keep overlapping?
Sometimes I understand, sometimes I don't.
[LAUGH]
Why are you laughing this time?
Because I'm very happy.
(Kim Shin)
I can't believe moments like this
Everything is perfect.
What's going on?
(Eun Tak)
Is avoiding it the best option, or what?
Which way are you going?
There you go again.
(Kim Shin)
I'll listen to your broadcast well.
I always listen well.
How do you know I'm broadcasting?
(Eun Tak)
At this point, it's too suspicious.
At that time, I thought you were an actor.
You're not an actor, right?
I'm sorry, but what do you do?
(Kim Shin)
Ah, so that...
That company over there
The furniture company?
(Eun Tak)
What do you do there?
Ah, that’s uh, the highest person?
[Sighs]
Excuse me
(Kim Shin)
I saw you looking at the documents from that company earlier
Give it to me
It's the sponsorship documents, right?
Give it to me, I'll verify it
You’re the highest person over there.
[Bright music] (Mr. Kim) Sigh, originally
it's supposed to be the manager who signs.
The CEO has
specially requested this.
(Ahn Tak) Ah
[SECRETARY KIM PASSES THE DOCUMENTS]
So that person is the CEO.
Do they come to the head office?
They don’t come to work
(Euntak) Ah, then how
should I express my
gratitude? The truth is,
I don’t even know their phone number
(Secretary Kim) But you
told me to sign this document?
Why?
[EUNTAK’S AWKWARD SMILE]
Yes, um, so, why could that be?
[Euntak’s awkward
breathing] [Thinking breath]
Then could you leave your contact
information, PD? I’ll pass it on.
Thank you
But that person's name...
[AWKWARD SMILE]
Isn't it really strange?
[Smiling slightly]
If you get involved with that person, it becomes like this
They use the characters for Yuga and Jae
Ah, yes, thank you
[CHEERS FROM THE CROWD]
(Together)
Ji PD, Ji PD!
- (Staff 3) Ah, PD-nim is the best!
- (Staff 4) Ji PD!
[CHEERS FROM THE CROWD]
(Writer)
What happened? How did you get the advertisement?
Ha, I don't know
It feels like I've been enchanted by something
Like a miracle
Other than that, I can't explain it
So what if it is?
It's important for our program
to survive during the restructuring
[CHEERS FROM THE CROWD]
- (Staff 3) PD-nim, the best!
- (Staff 4) Ji PD, the best!
(Writer)
Okay, okay, let's ride this good energy
And do well with this item
(Euntak)
'Looking for a person'
'Looking for that person we broke up with
10 years ago in a phone photo album'
"I'm searching for the forgotten faces
and the forgotten memories."
"If you send in your stories,
we'll introduce them on the spot"
"and even connect you with the person involved"
(Euntak)
Oh, that's great?
(Writer)
First, each of us should dig through our phone's photo albums
and organize our stories for the next meeting
You know about sincerity, right? Sincerity
I can spot a story right away
(Euntak)
Yeah, oh, the writer can really spot it right away
Work hard, everyone
(Staff 2)
Yes
Who's waiting for a call?
[A CHUCKLE]
Not doing it
[EUN-TAK GRABS A DRINK]
[THE WRITER RUSTLES THROUGH THE PAPERS]
[EUN-TAK EXHALES]
[YOON-A EXHALES]
(Yoon-a)
The plan is good
Should I also look for my first love?
You look for that person, Kim Shin
[YOON-A POURS THE ALCOHOL GENTLY]
Should I?
But is that really your handwriting?
I’m telling you it is, so it’s weird
Ugh, isn’t it a ghost?
You saw ghosts until high school.
After not seeing them for about 9 or 10 years,
they started showing up again recently.
Right behind you now!
(Yuna)
Ah, hey!
Can you get me a napkin?
[Yuna's annoyed groan]
Just die, seriously.
[Yuna's sigh]
[Euntak exhales sharply]
What are you, anyway?
Why am I your bride?
(Euntak)
You're that person's bride.
Who are you?
(Deokhwa)
Uncle!
(Duk-hwa) The humble
building I have I heard something
came to this address on
the first floor, but I don’t
understand the situation, it
used to be that chicken place
here I hesitate to throw
it away (Eun-tak) I have
something to do, so I don’t know when
I’ll come back You can wait well, right?
You can throw it away to this person,
is your uncle’s name Ji Eun-tak? Huh?
(Duk-hwa) Why do you have
so many names, uncle? Huh?
You bring it, I’ll take
it, saying what, this?
(Duk-hwa) Then I’ll bring it.
(Grim Reaper)
Then bring it to Sunny and
ask her to pass it on
For some reason
Sunny has moved to the rooftop of her house
The two of them are getting along well as neighbors
It's the same
Rather, the other side is more suspicious
Me, I'm the most natural
Because I'm the landlord
Since things are getting strange anyway
It seems better for you, who is a stranger to everyone, to be the strangest
(Deok-hwa)
Me, me
The boss over there looked pretty, I'll go
Hello?
After 9 years
I have an excuse
(Deok-hwa)
No, uncles, can't you hear me?
Who am I talking to right now?
Yeah?
[SOFT MUSIC]
(Employee 3)
Welcome
The boss...
Isn't coming today?
[CLEARING UP THE DISHES]
(Employee 3)
Huh?
Um, the boss...
(Employee 3)
Ah, she's not coming today either?
What brings you here?
(Employee 3)
Enjoy your meal
(Guest 2)
Yes
(Employee 3)
Huh?
The boss...
You're not coming out?
(Employee 3)
What is your name?
Should I call you?
No
Please just pass this on
(Employee 3)
Yes
[FOOTSTEPS ECHO]
What is this?
So, no, what is that?
(Sunny)
It's not a store right now, but they said they came to the previous store
The landlord
gave it to a handsome guy
They said that guy brought this
so I checked the CCTV
He was really handsome
(Euntak)
The previous store?
Where is the store from before?
That’s why it’s strange
(Sunny)
It's actually
international mail, ah, that
store
The director has never
been there and it's strange,
so strange that it's too good-looking, what is it?
(Euntak) It's my handwriting
(Euntak) Mom, hello?
My beautiful mom, who is probably
only worried about me, how is heaven?
Could it be just like this place?
I am currently in Canada
Writing a letter
to Mom about how I came here [soft
music]
Mom would really be surprised if she knew?
Just a door away, a
place like paradise unfolds.
If I'm with the uncle
I have someone who
asks about my well-being.
My mom sees things that
I shouldn't be looking at.
I will worry and feel sorry, but
Don't do that anymore.
Thanks to you, I've become
special to someone like this.
I'm doing okay, Mom.
It will get better.
I will become happier
than anyone else.
See you again someday.
I love you, Mom.
In Canada, mom and
daughter Eun-tak are.
In Canada?
I don't even have a
passport, but this...
What is this?
[TREMBLING BREATH]
This is really scary.
[I RUMMAGE THROUGH THE BAG]
(The uncle) The
person called "Uncle"
Is it Kim Shin?
What on earth
happened 9 years ago?
What are you forgetting, anyway?
[MOBILE PHONE RINGTONE]
[CLEARS THE THROAT]
[Clears throat] Hello
(My name is) Yushin Jae.
[EUNTAK'S SURPRISED BREATH]
Oh, hello, just a moment.
[EUNTAK BLOWS AIR
THROUGH HER MOUTH]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
( Eun-tak ) Yes, hello.
Hello?
(Kim Shin) Were you
perhaps waiting for my call?
(Ah, I'm busy)
I forgot to give you
my phone number.
(Ah, yes)
I'm late in expressing my gratitude.
I was really thankful at that time.
How about a walk with me?
(Kim Shin) Director Ji,
where did you say you live?
Me?
I didn't say where I live.
Ah, ah
Oh, so where do you live?
[EUN-TAK SUDDENLY STANDS UP]
(Eun-tak) Incheon Haean-dong
It's near the art platform.
Where is near the art platform?
My life is a bit complicated
in various ways.
(Euntak) Where is
the representative?
I'll be there soon.
It seems like it will be near the
art platform in about 30 minutes.
Are you asking me
out on a date right now?
Yes
I made up my mind to
go on a date with PD Ji.
(Seung-tak) Please call
me when you get close.
In about 30 minutes.
[CELL PHONE OPERATION SOUND]
[SMILES FAINTLY]
[SOFT MUSIC]
[EUNTAK TAKES A BREATH]
[EUNTAK SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(Kim Shin) I like
that scent too.
(Euntak) Ah, this is a
scent that women like.
You seem to know a lot
about women's perfume, huh?
(Kim Shin) Is it bad that I know
a lot about women's perfume?
(Understood) What did I say?
She's the only woman who
knows my phone number.
Really? Why?
That's a bit strange, isn't it?
There's nothing
strange about it.
I just activated it
a little while ago.
I haven't needed to
use my phone lately.
I went to a place where the cellphone doesn't
work well, there were just a lot of eyes.
(Ah)
[Mobile phone alarm sound]
[Euntak's surprised moan]
[THE CELL PHONE
ALARM SUDDENLY STOPS]
Just a moment.
[EUNTAK RATTLES
THE MEDICINE BOTTLE]
[EUNTAK PUTS THE
WATER BOTTLE DOWN]
(Eun-tak) I keep forgetting.
You have to eat it regularly.
What kind of medicine is it?
Medicine for the
illness of the mind?
Since when?
May I ask why?
[EUNTAK'S TROUBLED GROAN]
Actually, I don't really know.
What was the beginning?
(Euntak) You can escape.
I'm being honest to
give you that opportunity.
[EUNTAK SMILES SLIGHTLY]
Isn't it a bit strange for me?
I'll try to be more strange.
[LAUGHTER]
Ah, I'm going on vacation.
(Eun-tak) I'm just wondering if
you might be near the art platform.
I'm telling you in advance.
Where are you going?
(铠咖) Foreign Affairs
I'm going to a foreign country for
the first time, and I'm so nervous.
I'm so uncool, right?
Even if it's the first
time, I won't be nervous.
(Kim Shin) Very natural
As if it's the first time here
I'll behave like the people
who live there. Don't worry.
You don't really
know me, do you?
I believe you.
(Photographer) Alright,
I'm taking a picture.
One, two
[CAMERA OPERATION SOUND]
[CAMERA SHUTTER SOUND]
[I TAP THE KEYBOARD]
[MOUSE CLICK SOUND]
It seems like there’s something
there I’m going to find it.
What's there?
I'm going because
I don't know that.
(Sunny) Yeah, if you don't
know, you should go ask, okay?
Go ask when you’re
even a year younger.
(Sunny) If you take a t-shirt
with a hat when you go overseas...
You know this falls under
international law, right?
[EUNTAEK SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(Euntak) Yes
Let's match the TPO, okay?
It's still my first overseas trip.
(Eun-tak) Yes
But
The boss made a killing in
business and earned a lot of money.
Why aren't you moving?
Did you not know, PD?
This building is
mine, I bought it.
Why don't you know? You've talked
about it more than a hundred times.
(Eun-tak) I asked
why you're not moving?
[SUNNY'S SIGH]
Moving is a hassle.
And I have sick house syndrome.
That doesn't mean that.
[Smiling slightly]
No, that's not it.
(Sunny) The
tangerine is delicious.
- (Euntak) It's really delicious.
- (Sunny) Yeah.
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
[SOUND OF AN AIRPLANE ENGINE]
Excuse me.
(Seung-tak) I received a letter, and is it
correct that it was sent from this hotel?
(Staff) [Korean] It's
correct that we sent it.
Ah, are you Korean?
That's a relief.
(The staff) The founder
of this hotel is also Korean.
Ah, yes.
(Employee) There was a maintenance project
for the mailbox hallway on all floors.
A few letters have been
discovered caught in here.
It's the first time that a letter from
10 years ago has been found, but...
How do you know
it was 10 years ago?
(The staff) This envelope
design is from 10 years ago.
It must have been a precious
memory I'm sorry for being late.
It's okay.
Isn't there a reason
for coming late?
Every step of God's
has a reason behind it...
Who do you think said that?
[AWKWARD SMILE]
Elegant
Good.
[CALM MUSIC]
[THE DOOR CREAKS]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
[A SIGH]
(Seung-tak) Ah, I feel so
strange today, seriously.
How do we meet here?
I am on a business trip.
I need the reference quality for that, which
is necessary for the furniture corner...
(Seung-tak) What did you say?
How have you been?
Did you follow me by any chance?
Then will we be caught?
- What should we do?
- I'm not a bad person.
How would I know that?
If we hang out together,
wouldn't you know?
There's no reason
to go together.
He, our company has
sponsored the PD's program.
(김신) At that time, you definitely
said you would buy me a meal.
Is this your first time
in Canada, CEO?
Alright, then let's go this way.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
(Sunny) To you who thought
that my oblivion is my peace.
I missed you.
(Sunny) Please, in
the next life, we will
Waiting is short, but the
meeting becomes a long bond.
Long long ago
Goodbye.
(Euntak) What if we
Have we met before?
About 10 years ago?
Here, CEO.
Are you a ghost?
(Kim Shin) Where is the sorrow
that lasts a thousand years?
(Eun-tak) I'm
voting for 'exists'.
(Kim Shin) Which side will you
hang on? Is it sadness, or is it love?
(Eun-tak) [sniffling] Sad love
Subtitle: Choi Hye-ran