[THEME SONG]
(Kim Shin)
Yeah, that's what I'm saying
Today is just the right day for this
I'm saying this because you keep dazzling me
All those first loves
were you, that's what I'm saying
On another day that's just right
Will you be the bride of this Goryeo man?
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
I will
(Euntak)
I will be the bride of this lonely man
I will be the
first and last bride of this radiant man
I will definitely do that
(Euntak)
Mom
I'm getting married.
I'll live well.
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
(Ghost1)
Did you meet a goblin?
You're getting married too, that's great
[Sniffling]
Why am I crying?
[GHOST1 SOBS]
(Euntak)
Sister?
[GHOST1'S SURPRISED MOAN]
Can you see us?
Yes, wow, how long has it been?
(Euntak)
Have you been well?
[Mysterious sound effects]
(Ghost1)
Ah, girl
You can see us now?
(Euntak)
Ah, you startled me
[EUNTAK SMILES A LITTLE]
Have you been doing well?
It must have been lonely, right?
[GHOST 1 IS SOBBING]
(Ghost 1)
Come with me.
I’ll treat you better than a goblin.
Just stay still here.
There’s a sack of salt over there!
(Ghost 1)
Oh, girl, you still have that temper, huh?
[LAUGHTER FROM GHOST 1 AND EUNTAK]
Congratulations on your wedding!
[Laughter from Ghost 1]
(Ghost 2)
Congratulations!
[Laughter from Euntak]
(Ghost 1)
Yes!
[THEY LAUGH TOGETHER]
[GHOST 1 HUMS]
[THE SCENERY RESONATES]
(Grim Reaper) Drink up, it helps
you forget the
memories of this world.
(Man 1) Thank you.
(Man 2) What kind
of nonsense is this?
Sharing a table with the
guy who holds the steering
wheel of my car and
being told to drink the same
thing is just one drink all
the same. [Heavy music]
What the hell are
you talking about?
It's infuriating that I'm
dead. (Man 2) If you live
your whole life and it
amounts to less than the
[PRICE OF A WATCH, IT’S QUITE
UNPLEASANT TO BE TREATED THE SAME WAY]
I’ll say it again, here it’s
just one drink all the same.
Your watch has already stopped.
(Grim Reaper)
Anything you have
cannot cross that door
Did you live well in this world as a strong person?
But the moment you cross that door
you will know
The sins committed with your eyes, the sins committed with your mouth
The sins committed with your hands and feet, the sins committed with your heart
How powerful they are
How they pull you down to the very depths of hell
[THE TREMBLING BREATHS OF MAN 2]
[MAN 2 IS SOBBING]
[Significant sound effect]
[Bright music]
(Yoona)
Are you really not going to do the blind date?
(Euntak)
I don’t like chefs.
It's not a chef, it’s my client this time.
(Yoona)
He’s a chaebol, has a lot of money, and is good-looking.
Decisively
He’s younger than you.
He likes older women.
And the request isn’t anything weird.
It's about inheritance, what do you think?
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
Blind date?
[A GASP OF DISBELIEF]
[PLAYFUL MUSIC]
[SHARP SOUND EFFECT]
[THE BAG FALLS WITH A THUD]
[YOONA’S ANNOYED BREATH]
[YOONA'S SURPRISED GASP]
(Yoona)
Ah, what is this? It's new
Ah, why is this happening
I shouldn't be waiting here
(Kim Shin)
Ji Eun Tak!
(Eun Tak)
Huh, what should I listen to? A rookie singer?
(Writer)
What
(Eun Tak)
Hmm
[GASPING BREATH]
[The door slams shut]
How did you come here?
I'm Ji Eun Tak PD's boyfriend
[LIVELY MUSIC]
(Staff)
Whoa
(Kim Shin)
Oh, technically, we’re at the stage of getting married
How about the wedding this weekend?
[The Writer's Surprised Breath]
- (Staff) Wow
- (Euntak) Wow
(Kim Shin)
Ah, should we eat lunch from now? Let's go out
Who's coming?
Deokhwa, you should greet properly
Ah, right
I hope you don't think I look too old
(Kim Shin)
No way
[Euntak smiles slightly]
(Deokhwa)
Aunt, please give me something spicy
- (Staff 1) Yes
- (Kim Shin) Here it comes
[DEOKHWA'S SIGH]
(Deokhwa)
What is this?
With this formal feast
the man and woman are sitting side by side
Ah, I caught on, I caught on
Yeah, we're going to get married
(Euntak and Deokhwa)
Whoa
[COMICAL MUSIC]
Is Saturday better? Is Sunday better?
Why are you doing this, since earlier?
Then is lunchtime better? Is dinnertime better?
(Deokhwa)
I prefer Sunday evening, because Saturday is a party night
[DISCONTENTED SIGH]
Why do you ask?
Are you asking because you don't know?
This is why you won't go on a blind date.
(Kim Shin)
A conglomerate, a handsome conglomerate
and a significantly younger conglomerate
What does that mean?
The only one that fits that condition
is me in the country
Don't worry, he's not my type
Nice to meet you
I’m Yu Deok-hwa
Oh, yes, I've heard a lot about you
(Eun-tak)
I’m Ji Eun-tak
Oh, you became the team leader, team leader
Ji Eun-tak?
(Deok-hwa)
That old letter, that Ji Eun-tak?
You know my building, that Ji Eun-tak?
Oppa still has a lot he doesn't know.
(Employee 2)
Enjoy your meal.
(Deokhwa)
Ah, yes, I'll do that.
[DEOKHWA SIGHS]
But our uncle
knows what it is and got married...
It's a goblin.
(Euntak)
Isn't it true that everyone has at least one goblin they know?
Then
That's amazing.
My building knows, and our uncle knows too.
[Kim Shin clicks his tongue]
(Deokhwa)
What is it? Why does it seem like I'm the only one who keeps not knowing?
(Kim Shin)
Come on.
Hurry up and eat more.
You'll understand when you grow up.
Me too.
I just go on blind dates, a lot.
I’ll soon be a married woman, so what.
[COUGHING]
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
(Kim Shin)
They said they are a married woman.
Where do you live?
(Deok Hwa)
Oh, they're not my style.
Is this job suitable for you?
(Deok Hwa)
Uncle is getting married.
Hmm, that's good news.
Yes, so I plan to get married before my uncle.
That's even better news.
That's right? I'll raise a lot of kids
and definitely give them a lot of siblings
Ah, then there’s nothing more to wish for
But Deok-hwa
You can't get married alone
[snickering]
There are many women
(Secretary Kim)
That's right
It can't be too many; that's the problem
(Deok-hwa)
Ah
[SIGH]
Was there anyone who felt their heart race just thinking about it?
(Secretary Kim)
Was there anyone you missed so much it made you cry if you couldn't see them?
I would even die in
place of that person.
Did anyone think about it?
Not yet
Then, Mr. Kim, don't you have any thoughts on marriage?
[SECRETARY KIM SMIRKS SLIGHTLY]
- (Secretary Kim) No, I don't
- (Deokhwa) Why not?
I’m already married and have three kids
I married someone like that
Wow, really?
But why didn't I know?
I haven't talked about it
Why didn't you talk about it?
Because you didn't ask
[LAUGHTER]
Deokhwa, you're still not interested in the affairs of the world or people around you, right?
So I’m waiting
for Deokhwa’s questions
Real adult questions
[SOFT MUSIC]
About the world
About the joys and sorrows of those around
[I SMILE SLIGHTLY]
(Deokhwa)
Thank you
Please wait just a little longer
I will grow up diligently
Yes
(Secretary Kim)
Um
[SECRETARY KIM SMILES SLIGHTLY]
Wow, how can you come out everywhere without my consent, huh?
How is it that everyone is coming out here and there?
Oh, look in front, look in front.
[Tire Noise]
(Kim Shin)
Left, left, car, car, car, car, car
[Smiling slightly]
Why, are you anxious?
No, seeing you drive
makes me feel like you're really grown up
Hey, lane, lane, grip the steering wheel tight, tight
Oh, I see it all
I know, I know, I know everything!
I'm just curious, curious
It's my first time sitting in the passenger seat
Left turn, left turn
(Eun Tak)
Ah, left, left...
(Kim Shin)
Left, left turn, left, left!
[Tire screeching sound]
[EUNTAK'S TREMBLING BREATH]
Ah, really, where are we going?
When you turn left
turn on the blinker, the blinker, always
[EUNTAK TURNS ON THE BLINKER]
[SOFT MUSIC]
So pretty
[EUNTAK'S LAUGHTER]
So cool, Mr. Kim Shin
It must not be just a day or two
[LAUGHTER]
[SHE SMILES SLIGHTLY]
Set a bowl of cool water aside and do it
Mystically
(Kim Shin)
Yeah
[LAUGHTER]
(Store clerk)
Are you going to give a gift?
It's a wedding watch.
Since you have pretty wrists, I'll choose this one.
(Eun-tak)
I love you for all the roads we will walk together
and all the scenery we will look at together
The shy and fluttering
every question and answer we will share
and all those moments with you.
I am your bride.
[snickers]
(Radio host)
Then let's listen to some music
and I'll be back with listener stories.
(Eun-tak)
Cue
What is this?
There's no subject, and
Is this a love letter written at night?
What is it? I like love letters, me
That would be the case
(Writer)
'To you who will think
my oblivion
is my peace'
'I knew the moment our eyes met'
'That you too are
holding on to all memories'
(Euntak)
Choose this story, it's up to the PD
I’ll be out for a bit
(Writer)
Hey, PD Ji, hey!
This is live right now
[The door opens with a click]
(Radio Host)
'I hope that in the next life we will'
[The door clicks shut]
'Waiting is short and our meeting is a long connection'
'With a face we can meet without excuses'
'With a fervent name that is the only one in this world'
[Sound of tire friction]
'If we accidentally run into each other
let's be the kind of people who greet each other with a smile'
[The radio host continues reading the story]
(Sunny)
With love that is always the answer
I pray that we meet like that
Now that we've seen each other's faces, that's enough
Perhaps Kim Woobin
Perhaps the queen lady you
Please last long
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECTS]
Goodbye
Did you really dig up the building?
You didn't just move out?
Yes, last week
(woman)
Miss, it's the rooftop, right?
I signed the lease with your deposit
You mentioned you work at a broadcasting station?
Oh, yes
I'm a bit in a hurry right now
I'll see you later
[EUNTAK'S FAINT BREATHING]
[EUNTAK'S TREMBLING BREATHING]
(Sunny)
Part-timer, I'm leaving
Take care, don't cry
[Calm music]
You eat everything in big bites
Without a care in the world, all alone
I hope I was a comfort to you, even for a moment
Stubborn older brother, please take care
Let's be happy together for a long, long time
[THE FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Goodbye
You remembered it all
Boss
You've left
The boss remembered everything
(Euntak)
I kept that memory alone
Caring for me, who has no memories
Missing the vanished older brother
So lonely by myself.
But why did you leave?
I can't forgive you
[THE TREMBLING BREATH]
In this life
You've made the choice not to see me again
To the afterlife.
There couldn't be a greater punishment than that
[A SIGH]
I should count to five hundred thousand and then go
[MAN 3 MUTTERS]
(Sunny)
One
This
Forty-seven
Forty-eight
Forty-nine
(Grim Reaper)
One
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
This
Three
[SNIFFLING]
I won't convey
The news
In this life.
I will never see you again
Just once
Can I hug you?
Take care
Goodbye
(Grim Reaper)
That’s how we
said farewell in this life
I heard news of her
a long time after that
[THE GRIM REAPER IS SOBBING]
[THE GRIM REAPER KEEPS SOBBING]
[THE GRIM REAPER'S CRIES CAN BE HEARD]
[SNIFFLING]
(Kim Shin)
I touched this filthy thing for you
Is it okay to eat a bit?
[A SIGH FROM THE GRIM REAPER]
Even though the
apple is a rabbit?
[A HOLLOW LAUGH]
Sunny has
left
(The Grim Reaper)
That woman
until the very end
always goes well
[THE GRIM REAPER SOBS]
(The Grim Reaper)
I don't know what to do with you like this
I've had it
I was supposed to return it long ago, but
Sorry for being late
It wasn't mine from the beginning
[SOFT MUSIC]
(Kim Shin)
It was your sorrow, your sin, and your longing
It seems right for you to have it
Is that okay?
(Kim Shin)
Yeah
If you eat this
[I CHUCKLE]
And thank you
The temple that holds the tablets
For the 9 years I was absent
You lit a candle for me every year.
(Grim Reaper)
I don't know if I deserve to honor them
But I want to face my sins
I wish someone would tell me
Our side
'That's enough'
[A FAINT SIGH]
Saying 'That's enough' and
[A SIGH]
[KIM SHIN'S SIGH]
You said you wanted to see me
(Grim Reaper)
Yeah
I want to let you in on a secret
A secret?
It is said that if you commit a great sin in your past life, you become a grim reaper.
What is that sin?
The great sin we have committed is
the sin of taking our own life.
(Grim Reaper)
Those who have taken their own lives
are awakened as grim reapers.
Guiding countless deaths,
living as a being that is neither alive nor dead.
What could be the reason?
Someone with no name, someone with no memory
[THE GRIM REAPER'S HOLLOW LAUGH]
The reason why we needed a home
and why we needed food.
Finding the answers to those questions one day suddenly
The things we gave up
The name, the life we abandoned
Isn't it that we want to have them
When life becomes so desperate
Doesn't our punishment come to an end
[THE REAPER'S SIGH]
I know the reason you avoided me
Because I can guess you met Park Joong-heon nine years ago
So you must have known who you are
And who I am
So
I wanted to apologize
Borrowing your hand like that.
Death should not have been taken
I regret it
And I ask for forgiveness
[HEAVY MUSIC]
[A SIGH]
So forget everything
Live while forgetting
As you kindly send off the deceased
Live by atoning like that
I hope you also
Get to forgive yourself
What God wishes for us
Is to forgive ourselves
And realize the urgency of life
[I SOB]
[LION 1 SOBS]
[THE RICE COOKER LID IS SNAPPED SHUT]
(Euntak)
Aunt, please eat.
[Euntak slams down the rice bowl]
(Aunt Euntak)
Where are you going? At this time of night
[GRABS THE BAG]
The soup is getting cold, eat up
(Aunt Euntak)
Have you got a boyfriend?
Oh dear, you shouldn't be a single mother like your mom
(Euntak)
Aunt, why do you always have to...
[TREMBLING BREATH]
How long are you going to stay?
(Euntak)
I’ve set the table enough for dinner
Aunt, it’s a ghost
It's not good to roam around for long.
(Aunt Euntak)
Where are you looking, with your eyes wide open
Hey
I can't go on like this, it’s unfair
If only I had that bankbook
If only you hadn’t hidden that bankbook
I wouldn't have ended up like this on the street!
[Tense sound effect]
[The light suddenly breaks]
[EUNTAK'S SURPRISED BREATH]
Aunt, why are you really like this?
Do you really have to do this even after death!
(Aunt Euntak)
Hmm, you've been acting up lately
and you're talking back, right, huh?
Sure! [Mysterious sound effect]
[Exciting music] [Euntak
aunt's moan of pain]
(Ghost 1) Ma'am, where are
you touching me, right now?
How much do I cherish this kid
[twisting the arm abruptly] Are
you going to break my hand off for me?
(Euntak aunt) Hey, what are
you? What the hell is this crazy girl?
Crazy about a senior that’s far out...
(Ghost 1) This isn't going to
work, ma'am has to come with
[ME EUNTAK AUNT’S SHOCKED BREATH]
Come with me, I'm lonely that's why.
I get along well with bad girls?
Let go, are you not letting go? Not letting go?
Do you know her?
(Euntak)
Sister
I think I've finally found my companion
On this lonely road to the afterlife,
I will be a great sparring partner
[SAD MUSIC]
Are you leaving?
[CLEARS THROAT]
It's about time to go, right?
Thank you for everything so far
(Ghost1)
Live well with the goblin, girl
[Grabbing Euntak's aunt tightly]
Wow, ma'am, let's go
- (Euntak's aunt) Ah, um...
- (Euntak) Ah, wait a moment
[SIGH]
Aunt, thank you for raising me
(Euntak)
In the next life,
Let's meet as good connections
Don't make me laugh, why would I meet you again?
(Euntak's aunt)
Let go, are you not letting go? Let go, not letting go?
Let go, damn it, let go, let go, let go!
[Mysterious sound effect]
Let go! Ah!
(Grim Reaper)
Welcome
(Euntak)
[Sighing]
You’re still doing it alone, huh?
What about the goblin?
(The Grim Reaper)
I don’t know, I’m going to get some purifying water or something
When I see you, that’s when I’ll see that
I have something to give
By any chance
Did the list come?
No, nothing like that
Ah, never mind, what a surprise
Are you worried? That the list might come?
It’s not so much worry as it is curiosity
I wonder how my fate has changed
[SHE SMILES SLIGHTLY]
Your fate has so many variables
[EUNTAK SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(Euntak)
Exactly
The mark is gone, and I’ve drawn my sword
So, I have lived like this for 9 years
without any major incidents
However
the fact that I am still a missing person
remains unchanged
[CALM MUSIC]
(Euntak)
I almost wasn’t born
I lost someone I love to death
And even
the person who is now in front of me
is the grim reaper
Above all
humans die someday
That’s why life is more beautiful
And after my memories returned,
the first thought that came to me was
I should live as if today is the last
If today is the last, this memory
is the last memory of my beloved
So I should live and love as if I’m dying every moment
That’s how it was
Your life is already beautiful, remember that
[SHE SMILES SOFTLY]
Ah, but what is it that you’re going to give me?
(Grim Reaper)
Ah
Now
(Euntaek)
Wow
Congratulations on your wedding, goblin bride
Thank you
[LAUGHTER]
[SOFT MUSIC]
Until death separates us
Every word of yours
Whatever it may be
I too
Even if death separates us
In every word of yours, whatever it may be
Me too
[THERE'S A SIZZLING SOUND]
- (Euntak) That looks delicious
- (Kimshin) It's fully cooked
- (Euntak) Yeah
- (Kimshin) Yeah
(Euntak)
How many more shall we make?
[THE GRIM REAPER'S STRAINED GROAN]
(Grim Reaper)
Champagne is best between 7 and 9 degrees
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
[Secretary Kim is
[HICCUPING] (DEOKHWA) UNCLE IN THE
END ROOM, SECRETARY KIM IS COUGHING]
Oh my, I feel like I'm
getting drunk without
even drinking (Kim Shin)
What if I'm already drunk?
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[Kim Shin's strained moan]
[Mysterious sound effects]
[Kim Shin grabs the drink]
[Kim Shin's satisfied moan]
[A SIGH]
[HE'S HICCUPING]
[SECRETARY KIM IS COUGHING]
(Kim Shin) One shot
(Deokhwa) Why is
even Uncle like this?
[SECRETARY KIM IS COUGHING]
Are you okay? You don't look well.
Ah, it's okay...
[hiccups]
Okay
(Grim Reaper)
I set it to 7 degrees
Would you like a drink?
Yes, if you give it to me...
(Eun-tak)
[surprised]
Oh my
(Deok-hwa)
Mr. Kim, Mr. Kim
(Eun-tak)
Wow, really
Ah, let's be careful
(Deok-hwa)
Uncles are too careless and naive
[KIM SECRETARY'S ROUGH BREATHING]
What's this? Why does this phrase stick to my mouth?
Sing a song
(Kim Secretary)
[Eun-tak's awkward moan]
Sing a song
[EUN-TAK'S AWKWARD LAUGHTER]
(Eun-tak)
Oh no, what song would I...
- (Eun-tak) I can't sing
- (Kim Secretary) Sing a song
(Kim Shin)
♪ Among so many people ♪
[KIM SECRETARY HOLDS BACK LAUGHTER]
♪ Meeting you is truly a blessing ♪
♪ In the middle of this vast world ♪
(Kim Shin)
Everyone together
(Eun-tak)
♪ Meeting you
is a joy for me too ♪
[EUN-TAK SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(Kim Shin)
♪ Among so many people ♪
[Eun Tak smiles slightly]
(Eun Tak)
I'm sleepy
Good night
I love you
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
(Radio Host)
This is the last song
Everyone be happy
(Eun Tak)
Okay, you worked hard
Thank you for your hard work
[A staff's sigh]
Wow, today’s broadcast was really something
(Writer)
Perfectly timed and the song selection is amazing
Listener reactions on the bulletin board are good
Rarely perfect
Ah, this makes me a bit proud.
[THE WRITER'S LAUGHTER]
Then I'll just have the guest meeting and
leave right away.
(Writer)
Got it, okay.
- (Euntak) Good work.
- (Writer) Yeah, see you tomorrow.
(Euntak)
Yeah.
"Kim Boram, 7 years old"
(Reaper 2)
It seems the kindergarten bus got into an accident.
"Park Younghoon, 45 years old"
This seems to be an article.
(Grim Reaper)
Now
I really think this work is a job.
[THE MOBILE PHONE VIBRATES]
I’ll go take this call.
[THE SOUND OF AN APPROACHING CAR ENGINE]
(Euntak)
Uncle
(Lion 2)
Senior, it’s the roster team.
They said to destroy the roster we received today.
The fate of the children has changed.
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
Really?
(Lion 2)
Ugh, why has their fate changed?
[TENSE SOUND EFFECTS]
[HEAVY MUSIC]
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECTS]
[SIGNIFICANT MUSIC]
The roster is not coming
Because of some death
Is there a death that prevents the roster from coming?
(Lion 2)
What is that?
An incomputable death
[THE VIBRATION OF A MOBILE PHONE]
[PRESSES THE BUTTON WITH A CLICK]
(The Grim Reaper)
Victim
(Kim Shin)
Where are you? Why aren't you coming?
In this harsh world
What time is it now?
(Eun Tak)
It's currently 4 PM
I'm on my way to that meeting
Wait a moment, I need to make a right turn
(Kim Shin)
A right turn is to the right
[Blinker sound]
Ah, seriously
[TENSE MUSIC]
[THE CAR CREAKS]
[THE SOUND OF CHILDREN'S FOOTSTEPS RESONATES]
[TENSE SOUND EFFECTS]
(김신)
Hello, Euntak
Ji Euntak
(은탁)
The kindergarten bus...
If I avoid it, those babies...
[THE SOUND OF SCENERY IS HEARD]
What? I can't hear well, what's going on?
(은탁)
I think I'm crazy, what am I doing right now?
[TIRE FRICTION SOUND]
[TENSE SOUND EFFECT]
[BAM, IT HITS]
(은탁)
Thinking about it, it was a perfect day.
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
When I woke up, I was in that person's arms, and
I also perfectly
made a fried egg.
It was a satisfying live broadcast.
All that perfection
seemed to be for bringing me
to this moment.
So I wouldn't be late.
[THE TENSION-BUILDING SOUND EFFECT]
(Kim Shin)
Hello?
Where are you, Ji Eun-tak, where are you?
[KIM SHIN'S HURRIED FOOTSTEPS]
(Eun-tak)
We couldn't afford to be even a minute or a second late.
It was destined to be this way.
Good night.
I love you.
Me too.
[A SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
[A siren sounds]
(Grim Reaper)
The sacrifice of humans is...
It is an area that cannot
be calculated by God.
I won't even be
able to foresee it.
That's the instinct
of the moment.
Because it is entirely
a choice of one human.
Only humans can do this.
It's a choice.
[I TAKE A BREATH]
[A SIGH]
Late
The list has arrived
[The Grim Reaper's Sigh]
To the cruel question of a wicked god
I gave a terribly sad answer
Other missing persons
[PEOPLE ARE MURMURING]
[PATHETIC MUSIC]
(Grim Reaper)
Born on the day of Gyeongsin in the year of Muin
Age 29
Eun-tak
This person
Is that correct?
[HE SOBS]
(Eun-tak)
'Why is this happening?'
Even while thinking that
I am still doing it
[EUN-TAK'S TREMBLING BREATH]
I'm really
It was so scary, uncle
[A POWERLESS SMILE]
(News anchor)
This afternoon, a truck parked by the roadside
lost its brakes
and crashed into the road,
killing a woman in her 20s.
I guess that car absorbed all the impact in front
Oh, what should we do
Couldn’t it have been an angel?
I believe people like that are angels.
If it weren't for that person,
more people would have died.
(Euntak)
The place where the grim reaper uncle works
[The scenery resonates]
Looks like this.
It's really nice
Mister, I have a question
Humans have four lives, right?
Which life was I on?
Can't you tell the deceased?
You
were on your first life
That's a relief
Three left
[THE DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
[TREMBLING BREATHS]
(The Grim Reaper)
I'll bring the car, let's talk
[TREMBLING BREATHS]
[SOBBING]
[KIM SHIN CONTINUES TO SOB]
(Euntak)
Do you remember
what I said before?
[SHE SOBS]
(Euntak)
The remaining person
has to live hard again
and sometimes ends up crying
[KIM SHIN IS SOBBING]
And laughs a lot
and bravely
That's what it means to honor the love received
[TREMBLING BREATH]
[Sad music]
[Kim Shin's labored breathing]
(Kim Shin)
How can this be...
[SHE'S SOBBING]
How could you do this to me...
I'm sorry
(Euntak)
I'm really sorry
[SHE'S SOBBING]
[KIM SHIN CONTINUES TO SOB]
(Euntak)
Look at me a bit
Show me your face, okay?
[KIM SHIN'S PAINFUL GROAN]
[KIM SHIN'S TREMBLING BREATH]
(Euntak)
Uncle
You didn't grant one of my three wishes
[KIM SHIN'S TREMBLING BREATH]
Can't you grant it now?
Don't be sad for too long
Because I'll come to see you again
I'll wait well
And don't let it rain too much
It's inconvenient for the citizens
Why say three when it's just one?
(Kim Shin)
How can I live without you
I'll be gone for a moment
I promise
(Eun Tak)
This time
I will come
I will definitely
Come find you
In the next life
I will be born full of life
And I will be by your side for a long, long time
I will ask for it like that
I’ll go up there and plead
(Eun Tak)
When everyone has left
Please take a look at this person
[Kim Shin is sobbing]
(Grim Reaper)
It’s the cup of forgetfulness
Memories of this world
It makes me forget
[KIM SHIN'S TREMBLING BREATH]
I won’t drink
the tea
I feel like I have to
go now
[KIM SHIN IS SOBBING]
I’ll come back quickly
[KIM SHIN'S CRIES]
(Euntak)
I’ll run over
and I’ll run back too
(Kim Shin)
You have to come
Even if it takes a hundred years, even if it takes two hundred years
I’ll wait, for sure
[SHE SMILES SOFTLY]
[EUNTAK IS SOBBING]
[EUNTAK'S TREMBLING BREATH]
[FOOTSTEPS ECHO]
[A SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
[TREMBLING BREATH]
(Euntak)
See you again later
[Emotional music]
[The door slams shut]
[KIM SHIN IS ON THE VERGE OF CRYING]
[KIM SHIN'S TEARS]
[KIM SHIN'S TREMBLING BREATH]
(Kim Shin)
Loved and cherished
Goblin bride
Falls asleep here
[SOBBING]
[THE WAVES CRASH]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECTS]
(Grim Reaper)
The missing one from that day
[RAIN POURS DOWN]
Walked forever in someone's tears.
Times when I can't tell if it's day or night
Was swept away by the rain
It was a very long rainy season
As for the other missing persons
In this world where the guardian deity has vanished
They summoned the guardian deity again
And left them behind
The guardian deity, both desolate and radiant
Must have met their own mother
[SIGH]
(Student 1)
What’s that pin of yours?
You didn’t buy it with your own money, did you?
(Student 2)
Not me, it’s my dad's taste
(Student 1)
Then wear it only when your dad's around
Why do you go out wearing it?
I love my dad whether he's watching or not.
Can you just shut up and not care?
Ah, I don't even have a dad who can buy me a pin.
I don't know, alright?
[STUDENT 2'S AWKWARD BREATHING]
Hey, why do you take variety shows as documentaries?
What, what are you looking at, lady?
[FLUSTERED GROAN]
Kids these days are scary.
[scoffs]
What are you saying?
[SHE SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(Samshin)
Sweetie, I know that's how it is at that age,
but you don't have to be like that.
It's just because you guys are cute.
How is it that you’re so pretty?
[YOU SMILE SLIGHTLY]
I’m sorry
Should I give you more fish cake?
(Together)
Yes
[WE SMILE TOGETHER]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
(Eun-tak)
First love is meant to be unfulfilled anyway
It seems you loved a lot?
(Kim-shin)
I guess so
Seeing how hard it is to endure this
[A BIRD CHIRPS]
(Eun-tak)
No, I just miss you so much, it’s hard to breathe
It’s too dangerous
(Eun-tak) The woman
has forgotten everything.
It seems you still can't forget the representative.
(Kim Shin)
Yes
Not for a single day, not for a single moment
(Eun Tak)
But
It's not about pressing your head down like that
It's about gently petting it like this
[SHE SMILES SLIGHTLY]
This is the last list
(Reaper 2)
The long punishment
Is over
[THE REAPER'S SIGH]
(Reaper)
Is it one sheet?
(Reaper 2)
Yes
(Reaper)
Finally, the end of this long punishment
That's a period
Congratulations
(Reaper 2)
Rest in peace.
Go.
[A SIGH]
I owe you a lot.
Thank you.
[I’M CHOKED UP]
[I SMILE SLIGHTLY]
(The Grim Reaper)
There’s no need to dry anymore.
[SIGNIFICANT MUSIC]
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECTS]
"Kim Sun, 68 years old"
News
I was told you wouldn’t deliver it
[I SMILE SLIGHTLY]
The news has come.
It’s the last day at work.
Go well
Be well
In whatever form at whatever time
Be happy
You lived well during this time.
Don’t let it rain
Don’t worry.
Breaking up is my long-standing job.
When the laundry is done spinning, I hang it up a bit.
[I CHUCKLE]
[A SIGH]
After hanging it all up, come to the tea house.
I think I'll break the rules once more.
Since I'm going anyway,
[THE SCENERY RESONATES]
[THE DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
[I SMILE SLIGHTLY]
(Sunny)
Haven't aged a bit?
Still good-looking,
[I SMILE SLIGHTLY]
Have you been well?
(The Grim Reaper)
You said you wouldn't deliver news,
You just forgot,
That the man I met was the Grim Reaper.
(Sunny)
[Smiling slightly]
Did you think this news
would come this way?
I missed you
I knew that would happen
[SHE DIGS THROUGH HER POCKETS]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC]
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
(The Grim Reaper)
I wanted to fit you in properly at least once
I’m sorry for not fitting you in well
I missed you a lot
I knew that would happen
(The Grim Reaper)
Sunny, you
are the last soul I am guiding
I see
(Sunny)
Then what happens next?
What will happen to us?
Is this really a happy ending for us?
Sunny, this is
your third life, right?
How about you?
Well
this might
(Sunny)
be the last one
(Grim Reaper)
Your brother is here
outside
My brother still doesn't care
(Sunny)
I'm glad I can at least see your face like this
It's nice
It's thanks to having good friends
[SHE SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(Sunny)
Leaving my brother behind
I'm sorry for going first.
Take care, brother.
We'll meet again someday.
Be happy, our little one.
[THE DOOR CLANKS SHUT]
[FADING FOOTSTEPS]
[THE SOUND OF INSECTS CHIRPING]
(Kim Shin)
My sister
My friend
My bride
Has left.
And still
I remain all alone like this.
[A bird chirps]
[Approaching footsteps]
[MAN 4 SIGHS]
[MAN 4 SNIFFS]
[MAN 4 CRUMPLES A PLASTIC BAG]
[SNIFFING]
[A MAN IS SMACKING HIS LIPS]
(Man 4)
Cheer up
Do you know why there are two sandwiches?
It's because you’re supposed to share them
Don’t be polite, just take it
(Man 4)
In this vast world
is there not a place for us to write?
Come on
A young gentleman
must have been quite frustrated
But let's cheer up
There can also be a life that shines late
Isn’t that so?
[Cheerful music]
[Laughter of Man 4]
(Kim Shin)
In anyone's life
there are moments when God lingers.
When you are drifting away from the world
If someone pushed you toward the world
That is the moment when God
is staying by your side
(Man 4)
Then I'll go first
Hey, Mr. Kim
Don't say that, come this way
(Kim Shin)
There will be someone who needs your help
It's the cost of a sandwich
What would the chairman think if he sees this?
Yes, I guess I first realized that it's broken
(Man 4)
Shall I take a look?
Will you understand if you look?
It's been about 20 years since I've had only oil rice.
(Man 4)
Well
If you contact the insurance company, it would be faster
Why are you doing this?
(Secretary Kim)
Ah...
[Man 4 is clattering]
Did you contact the insurance company?
Ah, because the chairman opened the bonnet
I got distracted
[Mysterious music]
(Driver)
I'll do it right away
Maybe
[MAN 4 IS MAINTAINING THE CAR]
I guess I was trying to meet a new connection
Connection?
[SMILES SLIGHTLY]
You are romantic, sir
Yes, it's a bit like that
Well
[THE FOUR MEN RATTLE]
[PEOPLE ARE NOISY]
(Director)
Let's hurry up
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
"Kim Sun, Wang Ye"
(Kim Shin)
That day, while raising the lantern, I
wished that my sister from a distant life
and my lord from a distant life
would meet again in the afterlife
and that in the life we meet again, they would be happy
I prayed
[SIGH]
[THE ACTOR'S SCREAM]
(Actor)
What is this?
(Criminal Investigator)
When subduing a suspect, do it in one
go.
When putting on handcuffs, do it without mercy; accurately
inform them of their Miranda rights that they have the right to
remain silent and the right to refuse to make incriminating statements..
. (Actor) Hey, I asked what that
was. Is what I'm saying difficult?
You asked me to
demonstrate an
arrest scene, right?
No, did you ask me to show that to you? Did you want
me to do it? (Actor) The suspect is over there, look!
[Actor's angry breathing] (Criminal
Investigator) Oh, the suspect is over there?
You look so much like a criminal, I'm sorry.
[I UNFASTEN THE HANDCUFFS WITH A CLINK]
(Actor)
Damn
Isn’t it obvious that I look like a detective?
(Detective)
Even if you look again, even if you keep looking,
you still look like a criminal.
Is this person really
Where do I look like a criminal?
Did I steal your heart or something?
You clearly look like a madam at a gambling den.
(Detective)
From head to toe
I'm definitely a madam.
(Actor)
I'm currently undercover.
[Rolling the pronunciation]
Undercover
This is set in
a period drama from 2016...
[SIGH]
Ah, never mind, director, what's this person?
What's with the attitude towards me?
(Director)
Oh, I forgot to introduce him.
He's the detective from the violent crimes unit who is consulting with us.
This is Lee Hyuk from the Gangnam violent crimes unit.
(Actor)
Hyuk, what a big deal.
(Detective)
I can hear everything.
[HE EXHALES]
[AN AWKWARD LAUGH]
(Actor)
No, don’t misunderstand me.
I'm an actor, and I came here for a shoot.
[smiling slightly]
The staff didn't reserve a room, so
I had no choice but to come.
No choice.
[AWKWARD SMILE]
I'm the stylist.
[THE ACTOR SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(Motel owner)
There's only one room.
(Actor)
[smiling slightly]
Ah, really
Regardless of East or West,
there's always only one room
I can't help it, just give me that room.
[THE DETECTIVE'S SIGH]
(Detective)
Hurry up, please.
Oh, anyway, if I go out, my legs will just hurt.
Well, if my legs hurt, they'll get thicker.
I need to sleep early for my skin to be stable tomorrow.
Wait, why didn't I reserve a room for a female actress?
(Motel owner)
I didn't ask, you know?
Yes, here’s the key.
[THE ACTRESS CLEARS HER THROAT]
I’ll go first, stylist.
(Man 5)
Is there a room?
(Motel owner)
Oh, what should I do? There’s only one room.
(Actress)
Pretend you didn't hear.
I didn’t hear it.
[LAUGHTER]
So what are we?
What do you mean?
No, what, what Uh,
when are we going
to say 'let's date,' 'let's meet,' 'I
like you,' all that? Are we not going to?!
Do I have to do it first?
Then should I do it first?
I'm an actress, you know?
(Actress) It annoys
me that I liked you first.
Who says that? People say that just
because I liked you
first Isn't that right?
- No - What do you mean?
I liked you first.
(Criminal)
This is my statement...
Ah, no, this is my true feelings
[SOFT MUSIC]
(Actor)
Ha, really
If I had been just a little late
I would have fallen for you first
Try reaching out your hand
What is it?
(Actor)
Do you think it's like handcuffs?
[In a small voice]
You stole my heart just now
Look, there's a lion here?
They say it's the reaper of the violent crime squad
Isn't this a bribe?
Either arrest me or something, then
[SNICKERS]
Then from today, we're one day in
(Butler)
Where are you going, my lord?
(Kim Shin)
I was thinking of going for a walk
(Butler)
Please avoid the main road
Students from Korea are traveling
It's a bit noisy
(Kim Shin)
I will be back
(Butler)
Yes, my lord
[THE BIRDS ARE CHIRPING]
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECTS]
[CALM MUSIC]
I found it
(Kim Shin)
Where is the sorrow that lasts a thousand years?
Where is the love that lasts a thousand years
I vote for 'exists'
(Kim Shin)
Which side will you take?
Is it sadness or love?
Sad love
[EUN-TAK SLIGHTLY SMILES]
(Eun-tak)
Uncle
You know who I am, right?
My first and last
Goblin bride
[LAUGHTER]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
Subtitle: Choi Hye-ran