[THEME SONG]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
Wow, this is my second time here
At this rate, it's going to become my regular spot
(Euntak)
We sat over there back then
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
[FOOTSTEPS ECHO]
[English]
Welcome to Quebec
Please take a seat
[FOOTSTEPS ECHO]
(Euntak)
[Korean]
So, well, you should have visited a foreign country
(Sunny)
So why all of a sudden go abroad at this age?
When I was twenty-nine
I didn't even go to the supermarket in front of my house
- (Euntak) Really?
- (Sunny) Yeah, I didn't have any plans
(Euntak)
But I don't look like a first-time foreign visitor
And I'm doing really well
A little lost but not starving
And I'll eat a huge piece of beef
I came to a nice restaurant with some guy
(Sunny)
So what if the restaurant is nice?
The guy has to be nice
I'm sleepy, I'm hanging up
Yeah, sleep well
[A FAMILIAR BREATHING SOUND]
Boss, over here
[CLINKING SOUNDS]
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECTS]
[HEAVY MUSIC]
(Kim Shin)
At twenty-nine, you
Are still shining
But beside you
I am not
My life has ultimately
Ended immortality
After my death
You, sitting behind that time
Your life, in which I have vanished
Has forgotten me and has perfectly completed
I must disappear
[A SPARKLING SOUND EFFECT]
For your pretty smile
The choice I have to make
Is to end this life
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
In the end, I
Made that choice.
[THE BIRD IS CHIRPING]
(The Grim Reaper)
We need to look human, so let’s walk.
[SOUND OF A CAR REMOTE CONTROL ACTIVATING]
(Deokhwa)
Let’s get in.
If you’re human, you can’t walk to Incheon.
(The Grim Reaper)
Ah.
[DEOKHWA'S SIGH]
(Sunny's friend)
But can I really come out with you?
I was told to come out with my friend too.
A man should
see his true self when he's with friends.
They won’t match their words and will make mistakes.
That mistake is the man's true form.
The car door suddenly
opens. Even if I make a mistake.
(Sunny's friend)
I wish I could meet those kinds of guys
Sigh, what kind of girl would those guys date?
In the car, in clothes, in watches, oh, even the face
Gosh, some girl must be lucky
Oh, good
[SIGH]
[THERE'S A KNOCK SOUND]
[FADING FOOTSTEPS]
[SIGH]
[THE DOOR OPENS WITH A CLICK]
Draw your sword, now
[TOUCHING MUSIC]
Please
What’s the sudden appearance...
You knocked just a moment ago but didn’t answer
I came out to answer
I want to stop now
What do you mean?
The thought that I could choose
The choice I eventually made earlier, that one?
What does that mean?
What exact choice
are you talking about?
Just the answer, no questions
I’m sorry
But for that,
my investigation isn’t finished yet
What investigation?
I looked up the uncle's name, on the internet
(Euntak)
Life, achievements, all that
There was nothing.
It's as if someone erased everything from the beginning.
The uncle told me before
If you find something from me
You will end up blaming me a lot
That something was a sword, and I discovered it
Uncle, I don't blame you, but
Given that you said I would blame you
That means there's still something left
So
That sword
The person I believed would never do such a thing
Said that, right?
Uncle, by any chance
Did something bad happen, and is it erased from history?
If it’s about being punished for doing bad things
It feels a bit odd to unsheathe the sword
Sir, um, did you perhaps commit treason...
Such things?
[A FAINT SIGH]
[GENTLE MUSIC]
[THE ENEMY COLLAPSES HEAVILY]
[A SOLDIER SWIFTLY STRIKES WITH A SWORD]
Oh
You're right, what you said
It was a life busy just surviving
Times that were not recorded in history
I struggled hard, but
Even death was not honorable
[TENSE SOUND EFFECTS]
(Kim Shin)
Just because I move toward the king
nothing will improve
[AN ARROW FLIES BY SWIFTLY]
But I moved forward
and with each step I take
[AN ARROW FLIES BY SWIFTLY]
Innocent lives have been lost
[SOLDIERS SLASH WITH THEIR SWORDS]
[FOOTSTEPS ECHO]
My sins have not been forgiven
and now I am being punished
This sword
is that punishment
(Kim Shin)
But
even if it's punishment
Isn't it a lot if you received 900 years?
No.
It can't be a punishment.
(Euntak)
God wouldn't have given such a power as a punishment.
If the uncle had been really bad,
if the uncle had been really bad,
he would only have made goblins exist.
He wouldn't have let me meet a goblin bride
or made me pull out that sword.
I don't know what kind of being he was,
but the uncle is loved, really.
[HE SOBS]
The bad thing I mentioned is...
Loving the king's woman
So it was a version like 'let's confine her'
What, something like that
I'm sorry for talking about treason
[SNIFFING]
Well then now
Could you make me pretty?
Yes
- (Eun-tak) That won't do
- Right, good thought...
Huh?
(Eun-tak)
Oh, that's bad
Uncle, have you lived with that thought every day for 900 years?
Then it must have been desperate for 900 years every day?
[Sobbing]
Uncle, that's so pathetic
No...
[Eun-tak sniffles]
[Sniffling] Can't you be a bit more
consistent with your words and actions?
I'm sad and I'm crying, but what can I
do if you keep saying that empty-handed?
(Euntak) Don't you think you're not
trying hard enough to look good, uncle?
- What did you say?
- You heard me
(Euntak) I know it’s pitiful,
but when you're feeling sorry for
someone, it's better to have
[SOMETHING CERTAIN RATHER THAN JUST SYMPATHY]
[THE CLOCK IS RINGING]
Sniffles. I think it's time
for me to go to work.
Hey, while I'm gone to
work, please think about it carefully.
What I want
(Euntak)
You're more pitiful than I am
[Sobbing]
I'll scold you thoroughly
Oh, no, what is it that you want?
Is it money, a house, jewels, something like that?
Is that really it?
[SIGH]
Then could it be
That thing I said I would do if you needed it?
What, love?
(Euntak)
Are you not thinking of buying a house full of jewels with money
And filling it with love?
[Playful music]
You go, hurry, go to work!
(Euntak)
I already said this
Maybe it's because you're a former god
It seems you’re not good at memorizing
(Kim Shin)
Hey, is there a hierarchy of jobs?
Isn't that job discrimination?
[THE DOOR OPENS WITH A CLICK]
[SIGH]
You comfort me and cry with me
But you don't offer a black card?
How could such a conclusion come about
In the midst of that sadness?
[A FAMILIAR BREATH]
CEO, over here
[SMILING SLIGHTLY]
In the meantime, I encountered the CEO.
Dying is dying
(Kim Shin)
Boss?
[Kim Shin's exasperated sigh]
(Eun-tak)
Here
"Here"?
[Exasperated sigh]
[SIGH]
[Cheerful music starts playing]
(Sunny)
This is a makeup artist
I'm self-employed
If I may ask, what is your friend's occupation?
(Duk-hwa)
Not a friend, but a younger sibling
And my occupation is the third generation chaebol
So I guess I’m being punished
By you, that punishment
I am Yu Deok-hwa.
(Sunny's friend)
Ah, yes
(Sunny)
How about you?
What kind of work do you do?
[EXCITING MUSIC]
[AWKWARD BREATHING SOUNDS]
Do you not have a job?
It's a kind of service job
(Grim Reaper)
Details are... due to the nature of the work...
I hope you understand
Ah, then do you have a name today?
[THE PLEASANT BREATH OF THE GRIM REAPER]
[Clears throat]
Kim Woo-bin
(Sunny's friend)
They said service job, must be a waiter
I can hear everything, girl
[SUNNY'S COUGH]
(Sunny)
Do you have a business card? Please give it to me, I'll come visit
Ah, how many business cards
I guess I need to have something every time
(Reaper)
If you let me know in advance
- I will prepare next time...
- (Sunny's friend) Huh?
- (Sunny) Why?
- (Sunny's friend) Look, look
(Sunny)
[surprised]
Huh?
Was he really a chaebol?
[DEOK-HWA'S LAUGH]
(Deok-hwa)
Yes, it turns out I was born into it
[Sunny's friend's exclamation]
Looks like I'm seeing someone in successor training.
(Sunny's friend) Oh, have some
seolleongtang I
can see you're not
picky about food
(Sunny) I didn't
realize, having a lot of money, being
tall, young, and
handsome I only see
that in fantasies, so I call you Sunny.
[YOUR NAME IS REALLY COOL. IT'S
THE BREATH OF ADMIRATION FOR SUNNY]
You too, Sunny, are cool,
your name (Sunny) Wow,
you have great taste.
[Sunny's friend's laughter]
You understand it all at once [tense
music] (Sunny's
friend) But doesn't
it feel a bit dark here for some reason?
I'll go first - Go ahead -
That's what you should say.
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
I’ll go first.
You too.
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
I’ll go first.
(Grim Reaper)
Forget everything I just said.
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[SUNNY'S PUZZLED MOAN]
[A SIGH]
(Sunny)
Huh? Where did everyone go?
They said they had busy things to do and left first.
(Sunny)
What did they do that made them both leave?
She’s not normally like that.
I’m not at all, oh my, really.
(Grim Reaper)
I’ll give you this.
It's okay.
You picked it up first.
Woorbin paid for it.
It suits you better.
Okay, I’ll accept it.
(Sunny)
Since I got the ring, can you give me your number?
(Grim Reaper)
The number I called you from yesterday...
(Sunny)
Not Woorbin, but the heir from a conglomerate.
My friend took his business card, so
I don’t know his contact number.
It’s a bit awkward to ask him.
If he really is the Yudeokhwa of Cheonwoo Group,
He is my lord.
Your lord?
The owner of the building.
(Sunny)
So, can I get the number?
I have quite a bit to say
Just a moment
[CLEARS THROAT]
(Sunny)
Let me see, I'll do it faster...
[PLAYFUL MUSIC]
Did you just throw that?
To someone who wants to help?
Ah, I just got flustered, thank you
Thank you
[SUNNY'S BEWILDERED BREATHING]
Got it
What's the pattern? Or is it a password?
There’s nothing like that
(Sunny)
You really have a lot that’s missing every time
[SNICKERS]
Are you acquainted with the goblin and his spouse?
Ah, well, unintentionally
What is this goblin's occupation? The restaurant business?
The goblin I know owns a rice cake shop
Ah, the goblin I know
has just a lot of jobs
[SUNNY'S SMILE]
He's really a strange person
[SUNNY CHUCKLES SLIGHTLY]
[SUNNY'S SMILE]
[THE DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES QUIETLY]
[HE EXHALES]
[A SIGH]
Does human medicine actually work?
I tried choosing between alcohol and medicine
Did you have a good time?
You're drinking
(Reaper)
They say you're a strange person
There's not much, is there, for me
Especially business cards
You really deceived well, not even a person
Is it mania or depression?
It's pain
(Kim Shin)
You just broke the rules
[Majestic music]
It's like a side effect of interfering with human life and death
(Kim Shin)
There’s also a way to die as per the original name
If needed, do that too
I love you
The words my mouth spat out
All come back to me again
The side effects related to
human life and death are too great.
(Kim Shin)
As a big person, there's no end to how useless I am.
(Grim Reaper)
Just tall, that's all.
If you've lived this long,
You might as well not say the things
that you can't take back.
Is it worth dying?
There's no death that's worth dying.
Is that true?
(Grim Reaper)
The problem is that there's always an exception.
[A SIGH FROM THE GRIM REAPER]
I thought you would laugh.
Why did you take the medicine?
What happened with the other missing people?
No, just
talking about this and that, I ended up
crying, they said I was pitiful, so I had
expectations (Kim Shin)
Well, I did cry because I
was sad, but they said they wouldn't let me go
black
Ah, what, was it just them who cried?
[The Reaper's sigh]
Did you cry? In front of
the other missing ones?
(Kim Shin) It was slightly to the
side, it was slanted [The Reaper's sigh]
Pathetic (The Reaper)
You're done
now, girls are picky and won't make
eye contact
They like indifferent
guys, where are those tears from, oh dear
(Kim Shin)
So you cried as soon as you saw me?
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
Drink, alcohol
[SIGH]
You need to make a decision quickly
Whether to be hated or liked
You're not some Hamlet
That Shakespeare guy, really
(Kim Shin)
He just wrote such a masterpiece
[THE GRIM REAPER COUGHS]
Are you feeling very unwell? Do you want to go to the hospital?
Can it be cured?
(Grim Reaper)
Don't you know the placebo effect?
If you at least get some counseling...
My sword started to hurt
(Kim Shin)
If God really
only gives trials
that can be endured
[SIGH]
(Kim Shin)
I wonder if I've been overestimated
[SIGH]
Do you want to cuddle as a quick fix?
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
Well, if you really dislike it that much
[SHARP SOUND EFFECT]
(Grim Reaper)
Oh dear, it's chaotic, stop it
[SHARP SOUND EFFECT]
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
(Sunny)
Hmm, still beautiful
It's definitely mine
Did you buy a ring?
No, the guy gave it to me, that
guy (Euntak) Whoa, the
guy from the overpass?
Did you meet him?
When? How was it?
He’s still good-looking
and still strange, even
though it feels strange
I keep forgetting when
[I SEE HIS FACE, THE SOUND
OF RESPONDING MOANS]
(Euntak) But this really looks
[LIKE AN OLD RING, EXCITING MUSIC]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
(Ghost 1) Once,
I also received it,
revenge on that bastard for the ring,
bloody revenge [mysterious sound
effects] Hey, even
ghosts have ups and
downs, don't they? (Ghost
2) Let me go first, just a bit.
Oh my, my poor child, what should I do?
[Mysterious sound effect]
[THE GHOST 2 IS CRYING SORROWFULLY]
So, here's the thing
Can you ask the goblin
for the lottery numbers, huh?
You said you would help at my goshiwon, right?
[TENSE SOUND EFFECT]
If I could find out the lottery numbers this time
and let you know, and you buy one ticket
it would be really nice
[THE DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
(Euntak)
I’m back
[EUNTAK'S HURRIED BREATHING]
Do you know, sir?
Just by being yourself
you become a role model
[A HOLLOW LAUGH]
The way you always keep books close
is so cool
(Euntak)
I should follow your example
Wow, how can you fit
the universe into just one watch?
Art is sitting on your wrist
So, here's what I want to say
Do you happen to know this week's lottery winning numbers?
Why do you need the lottery numbers?
[A SIGH]
If I know this week's lottery winning numbers
I think I'll have time to take out the sword
(Kim Shin)
4, 10, 14, 15, 18, 22
[HUMOROUS MUSIC]
Thank you
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[SNIFFING]
(Euntak)
Oh, you surprised me
Were you following me?
It's a pursuit.
You're revealing a secret
(Euntak)
That grandmother is okay
She lived really kindly
so she's allowed to receive this much fortune
What does it matter if a ghost knows the lottery numbers
They say it appears in children's dreams to tell them
(Euntak)
Then I'll just go to the library
There's not much time left until the college entrance exam
Ten pages.
Minors can't buy lottery tickets.
What?
Oh, where is such a law?
There is definitely such a law, student.
- Ten tickets.
- ID, please.
[Comical music]
Oh, I...
[QUICKLY GRABS A PIECE OF PAPER]
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
(Euntak)
Mister.
[EUNTAK'S HEAVY BREATHING]
This, this is a real secret.
Since this is a really big deal,
I'm telling you.
In this world, there is something called a guardian deity.
This is the moment when the
guardian deity resides in the uncle's life.
You have to believe it
[EUNTAK'S ROUGH BREATHING]
Sir
So, this is it, right?
Today’s lottery first prize winning numbers
I’ll pay for it, so
you just buy it
and we’ll split it right down the middle, okay?
Cool
(Clerk)
Get out!
[EUNTAK'S STRAINED BREATHING]
[EUNTAK'S ROUGH BREATHING]
Oh, oh, it’s real, oh, it really is
Oh, there’s no time
- Is this a library?
- (Euntak) It’s real...
[EUNTAK'S SURPRISED BREATH]
This is the last supermarket on the way to
the library, so I stopped by to buy some
milk, but I heard he bought a lottery ticket instead?
What, does he know
everything every day, this guy?
(Eun-Tak) Yeah, I used that
kid, but I couldn't buy it, okay?
[Sighs] I wonder if
Grandma's son bought it.
He probably couldn't because
he was too busy working
without time to sleep
He couldn't even dream.
Oh, what should we do? He
should have been put to sleep.
(Eun-Tak) This year's farming
hasn't gone well, you know.
It's only raining in
Seoul, only in Seoul!
(Kim Shin)
Not all the rain is dropped by me
Absolute power requires etiquette
Ah, what do you mean?
This week, there wasn't a first place winner,
so the amount will be carried over to next week
So what are you saying?
They were an honest and good couple
You will have a very strange dream
The guardian deity treats you
Really?
Then
Will it be right next week?
Oh, that's kind of cool?
Anyway, you won't be able to buy next week either,
so why are you happy?
What, will I not be able to buy it forever?
[Cheerful music]
(Eun Tak)
In two months, I will be twenty years old
Saturdays come every week, and Saturday nights are nice
Rokkabee, Tokkabee, bang!
(Kim Shin)
Hey, don't act like you know, oh my
(Eun Tak)
Huh? Oh!
Wow, you really got it all right
You got it all right
[THE CLERK COLLAPSES]
Huh? Sir, are you okay?
(Ghost 2)
Oh, is it real? Oh, what should I do?
Thank you, really thank you
[EUN TAK SMILES SLIGHTLY]
I will tell the uncle.
[Soft music]
But why hasn't that kid from the goshiwon been seen lately?
(Ghost 2)
Because of you, that's why I went there.
[Shimmering sound effect]
Release everything you have.
Then, grandma...
Oh dear.
[GHOST 2 SMILES A LITTLE]
(Ghost 2)
Hey, hey, you too.
You need to be happy with the goblin, okay?
[SMILES A LITTLE]
[GHOST 2 SMILES A LITTLE]
[EXHALES A BREATH]
[THE DOOR CREAKS OPEN AND SHUT]
Cheers!
[SHE SMILES SLIGHTLY]
[THE GRIM REAPER IS SIPPING A DRINK]
(Euntak)
Uncle
Can I meet a god if I die?
[While sipping the drink]
Why?
I just want to ask a few things.
(Euntak)
Goblin,
I feel like you're too lonely of a guardian spirit.
People might not know,
but when you are drifting away from the world,
someone pushes you back towards it.
But I know,
So I'm trying to take the sword from you.
[CALM MUSIC]
What?
Become prettier without the sword
so you can be a more brilliant guardian
Hey, Euntak, no, any other missing person
(the Grim Reaper)
You shouldn't be in a position to worry about others right now
If your utility value or whatever disappears
you could be kicked out
Are you okay?
What is this, is it mine?
(Euntak)
Life
is originally just something borrowed for a moment
and you pass by for a short while
Hell
isn’t just found in hell
(Aunt Euntak)
Where's your mom's insurance money?!
[THE RAIN IS POURING DOWN]
Stop the nonsense and bring it here, if you don't want to get beat up.
(Euntaek's aunt)
Are you going to repay the grace that you raised me with like this?
Like this, like this, like this!
[Euntaek's painful groan]
But I was happy every day when I came to this house.
It's like I had a glimpse of heaven?
So, I want to repay you.
(Euntaek)
I don't know exactly what it means to become pretty,
but when I see the grim reaper pulling out that sword,
I can tell it's a good thing for him,
[AND I SLIGHTLY SMILE]
[AWKWARD BREATHING]
[Heavy music]
[Pedestrian signal sound]
[PEDESTRIAN SIGNAL SOUND]
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
Huh? Grandma
(Child 1)
Hello
(Three gods)
Shh
[SLIGHTLY SMILES]
[ECG beep]
[Child 2's rapid breathing]
[RAPID BREATHING]
Is it time to stop hurting now?
(Three gods)
It hurt a lot
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
Mom is worried
[SLIGHTLY SMILES]
(Three gods)
Be good
[THE SCENERY RESONATES]
(Woman)
If I am reborn again
I want to be Kim Tae-hee...
[SHE SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(Man 1)
Hey, are you crazy, me?
To be reborn and meet you again?
Honestly, I'm so tired of you
[Man 1's surprised moan]
You bastard, damn
Where do I go now?
You can go out through the door you came in
The afterlife is a U-turn
[MAN 2 CLINKS HIS CANE]
[MAN 2 TAPS HIS CANE]
[THE DOG BARKS]
[CALM MUSIC]
(Man 2)
Happy?
[THE DOG BARKS]
I wonder if it was heavy on your mind that you went first
I've been waiting since a while ago
The road is something Happy knows well
[HE TAPS HIS CANE]
[THE DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
Ms. Kim Mi-young
is the team leader
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
[APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS]
This footstep sound
[A STARTLED BREATH]
[THE SOUND OF FOOTSTEPS ECHOES]
(Grim Reaper)
Oh, oh, oh, no
[TENSE MUSIC]
Oh, what to do, what to do
Uh, Kim Mi-young, uh, hey...
(Grim Reaper)
Damn it
[Mysterious sound effect]
[SUNNY'S IRRITATED BREATHING]
(Sunny)
Ah, why the hell isn’t this person answering the phone?
Is it even possible to meet if the phone doesn’t work?
What kind of person are they, anyway?
(Grim Reaper)
I am the Grim Reaper
[Sunny's sigh]
The Grim Reaper moves on command
Sometimes the person I believe to be Sun-hee
Is seen as Sunny by someone else.
Should I really kill this bastard?
(Sunny) Ah, I’m so mad,
oh, is it supposed to hurt
my pride and make me
obsess over someone like this?
He’s a man who drives people
crazy, damn, just wait until
I get my hands on him. [Mobile
phone manipulation sound]
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
[SUNNY'S ANNOYED BREATH]
[MOBILE PHONE RINGTONE]
[A GASP OF SURPRISE]
[THE REAPER'S URGENT GROAN]
[MOBILE PHONE MANIPULATION SOUND]
[SUNNY'S PUZZLED BREATH]
(Sunny) What is it,
scaring me like that!
[TSK, HEAVY BREATHING]
[Tense music] [Sunny’s scream]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
[SUNNY'S CURIOUS BREATH]
[A STARTLED BREATH]
[SUNNY'S SURPRISED MOAN]
[SUNNY'S FRIGHTENED BREATH]
[SUNNY'S SCREAM]
(Euntak)
The chicken is out, enjoy your meal
(Customers)
Thank you
[THE DOOR SWINGS OPEN]
[SUNNY'S RAPID BREATH]
(Euntak)
Boss, is there something wrong?
[SUNNY'S ROUGH BREATH]
Part-timer
Do you believe in ghosts or something like that?
(Euntak)
What?
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
No, oh, well, boss, really
Where in the world are there ghosts?
(Sunny)
Right? There can't be such a thing as ghosts?
Of course
(Euntak)
People who say they've seen ghosts
that's all made-up stories
But why do you say that?
No, I've just experienced something strange
[SUNNY'S RAPID BREATH]
(Sunny)
Oh, by the way
Part-timer, don't come in for a while
Why?
I saw the news, the college entrance exam is coming up
Just focus on that, get a perfect score.
If I get a hundred points, I can't go to college, boss
Really?
Then just make a few mistakes
Just a couple of the hardest ones
[SLIGHTLY SMILES]
Yes
(Eun-tak)
While I go to that part-time job
Think about it well
What I might want
As long as I live in this house
Please be happy
If that's what you want above all
That would be quite awkward
[HEAVY MUSIC]
(Kim-shin)
Life walks towards me
Death walks towards me
With life, Sarro, you are
I walk on without getting tired.
Then I
end up saying this
I am not sad
This is enough
It has become so
(Euntak)
What are you doing here?
Can't you see me?
I saw you
What?
Your coming
Oh, that long? Oh, that's a bit touching
(Euntak)
But does it feel different if you look that long?
Or is it still the same?
What?
(Euntak)
You said that before, that I couldn't be seen.
My twenties, thirties
Is it still like that for me?
(Kim Shin)
Yeah
You can’t see it
Usually, you can see at least a bit of fortune or misfortune
I see
I guess it's because I'm a missing person
(Eun Tak)
My existence was really boring, but now it’s become special
As I create it
That will be my future
Don’t worry, I’m not always sick
I’m now humbly accepting my fate
I’m a spirited bride of a goblin living boldly
[I CHUCKLE]
But I'm really curious
What is it?
My twenties, my thirties
Will it keep growing like this?
Huh?
(Kim Shin)
It will keep being beautiful like this
How do you know?
You might hate it for a day or two
It could be a month or two
(Eun Tak)
But
Mister, when you do that guardian deity thing
Is there a standard?
No
Just my feelings day by day?
I mostly help the child among adults and kids
[HEAVY MUSIC]
(Kim Shin)
The hand that first reached out to me, who was about to drift away from the world
was that of a child
(Child 3)
[Sobbing]
Grandpa
Please accept my bow
From now on, I will take care of you
(Eun-tak)
Um
Then why did my mom help back then?
She was an adult?
At that time, I was drunk
and my heart was weak
And what your mom asked for help
was not for herself
(Eun-tak)
The one who answered the plea for help was you, uncle.
It feels like a miracle all over again
[SOFT MUSIC]
I like it
[AND I SMILE SLIGHTLY]
[I SNIFFLE]
(Euntak)
But you know
it's not about pressing your head down hard
it's about gently petting it
[I SMILE SLIGHTLY]
(Kim Shin)
I guess it's today
A day or two of feeling annoyed
Oh, me...
[I SNIFF]
Stand there, okay?
(Euntak)
Ah, when a person teaches something...
[THE DOOR CLICKS SHUT]
[EUNTAK'S SURPRISED BREATH]
(Euntak)
Wow, what is this?
(Kim Shin)
Tree
That's not what I was asking
Did you do this, sir?
Just to prune it, and also to cut something
You did it all by yourself with those little hands?
(Kim Shin)
Yeah
These two hands need a rest, so I guess I'll be going
(Euntak)
Sir
I'm sorry for only thinking about myself during this time
I was really worried that I might get kicked out
And while I was begging you to not take it away, it was also kind of fun.
The uncle has become pretty.
I was also wondering
what would happen if he met another woman.
Doesn't he say 'no'?
Should I?
Oh, that's petty.
Well, I didn't expect anything.
Anyway, I have already come to a conclusion.
I will make you pretty.
(Eun-tak)
A good person's request, like that of the uncle,
can't lead to a bad outcome.
Where do you want to become pretty?
In front of a pretty tree?
W, right now?
Yes, why?
Today, right away?
(Eun-tak)
Yes, even a ram goes down when it gets hot.
(Kim Shin)
I got a call, I got a call
Hello?
Ah, oh, I'm going now, okay
No
[The door closes tightly]
You were holding your phone upside down?
[THE SCENERY RESONATES]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
(The Grim Reaper)
What’s going on, are you dead?
(Kim Shin)
It’s a rehearsal, do you have any alcohol?
What’s the matter?
He says he’ll draw the sword
[A FAINT SIGH]
He doesn’t know exactly, right?
What it means
He couldn’t say it.
I think he really likes me.
I'm worried, are we
joking or fighting?
(Kim Shin) Hey, you don't
know, but he really likes
me. The moment he saw
me, he said, 'I love you,'
'I'll come to your house.' Do you
know how embarrassed I was?
[HE HASN'T GOT A CLUE,
LAUGHING LIKE A GRIM REAPER]
He has no reason not to like me (grim
reaper) Why not?
What's the age gap?
Once he goes to college,
there'll be so many
handsome young guys.
900 years? What's that?
Why do you keep reducing
my age? I'm 939 years old!
Hey, actually, I'm a fast learner.
Originally, I'm a year younger.
[WE LAUGH TOGETHER]
Ah, I shouldn't be laughing.
[KIM SHIN'S SIGH]
Better than alcohol.
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
Should I try to distance myself again?
[Sighing]
That kid is the only one who can kill me.
But that kid keeps making me live.
Isn't it funny?
Don't get confused.
You lived well even when she wasn't around.
Did I?
But why can't I keep remembering that time?
[GENTLE MUSIC]
(Euntak)
Are you a goblin, uncle?
Are you really a guardian deity, uncle?
You're a ghost, aren't you, uncle?
I'm glad to meet you, uncle.
So does that mean you're not leaving now, uncle?
I'm going to get married now, to you, uncle.
(Euntak)
From now on, every time it rains,
I'll think you must be feeling gloomy, uncle.
What on earth gives you the right to judge whether I'm valuable or not, uncle?
I don't need you, you know.
Uncle!
(Euntak)
The red carpet is a hit, you did it, right, uncle?
It's totally amazing.
Uncle
(Kim Shin)
Stop calling me
Please stop calling me, Ji Eun-tak
Let me go
[THERE'S A KNOCK ON THE DOOR]
(Eun-tak)
Uncle
Are you sick?
"Jungang High School"
[CAR HORN]
[A WELCOME LAUGH]
[THE CAR DOOR OPENS WITH A THUD]
(Loan Shark 1)
What if the student leaves the house?
[The car door closes with a thud]
It's dangerous
Auntie is worried, hurry up and get in
(Loan Shark 2)
Uncles are rough, get in quickly
(Loan Shark 1)
Stop
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC]
What is it, again?
Ah, this is for you, hyung (Loan Shark
1) Did you just step on my shadow?
Why, does it hurt?
(Loan Shark 2) Are
you going to hit me hard?
Let's talk, in this case, I want to take off my
rank
and have a real match (Loan Shark 1)
Oh
my, this is really
[Loan Shark 2's puzzled groan]
Hey, yeah, go ahead
and sue, where to, huh?
Let’s see if it goes
to trial—oh, come on,
hey (Loan Shark 2)
You don’t even know the law, what? Law?
- (Secretary Kim) Do you know any loan sharks?
- Ah, surprise
[THE LOAN SHARKS ARE FIGHTING AMONGST THEMSELVES]
Hello
Ah, well, I suppose everyone knows at least one loan shark...
[THE LOAN SHARKS CONTINUE TO ARGUE]
(Eun-tak)
What are you saying?
[SCREAMS OF LOAN SHARK 2]
[Slightly smiling]
I'm just curious
Do you know who I am?
Rather than knowing, I’ve seen you
following Deok-hwa oppa
(Secretary Kim)
Ah
But how do you know those people are loan sharks?
I used to be a loan shark myself
(Eun-tak)
What?
(Secretary Kim)
Deok-hwa is late
Let’s go in my car
What kind of grown loan sharks are fighting in front of a girls' high school?
(Secretary Kim)
Good work
This is in front of Joongang Girls' High School
So there’s someone even more interesting
(Loan Shark 1)
What is this kind of situation?
- (Loan Shark 2) What, what, what! Damn
- (Loan Shark 1) Oh my...
(Police)
Stop, stop, stop!
Do you know where this is, you people, tsk
Sit properly
So you two just fought?
Of all places, in front of the girls' school, without
any strange intentions, yes, this guy just has to
drive
He keeps going there, it's all because of you,
man then you should have stopped him before going
Why
are you causing a fuss now? Damn it (Loan Shark 1)
Damn...
Look at this, it makes people angry, I'm
getting pissed off too Answer me, okay?
Why did you fight, in the first place?
Aren't you guys on the same side?
(Loan Shark 1) Yes, but these days it's strange
We've been fighting like that among ourselves
The other day, we fought and I was in the hospital for two weeks, you know?
But as soon as I got better, we fought again.
(Loan shark 2)
It doesn't affect our health; we just fight among ourselves.
Are these guys for real? This is crazy.
That's right, we fight like it's not a joke.
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC]
(Reaper)
It's the two of them fighting.
They'll never reconcile for life, by the way.
What are these guys?
(Loan shark 2)
It's no joke.
[CLEARS THROAT]
(Eun-tak)
I really like Deok-hwa oppa.
He's kind and warm-hearted.
He keeps his promises well.
Calculates accurately.
Unlike a typical third-generation chaebol,
he's really down-to-earth and simple.
(Secretary Kim)
Yes.
(Eun-tak)
He often gives me encouraging words that really help.
For example?
I'm sorry.
(Secretary Kim)
Yes.
[HUMMING]
[SNICKERS]
I’m back.
[EUN-TAK IS BRISKLY CLIMBING UP THE STAIRS]
[EUN-TAK'S FRUSTRATED SIGH]
That's something I taught you.
[Kim Shin clanks the plate down]
Eye contact in front of a woman.
(Eun-tak)
Mr. Goblin, is there something going on these days?
(Grim Reaper)
I don't know.
I just don't remember anything from the past.
(Eun-tak)
What past are you talking about?
Did you leave your thoughts with me?
How would I know that person's thoughts?
But it seems like you do.
I don't know, just peel some garlic.
Before you call the name three times.
[TENSION-BUILDING SOUND EFFECT]
I'm sorry.
(Grim Reaper)
Just 100 years ago
I called your name three times
These days it's become convenient
Even if I call just once, the deceased can hear
That must be quite hard for you
(Grim Reaper)
Do you think I'm struggling because of someone?
Meanwhile, the one who has been left out
Shall I chop all the garlic?
[Eun-tak's awkward smile]
[Eun-tak swirls the water]
[CUTS THE GARLIC]
The Goblin
Actually, due to the quick reincarnation
I'm one year younger than my original age
(Eun-tak)
What?
What I can say is all of this
Do your best
[EUNTAK'S SMILE]
(Euntak)
But you know
When I first met you, sir
I was nine years old, right?
And when we met again
I was nineteen, right?
When I was nine
I got lucky because of my mom, let’s say
When I was nineteen
How did you know to find me?
[A SIGH]
Nine, nineteen, twenty-nine
(Grim Reaper)
Just before being complete
is when it's the most precarious
What does that mean?
[Sigh] [Slams the sword down]
Shall I tell you a secret?
Yes
(The Grim Reaper) You're
twenty-nine years old [Mysterious music]
I'm going to meet the grim reaper.
Even if it's not me.
That's the fate of other missing persons.
This world needs order,
and nine is the number of gods and a complete number.
Since it's the closest unfinished number to ten.
Do well in this too.
Why are you looking at me like that? What's the secret?
I had a good dream that day.
Oh, I could have been promoted.
(Euntak)
Ah, what is it?
Laundry.
You finish this, uncle.
[THE DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
(Euntak)
Uncle.
Why?
I really don't know who's in a hurry here.
Can you see me now?
Oh
Are you angry with me or something?
Why would I be?
(Eun-tak)
I'm not angry, so why would I be angry?
What on earth are you getting angry about from ages ago?
Why do I feel like I'm just accumulating mileage?
(Kim-shin)
When have I ever?
I can see you right now, can't I?
Who do you think you are?
What on earth are you doing calling me all the time, making a fuss?
Why do you keep making me feel awkward?
(Kim Shin)
Why do you keep confusing me? Who do you think you are?
I wish you had drawn your sword when I asked you to
because that is your value
[Calm music]
No, I...
So
I said I'll draw the sword for you?
Not saying anything and not responding was
by the old man
I thought maybe you were waiting for the first snow
Because that was the original promise
(Eun Tak)
That's enough
You live forever, so I don't know if you have spare time
But I am an ordinary human,
and time is money.
When will we wait until?
I'm busy with studies and part-time work too
- Tomorrow
- (Eun-tak) Why today?
I'm free today
(Kim Shin)
I don't want today, tomorrow
Today is such a nice day
I want to go for a walk with you
[The sky rumbles]
(Kim Shin)
Tomorrow
(Eun-tak)
Ah, why again?
Before heading to school, just bang!
(Kim Shin)
Today the weather is really bad
I have to pick you up later
(Kim Shin)
Tomorrow
One more day
Ah, why again today?
Just one more day
Do you think I can do it barehanded? Hmph
Nari
[HEAVY MUSIC]
[SOBBING]
Please forgive me
[Kim Shin's sigh]
[The subordinate's trembling moan]
I will soon come to see you
[The subordinate's straining moan]
[The subordinate stabs deeply with a knife]
[KIM SHIN'S WEARY GROAN]
[THE SUBORDINATE IS SOBBING]
[THE SOLDIERS' SHOUT]
[AN ARROW FLIES SWIFTLY]
[KIM SUN COLLAPSES]
[A SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
(Kim Shin) It's frustrating that
I can't find the people I owe.
If it's a grudge,
then it's a grudge.
This picture is
You take me for a ride.
Nari
(Kim Shin)
My young bride
Even if I am not there
Make sure to eat well, learn well
And live well
That is
Your last mission
I will keep your words well, my lord
[Sobbing]
My lord
(Chairman Yoo)
Ah, the card
[DEOKHWA'S OVERWHELMED SIGH]
(Deokhwa)
Is this really for me, uncle?
(Kim Shin)
Live freely, Deokhwa
No longer limited to the card limit
This is a gift I am giving
A gift?
Why am I receiving an award?
I haven't done anything to deserve it
You worked hard to grow up
I love you
You bastard
[HEAVY MUSIC]
I put the house documents in your room
This is really your home now
Please live long and well
And I have a request
If I disappear
that child's mark will also disappear
Then at that time
please erase that child's memory
So they don't blame themselves
(The Grim Reaper)
What did you say?
Say it loudly
I couldn't hear you because it's noisy!
Put on your earphones!
(Grim Reaper)
Um, I’m far away from your ear
I can see your face
Ha, hey...
Let’s hang up, I’m hanging up for you
If you have anything to say to God, text me first
[CALL ENDED TONE]
I can’t see your face, I can’t see your face
(Grim Reaper)
Did you put it to your ear? Hello?
[SOFT MUSIC]
(Kim Shin)
I’m happy to take a walk with you
I’m happy to come pick you up
(Eun Tak)
Oh?
When did you come?
I’m happy to see you
Why are you being so nice to me these days?
(Euntak)
It's suspicious
Hold on a second
What does this letter mean?
'Cheong' as in 'to listen'
(Euntak)
Ah, 'Cheong' as in 'to listen'
Thank you
Sir, good night
[LAUGHTER]
[EUNTAK SLIPS ON SLIPPERS]
[THE DOOR CLICKS OPEN AND SHUT]
Good
[Putting the pen down]
Now I just need to translate
[EUNTAK'S ANNOYED GROAN]
Ah, why can't I translate it
There must be a hint somewhere
[THERE'S A KNOCK AT THE DOOR]
(Kim Shin)
I'll be right in.
Oh, yes.
[THE DOOR SWINGS OPEN WITH A CLICK]
Wow.
What is all this?
[EUN-TAK'S EXCLAMATION]
I thought it might be needed, when I become an adult.
You know better about five hundred.
(Kim Shin)
This is for when you enter college at twenty.
And this is for when you get a boyfriend after entering college...
To look pretty on dates.
Why are you giving this to me all of a sudden?
[EUN-TAK SPRITZES PERFUME]
[Sniffing the scent]
Ah, it smells nice.
[SHE PUTS DOWN THE PERFUME]
Today
What about today?
Black
Right now? In this night?
Yes, right now
Okay, just for 5 minutes
But
Is there love anywhere in these things?
No
I just asked once
I'll be out soon
[SHE SMILES SLIGHTLY]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[HEAVY MUSIC]
(Euntak)
Elegant
[EUNTAK'S PLEASANT BREATHING SOUNDS]
Behind the uncle's door
There is always a wonderful place
[EUNTAK'S AMAZING BREATHING SOUNDS]
I've never seen a buckwheat field before, it's pretty
(Eun-tak)
Did the flowers you gave me come from here?
I still remember the meaning of those flowers
Lover
[SHE SMILES SLIGHTLY]
But it seems like this place is really special
(Eun-tak)
The fact that the sword has to be drawn here?
My beginning and end
Then I'll ask you
W-wait, right now? Right away?
(Eun-tak)
Oh, wait a minute
I'm in favor of you becoming pretty
'Then what happens after you become pretty?'
'Then I thought, doesn't that
mean I have no utility value?'
So I've written a few things.
[SNICKER]
(Kim Shin)
Are you writing this instead of studying properly to eat well?
You need to look at the last clause, too.
[Heavy Music]
(Euntak)
On the day of the first snow every year,
I will respond to the summoning of Gab.
Because Gab will be waiting.
(The Grim Reaper)
Are you really going to die?
(Kim Shin)
Yeah
Before the first snow falls,
Why before the first snow?
I don't want to ruin that kid's first snow.
Did you ask for my name for this?
No.
I was really curious about that
(Euntak)
It suits you, your name and the uncle
[EUNTAK RUMMAGES THROUGH HER BAG]
You know what I mean, right?
[KIM SHIN QUICKLY SIGNS]
(Kim Shin)
That's what it means
(Euntak)
How did you know?
It's a really hard meaning
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
Amazing
It's snowing
It's the first snow, uncle
But why is the first snow already here?
Oh, that's interesting
I'm happy because I'm pretty, but the flowers might be a bit cold
(Euntak)
Right?
We are迎接 the fastest
first snow in the world.
[EUNTAK'S SMILE]
But this is an uncle, right?
What you said about picking on the first snowy day, that's it, right?
I'm sorry for being selfish, but
I also want to leave behind this kind of memory
(Euntak)
But until when will you leave it behind?
Uncle, you have to get pretty quickly
Yeah, right now
(Euntak)
[Rustling the notebook]
So, now let’s see you get pretty
What is the last thing you want to leave behind?
All the time spent with you
Was dazzling
Because the day was good
Because the day was not good
The weather is just right
Every day was good
(Kim Shin)
And
No matter what happens
It's not your fault
Mister, by any chance...
Are you really turning into a broom?
[HE SMILES SLIGHTLY]
That won't happen
Thank goodness
[HE SNIFFS]
Now, let's draw
[A SIGH]
[EUN-TAK SNIFFS]
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[EUN-TAK'S FLUSTERED MOAN]
No, why isn't this working?
(Euntak) Ugh, even though I can
see this, it won't come out, why?
Did you put force in your hand?
Wait a minute, I'll try one more
[TIME WITH A MAGICAL SOUND EFFECT]
(Euntak) Earlier, you clearly said 'No
matter what happens, it's not your fault'...
No take-backs, so that
means you're the goblin bride...
Ah, I said no take-backs,
just stay still, okay?
Because I'm more flustered right now?
(Kim Shin) Hey, just stay still
How can I stay more still than this?
Hey, give me that vow document, I'll burn
it for you just a moment!
[HE SLAPS THE BAG]
[A REALIZATION SIGH]
I got it I think this is that
thing, I know what it is?
The prince in the fairy tale The
cursed prince, that one, ah, what is that?
[TENSE SOUND EFFECTS]
A kiss, Kim Shin's
[SURPRISED GROAN]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
(Euntak)
Anyway, I grabbed the sword and it looks like
this
It may look like it, but it can't be caught,
somehow I managed to come back (Grim Reaper)
It
doesn't seem like I'm a goblin bride
So I have to let you go, I!
(Kim Shin) Hmm -
why the business card?
- I want it
(Sunny)
Isn't that Kim Woo-bin's phone?
I still don't have a business card, so
I can't receive it (Kim Shin) So what?
- (Sunny) What
does Woo-bin like?
- (Grim Reaper) Sunny
(Euntak) Of course,
it was my first kiss (Kim Shin)
Bread
[Kim Shin's scream]
[People's surprised groan]
(Tae-hee)
Are you okay?
(Euntak)
Tae-hee oppa?
(Kim Shin)
Who is Tae-hee? Come out
Who are you?
[TIRE FRICTION SOUND]
Subtitle: Choi Hyeran