[THEME SONG]
[SOFT MUSIC]
(Samshin)
When a person's handprints or blood are on an object,
if a wish dwells within it,
it becomes a goblin.
[A SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
In numerous battlefields,
thousands of blood-stained swords
[THE SKY RUMBLES]
Since it has been stained with the blood of its owner,
how much more?
[DREAMLIKE MUSIC]
[Tire screeching sound]
Only the goblin bride
will draw that sword.
When the sword is drawn, it will return to nothing and find peace
(Samshin)
It could only be a wicked prophecy
Thus, the goblin who was awakened to immortality
is everywhere in this world
and nowhere at all
Even now, somewhere...
[LAUGHTER]
Why are you laughing, you rotten thing?
(Yeonhee)
'Even now, somewhere,
I'm looking for my bride'
'That bride is me' Is that what you mean?
[LAUGHTER]
Though I may seem like this,
in my youth, I made many men cry.
(Yeonhee)
Tch
I came here for no reason again,
don't be surprised where that old hag went.
Hmm, I'm envious
(Samshin)
I’m the one who’s senile.
It's not something to brag about in front of a single mother.
Tch, how cruel.
(Sanshin)
Lower the price of spinach, lower the price of cabbage.
What’s wrong with me?
That bastard who left you is the one who's bad.
[THE DISAPPROVING BREATH OF SANSHIN]
Well, that’s true.
[SHE SMILES LIGHTLY]
But that story is really sad.
(Sanshin)
[scoffing]
It’s plenty sad.
It’s an extremely romantic curse.
That you have to find a bride to die.
(Yeonhee)
God is cruel.
(Three Gods)
The gods were originally bad
Selfish and full of jealousy
Only knowing themselves, just themselves
They're just the same as any other guy
(Yeonhee)
Ah, I'm going to leave now, have a lot of sales
Please be here when I come next time
[LAUGHTER]
[YEONHEE PICKS UP THE CRINKLED BAG]
[Significant music]
[Three Gods' power-filled moan]
When the moment of life and death comes
I earnestly pray with my hopes
[PEOPLE CHATTER]
(Three Gods)
Perhaps a weak-hearted god
might be listening
[THE BIRD CHIRPS]
[THE DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
(Kim Shin) If it were me,
I wouldn't recommend it.
If you leave home now, you'll
end up living a worse life than now, and
you'll never see your mom again.
Who are you? Are you Korean?
I'm a more complicated
person (Kim Shin)
Now it's your turn.
Speak
[CLEARLY, BRIGHT MUSIC]
Since you adopted me, you're my dad,
so tell my mom to raise me well.
Ask for help, I'm
hurting (Child 1) What
nonsense is that? Get out of the way.
If you draw that way, you won't die
but you'll only lose the use of your hands, so bear with it
Who are you?
Don't look away, can you speak clearly?
If you end up getting hit and dying,
are you going to take responsibility?
So you broke my ribs
(Man 1)
[English]
You bastard!
[Man 1's surprised groan]
[Man 1 falls down heavily]
[MAN 1'S LABORED GROAN]
(Kim Shin)
[Korean]
This is a lunchbox, go to school after we finish talking
The answer to math problem number 17 is not 2, it's 4
[Man 1's labored groan]
You got that one wrong
Who on earth are you?
[KIM SHIN TAPS CHILD 1'S SHOULDER]
[THUNDER RUMBLES LOUDLY]
(Kim Shin)
He is water, fire, and wind
[Heavy music]
He is light and darkness
And for a time
[A SHARP SOUND EFFECT]
[KIM SHIN'S LABORED GROAN]
[KIM SHIN'S ROUGH BREATHING]
He was human
[FIGHTING NOISILY]
[ROUGH BREATHING]
[The battlefield is chaotic]
[Horses neigh]
[HORSES NEIGH]
[KIM SHIN'S STRAINED MOANS]
[THE SOUND OF HOOVES IS HEARD]
(Kim Shin)
The people called him
a god
Covered in bright red blood,
charging forward to slay the enemy
[Shouts of soldiers]
He was literally a war god
[Tense music]
[Fighting noisily]
[SHOUT FROM ENEMY 1]
[MOAN FROM ENEMY 2]
[Horse neighing]
[Shout from enemy 3]
[MOAN FROM ENEMY 3]
[SHOUT FROM ENEMY 4]
[MOAN FROM ENEMY 4]
[SHOUT FROM ENEMY 5]
[MOAN FROM ENEMY 5]
[KIM SHIN'S 힘주는 신음 (STRAINING MOAN)]
[HORSE'S CRY]
[Horse's cry]
[Kim Shin's moan]
[Enemy 6's shout]
[Kim Shin's shout]
[ENEMY 6'S GROAN]
[Enemy 7's shout] [Kim Shin's
힘주는 신음 (straining moan)]
[ENEMY 7'S GROAN]
[KIM SHIN'S 힘주는 신음 (STRAINING MOAN)]
[Tension-building sound effect]
[Solemn music]
[KIM SHIN'S 힘주는 신음 (STRAINING MOAN)]
[FIGHTING IN A NOISY MANNER]
[Kim Shin's shout]
[Horse's cry]
[THE URGENT GROAN OF THE ENEMY COMMANDER]
[THE WIND HOWLS]
[TENSION-BUILDING SOUND EFFECT]
[THE SOUND OF A HEAVY FALL IS HEARD]
[GRAND MUSIC]
(The people)
Long live General Kim Shin!
[THE CHEERS OF THE PEOPLE]
(Citizen 1)
Long live General Jang!
(People)
[THE CHEERS OF THE PEOPLE]
(Subordinate)
Open the door!
It is General Kim Shin of the returning army!
[LAUGHTER OF THE SUBORDINATE]
Kim Shin, lay down your armor and follow the imperial decree.
(Subordinate)
You rascal!
Try saying that again.
You, a mere seventh rank fellow,
dare to speak of the general's name...
The returning army's accompaniment, Kim Shin!
[TENSE MUSIC]
- (Soldier 1) Lay down your armor
- (Subordinate) Truly...
I heard it
Wait
Is it done?
The traitor Kim Shin
(Soldier 1)
Kneel with your sword in your mouth and follow the imperial decree.
I will pull out your tongue!
(Subordinate)
A traitor, you say?
Are you insane? Have you gone mad?
[People murmur]
[Angry breaths of the subordinate]
General
(Soldier 1)
The traitor Kim Shin
with a sword in his mouth, kneel...
[HEAVY MUSIC]
I wish to see His Majesty, clear the way
- The sinner Kim Shin...
- If you block the way, you will surely die.
(Kim Shin)
Clear the way.
[The arrow flies swiftly]
[The soldier's groan]
[Arrows are pouring down]
[People's screams]
[THE GROANS OF SOLDIERS]
(Commoner 2)
Please save me, please save me
Please save me
[THE SCREAMS OF THE COMMONERS]
[A SUBORDINATE SHOUTS]
(Subordinate)
You bastards!
In the name of the lord,
we have fought for three days and nights
This is the path of returning alive
from that hell on earth
Yet you guys, how dare you!
(Jungheon)
Open the gates!
[THE GATES SWING OPEN]
Guard them
I will be back soon
The king above the subjects, the god above the king
That god is said to refer to Kim Shin
[HEAVY MUSIC]
(Chunghun)
The author's endless victory announcements
enchant the people
As the author's power repeatedly mocks the royal family
May the national laws strictly govern it
(Kim Shin)
He saw the enemy's blades clearly
But he could not see
the young king's
jealousy and fear directed at him
That was
the sharpest blade aimed
at himself.
He did not know
Are you really going to go this far?
(Young King)
So don't come any closer, stop
Whatever it is, stop
Stop there and die a traitor
Then I will save everyone except you
But if you take even one more step closer
One step of yours, one glance
I will kill everyone
And bury them at your feet
[SIGH]
Go ahead, General
I
I'm fine
I am
- Mama, I...
- I know
I truly know
If this is the end
then this is also my fate
So go
(Kim Sun)
Do not stop and go to His Majesty, General
It's a rebellion
(Young Wang-yeo)
Do not let a single breath of that family survive
It is a royal command!
[AN ARROW FLIES SWIFTLY]
[KIM SUN COLLAPSES]
[THE SOLDIERS SWIFTLY CUT DOWN]
(Joongheon)
Stop!
What are you doing, make the criminal kneel!
[Military 2's shout]
[Sharp sound effects]
[TENSE MUSIC]
[KIM SHIN'S GROAN]
[ROUGH BREATHING SOUNDS]
[THE SUBORDINATE'S URGENT BREATHING SOUNDS]
(Subordinate) General!
[THE SUBORDINATE'S LABORED BREATHING]
Your Majesty, what is happening?
Are you not afraid of the heavens?
When has the sky ever
sided with you scoundrels?
(Jungheon) The
gaze of a sinner is
fierce, My heart is
disturbed; you must endure!
[MILITARY 2'S SHOUT]
[MILITARY 2'S GROAN]
This is not your business
(Subordinate) General, General,
[GENERAL, GENERAL, THE
SUBORDINATE'S LABORED BREATHING]
The last
I have a favor to ask of you
[THE SUBORDINATE'S STARTLED BREATH]
[THE SUBORDINATE'S TREMBLING MOAN]
[Heavy music]
[The subordinate sobs]
[While sobbing]
I shall heed the general's command
[THE SUBORDINATE CONTINUES TO WEEP]
Please forgive me
[THE SUBORDINATE'S QUIVERING BREATH]
(Subordinate)
I will soon come to see you
[The subordinate’s shout]
[The subordinate stabs deeply with the sword]
[KIM SIN'S PAINFUL GROAN]
[THE SUBORDINATE'S CRYING]
[The shout of Soldier 2]
[Soldier 2 swiftly slashes with the sword]
(Jungheon)
Let no one recover the body of the traitor
Leave it in the field
as food for beasts and birds.
[Melancholic music]
[Sobbing]
To satiate the hunger of the beasts
That is the extent of the author's worth
It is a royal command!
[HEAVY SOUND EFFECTS]
[PEOPLE ARE SCREAMING]
(Man 2)
Oh divine being, our general, our general...
[PEOPLE ARE SOBBING]
[MAN 2 PLEADS TO THE DIVINE]
[CROWS CAW MOURNFULLY]
[PEOPLE ARE SCREAMING]
(Kim Shin)
Don't beg anyone.
God is not listening.
On the sunniest day of the year.
He died by the blade of his lord he was protecting.
[BLOOD DRIPS DOWN]
[TENSION-BUILDING SOUND EFFECT]
[FOOTSTEPS ECHO]
[EXCITING MUSIC]
[BIRDS FLUTTER]
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
[TIRE SCREECHING NOISE]
Damn it, this crazy bastard, shit.
(Man 3)
Hey, are your eyes just for decoration? Shit.
I'm going to die, shit...
[SIGNIFICANT MUSIC]
(Man 3)
You, you bastard
What's that?
Wild boar
What?
You have received a wild boar
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[TIRE SCREECHING]
Are you okay? Should I report it?
I, I hit a wild boar
(Man 3)
So suddenly
a wild boar popped out
Wild, wild boar? In the middle, in the middle of Gangnam?
[SCREAMS FROM PEOPLE]
[Tense sound effects]
[Man 4’s surprised groans]
[A MAN IS RAMBLING INCOHERENTLY]
[PEOPLE ARE MURMURING]
(Man 5)
Hello, yes, is this 112?
I'm at the Yeoksam
intersection, there’s a woman in the trunk
I think she’s dead,
yes, I’m not sure, there’s no movement right now, yes
[Woman's surprised breath]
[Woman's scream]
[Calm music]
I don’t know the exact situation I’m not sure if
this is just an accident [Woman's trembling moan]
I can’t accurately assess the
situation You need to come quickly, yes
(Woman)
Why am I...
[Man 5 is on a call]
Why am I over there...
[Trembling breath]
(Grim Reaper)
Hwang Mi-young, 25 years old
Born on the 2nd day of the 4th month of the Year of the Ox, during the Hour of the Serpent
Died on the 1st day of the 2nd month of the Year of the Horse
08:32
Cause of death, asphyxiation
Is this you?
[THE GRIM REAPER SHAKES THE CUP]
Drink up
It will help you forget the memories of the living
If you don't drink
What will happen?
You will regret not drinking
Whatever regret it may be, please only experience it in the living world
[THE SCENERY RESONATES]
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC]
[A BIRD CHIRPS]
Goblin?
Grim Reaper?
You wear a very vulgar hat
[CALM MUSIC]
(Chairman Yoo)
My lady
It’s been 20 years since we last met
Have you been well all this time?
Have you been without troubles?
I have aged quite a bit
(Chairman Yoo)
My lady, you are still splendid
[CHAIRMAN YOO'S LAUGHTER]
Not that splendid?
Hmph, you brat
(Chairman Yoo)
As I mentioned in my letter, he is the grandson.
Greetings.
Who is this uncle?
You're Deok-hwa.
(Kim Shin)
I will be your uncle, then a brother,
then a son, and then a grandson.
I look forward to it.
What is that?
[Playful music]
It’s getting suspicious.
(Chairman Yoo)
You rascal!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Since you’re the sole heir, I pampered you.
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
But you...
Me? Why?
There was someone who was born in Goryeo
and sleeps in a foreign land.
That is your distant ancestor.
You really look like that kid
(Young Deok-hwa)
Where are you going?
Was that ancestor handsome?
(Chairman Yoo)
Tsk, you rascal
I have no face, my lord
(Kim Shin)
Don't worry about it
No one in your family has ever been disappointing
But uncle
Why do you keep talking informally to our grandfather?
Do you want to die?
(Chairman Yoo)
You rascal!
[Kim Shin snickers]
Oh dear
(Man 2)
[choking up]
My lord
I apologize for coming so late.
I have been suffering for a few years.
[PAINED BREATHS]
I am now
about to go.
From now on,
this child will take care of you.
He is my grandchild.
Is this knife for you, grandfather?
[TENSE MUSIC]
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
(God)
The wishes of your people save you.
[Thunder rumbles]
[Meaningful music]
(God)
One, your sword is stained with thousands of blood.
You were an enemy to him
But he too is a creation of God
[The soldiers' roar]
Living in immortality alone
Watch the deaths of those you love
No death shall be forgotten
It is both my reward
and the punishment you receive
Only the goblin bride
will draw that sword
When the sword is drawn
You will return to nothing and find peace
[THUNDER ROARS]
(Man 2)
My lord
I have somewhere to go
[JUNG HEON WHISPERS]
[Heavy music]
It is impudent!
(Officials)
What on earth are you doing
to emit such irreverent energy?!
Oh, this brat...
[THE OFFICIAL FALLS DOWN HEAVILY]
You, you...
[A crackling sound is heard]
[Jeong-heon's painful groan]
[A PAINFUL GROAN]
I
am late
[A MOURNFUL MUSIC]
[THE CRY OF A CHILD]
(Child 2)
[Sobbing]
Grandfather
[CHILD 2 CRIES SORROWFULLY]
[CHILD 2 SNIFFLES]
(Kim Shin)
You
It seems to be the first punishment I receive
Bow
(Child 2)
Please receive it
From now on
I will take care of you
It was Grandpa's last wish
Blinded by revenge
How have you been
I couldn't say a word of greeting
Still
Will you do that for me?
[THE WAVES CRASH]
It's nice to see this scenery without speed
I like that you are seeing
this scenery without speed
[PEOPLE ARE SLURPING]
[THE SATISFIED MOAN OF CREW MEMBER 1]
[THEY ARE SLURPING]
(Kim Shin)
I
I'm still full, so please eat, Nari
How can I be full when I haven't eaten anything?
(Child 2)
I'm small, so even if I eat a little
I'm full
Nari is big, so please eat, Nari
(Kim Shin)
Then this will work
It's far to the mainland
(Child 2)
If we share, then
no one will be full
[Calm music]
So are you saying you'll go hungry?
(Child 2)
If I'm really hungry, I'll do some work on the boat
and I can get a little food.
Do you think I brought you here to feed you?
Trust me
I might be a bigger person than you think
(Kim Shin)
Hurry up
[SPARKLING SOUND EFFECT]
(Kid 2)
Wow
[Mysterious music]
[Kid 2's surprised gasp]
Wow
[Kid 2's applause]
[Approaching footsteps]
[KID 2'S ADMIRATION]
[Tense music]
[Kid 2's surprised gasp]
[KID 2'S LABORED GASP]
(Kid 2)
Nari
Nari...
[KID 2'S LABORED GASP]
(Seaman 2) Can I take
a look at that bundle?
We need to lighten the weight of
[THE SHIP, SO THE SEAMEN ARE LAUGHING]
(Child 2)
[In a strained voice]
Nari nari, nari
(Kim Shin)
Hurry and put the child down [Seaman 2
snorts]
Then I'll spare your life [Child 2 calls
out to Kim Shin]
(Seaman 2)
The waves seem
suspicious, no matter how I see it, it feels like
there's an unruly person on this ship
[Child 2's strained groan]
It's you, you will be sold as a
slave
Keep your limbs intact and
[THROW THE CHILD AWAY [CHILD 2'S SCREAM]
[THE CREW RATTLES THEIR WEAPONS]
Do you know what happens if
a human is worse than a beast?
[THUNDER CRASHES]
[THE BELL JINGLES]
[THE CREW'S ASTONISHED GROANS]
They will meet an angry
[GOD, THE CREW'S SCREAMS]
[THE CREW'S ASTONISHED GROANS]
[THE CREW'S GROANS]
[CREW MEMBER 2'S STARTLED GROAN]
(Crew member 2) [Stammering]
[IT'S A GOBLIN, THUNDER CRASHES]
[CREW MEMBER 2'S FRIGHTENED GROAN]
[THUNDER CRASHES]
[THE CREW'S ASTONISHED GROANS]
[THE CREW'S SCREAMS]
[A SQUEAK]
[THE MAST BREAKS WITH A CRACK]
[THE CREW'S FRIGHTENED GROANS]
[THUNDER CRASHES]
[THE CREW'S URGENT GROANS]
[CREW MEMBER 3'S SCREAM]
[THE WAVES CRASH]
(Crew member 4) P-please
[SAVE ME, THUNDER CRASHES]
(Kim Shin) It's too late [Mysterious
sound effect] [Grand music]
[THE SHIP RUMBLES AND SINKS]
[A CAR HORN SOUNDS FROM AFAR]
[A SIREN CAN BE HEARD FROM AFAR]
[A BABY'S CRYING IS HEARD]
[CHEERS CAN BE HEARD FROM THE PEOPLE]
[CONVERSATIONS AMONG PEOPLE CAN BE HEARD]
[A NERVOUS LAUGH]
It's nice to return without speed.
[THE SOUND OF A CAR ENGINE IS HEARD]
[The sound of tire friction is heard]
[The sound of a loud crash is heard]
[THE SOUND OF COLLAPSING IS HEARD]
[TENSE MUSIC]
[CAR ENGINE SOUNDS]
[YEONHEE'S STRUGGLING MOANS]
[Sobbing]
Please, save me
[YEONHEE CONTINUES TO SOB]
(Yeonhee)
[In a struggling voice]
If there is a god, please
Save me
Please save me
Anyone, please
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[MUSIC BUILDS ATMOSPHERE]
[In a struggling voice]
Who are you?
[STRUGGLING BREATHS]
Anyone
Ah, please, please just...
[SOBBING]
Well
It's my principle not to intervene in human life and death
[STRUGGLING BREATHS]
I...
[THE SOUND OF A HEARTBEAT IS HEARD]
(Yeonhee)
I can't die like this
[SOBBING]
It's not you that is asking to be saved
[YEONHEE'S STRUGGLING BREATH]
Please, please...
[STRUGGLING MOANS]
If not for anything else...
[YEONHEE'S LABORED BREATHING]
[THE SOUND OF A FETUS'S HEARTBEAT IS HEARD]
[LABORED BREATHING]
[BREATH STOPS]
[A DEEP SIGH]
You were lucky
to have met a weak-hearted god
(Kim Shin)
Tonight, I don't want to see someone die
[THE MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
[THE MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
[A FAINT GROAN]
[GASPING BREATHS]
[ROUGH BREATHING]
[FOOTSTEPS ECHO]
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
"Jiyeonhee, 27 years old"
"Unnamed, 0 years old"
[THE LIST RUSTLES]
[THE CLOCK TICKS]
Eyes and blood and
flowers
[THE WIND BLOWS SOFTLY]
(Ghost 1)
It's the goblin bride
[The ghosts whisper]
(Ghost 2)
Oh my, the goblin bride has been born
The goblin bride has been born
[THE GHOSTS CONTINUE TO WHISPER]
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECTS]
[THE SEAGULL SQUAWKS]
[THE WIND BLOWS FIERCELY]
(Yeonhee)
What should we prepare for our Euntak for this birthday?
Honey rice cake? Rainbow rice cake?
Mom, can we have a party instead of a feast now?
(Yeonhee)
What's the difference?
(Little Euntak)
The rice cake turns into a cake.
I also want to blow out the candles and make a wish.
Since I make wishes on the rice cake,
it doesn't seem like they get heard.
[YEONHEE'S LAUGHTER]
Mom didn't think about it.
Mom made rice cakes because you like them.
(Yeonhee)
Yeah, let's have a party starting this year,
with a cake.
Wow, Mom is the best.
Huh? It's a puppy.
Huh? A puppy?
[THE PUPPY IS WHIMPERING]
(Young Euntak)
Look at this.
[Soft music]
Spring has come again, isn’t it amazing?
[A SIGH]
[THE SOUND OF INSECTS SINGING]
(Young Euntak)
Oh dear, it's tough.
Mom, I got a perfect score in English today.
I've thought too much, I'm completely exhausted.
[Smiling slightly]
Is that so?
Wow, it's a cake.
Mom, are we having a party right now?
Yes, come sit down quickly, we'll light the candles.
Can I light them?
Our Euntak is all grown up now and can do it
That's right, I'm nine years old now, right?
(Young Euntak)
I even got a perfect score in English
This kind of thing is like eating soft rice
[YUNHEE'S LAUGHTER]
Where did you learn such words?
(Young Euntak)
Mom doesn't need to know
I just learn how to talk really well from different people
I must be a genius...
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
Why? You have to make a wish
Happy birthday, our puppy
No, that's not it
[POIGNANT MUSIC]
It's really not mom, it's mom's soul.
You
I can really see everything.
I hoped it wouldn't be so, but mom
[sobbing]
Mom, did you die?
[SHAKY BREATH]
Really?
Where is mom?
Where is mom right now?
At the hospital at the intersection
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
[SOBBING]
They'll call from the hospital
And if I go, aunt will be arriving soon too
[SNIFFLES]
(Yeonhee)
It's cold at night, wear a scarf.
I asked Super Grandma to go together.
Can we find Super Grandma's place?
Go down the laundry alley and turn right.
[smiling slightly]
Be smart, our puppy.
From now on, never make eye contact with the spirits, okay?
[SHE SOBS]
I'm sorry, Mom.
It's just that I saw that.
[LITTLE EUN-TAK IS SNIFFING]
But I can see things like that.
So it's something Mom can see too.
I'm just fine.
[choking up]
Yes.
Thank you for watching over mom
Thank you
(Yeonhee)
Euntak
[IS SOBBING]
Mom...
I think I have to go now
I love you, our puppy
[IS SOBBING]
Me too
I love you too, mom
Mom, goodbye, mom, take care
Mom, please go to heaven, okay?
Definitely, definitely
[YOUNG EUNTAK KEEPS SOBBING]
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
Mom!
[CRYING]
[YOUNG EUNTAK KEEPS SOBBING]
Mom
[THE PHONE RINGS]
(Hospital staff)
Hello, is this Ji Yeonhee’s home?
This is Jeil Hospital at the intersection.
I know, I’ll be going.
[THE RECEIVER IS ABRUPTLY PUT DOWN]
[A SOBBING BREATH]
[COUGHING]
[YOUNG EUNTAK SNIFFLES]
[YOUNG EUNTAK CONTINUES TO SNIFFLE]
I won’t make a wish
I won’t make a single one
Who should I ask, when no one listens?
"Happy Birthday"
(Yeonhee)
How come Grandma doesn’t seem to age?
Where is there left to grow old, here?
[SLIGHTLY SMILES]
That's true, too.
On the way, our Euntak a bit.
Can you not take a look?
What the hell, why would I bother with your daughter?
Tch, just passing by
(Yeonhee)
If there are leftover cabbages, give some
And a bit of spinach too
Exactly, why didn't we just die together then
What’s the point of living any longer
That’s mean
Grandma told me
To pray earnestly
[SOFT MUSIC]
There are actually girls who believe those words
Thanks to believing those words, I got to live a bit longer
Thank you, Grandma
[SHE SMILES SLIGHTLY]
I came to say goodbye
I’m leaving now
[SHE SMILES SLIGHTLY]
[SHE QUICKLY PREPARES THE VEGETABLES]
[TENSE MUSIC]
Sir, who are you?
[Tense sound effect]
(Grim Reaper)
Can you see me?
[A STARTLED BREATH]
(Young Euntak)
Oh, I didn't wear my scarf
I'm going to get scolded by mom
(Grim Reaper)
But I did, the scarf
Is this Ms. Ji Yeon-hee's house?
I came because she wasn't at the hospital
(Grim Reaper)
But
[Startled breath]
Why are you a child who shouldn't have been born...
Are you nine years old this year?
[A BREATH THAT SOUNDS SCARED]
I can't hear the uncle's voice at all?
(Grim Reaper)
But
what are you doing here?
[EXCITING MUSIC]
(Three Gods)
Leave this child alone
(Young Euntak)
Grandma!
(Grim Reaper)
This is interfering with my work.
(Three Gods)
You're talking nonsense about interfering with work.
What was that long ago that you're bringing up now?
(Grim Reaper)
It's a relief that I can do it even now.
I don't have time right now
That's your situation
Is this child on the list?
(Three Gods)
At that time, this child was nameless
But now this child has a name
If you have the list with this child's name on it
bring it to me
Then I'll give it to you
(Death God)
To receive cooperation from the list department
you need to submit proof for the past 9 years
Someone you might know...
[A SIGH]
[A SURPRISED BREATH]
See you again
Little one
[A MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
[YOUNG EUNTAEK SNIFFLES]
Grandma, it's Mom
I know
You can't do that, just live your life
(Samshin)
You have to move quickly, within 3 days
Then they won't be able to find you
You've made eye contact with the grim reaper
You can't live here anymore
If I move, won't they be able to find me?
They won't be able to find you
That's why the location of the house is important
After midnight today, at the funeral home
A man and two women
Will come looking for you
Follow them
It will be tough,
But you have no other choice,
[YOU SOB]
[CALM MUSIC]
But why are you telling me this?
Because you're pretty
(Samsin)
When I blessed you
I was happy
(Samsin)
This is a birthday present
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECTS]
[RHYTHMIC MUSIC]
(Deokhwa)
Excuse me
Shall we
have a drink?
Sure
[THE PHONE RINGS]
[VOICE MAILBOX ACTIVATION SOUND]
(Deokhwa)
No, the card that was working fine until yesterday
suddenly isn't working
So, about that, uncle
There are those unfriendly men in suits
at the bar, you
know? [Elegant music]
Right now, I'm with that person...
Please just answer the phone, Uncle,
they said to give me
your cell phone number.
But our uncle doesn’t have a
cell phone, you know? He was really
unfriendly to me,
Uncle, are you listening?
Uncle!
[Choking up] Uncle!
[THE SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
(Student 1) That guy is
about to finish his senior
[YEAR, BUT HE'S STILL EATING
ALONE. STUDENT 1 SCOFFS]
(Student 2) If it's sad,
just eat with him, right?
(Student 1)
Ah, are you crazy? Why would I? That person says they saw a ghost
(Student 2)
I'm more scared of them than the ghost
At least ghosts aren't visible
Look at them, they can hear everything
But they're pretending not to
(Ghost 3)
Hey
Hey, aren't you the goblin bride?
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
[EUNTAK HUMS]
You can see me, right?
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
Let's go together
I'm really lonely and sad, okay?
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
Hey, why are you pretending you can't see me again?
You bad girl!
[EUNTAK'S SURPRISED BREATH]
Ah, oh, the visuals are really
[EUNTAK'S HEAVY BREATHING]
(Ghost 3)
See, you can see everything
[GHOST 3'S LAUGHTER]
[GHOST 3'S SURPRISED BREATH]
You really are
I-I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
What? Why are you apologizing without any context?
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
[TURNS ON THE TORCH]
(Chairman Yoo)
You don’t even turn on the lights.
[Turning off the torch]
[Kim Shin's awkward breath]
I had deep thoughts
(Chairman Yoo)
This is the place you'll be staying in Nice
[CALM MUSIC]
In the meantime
(Chairman Yoo)
Yes, that has happened
Deokhwa is already twenty-five
I told you to check the connections here and there
You'll be going around the end of this month
If you leave now
I will never see you again in my lifetime?
Every moment
Thank you
When you return
Deokhwa will be here, yes
[DOOR LOCK OPERATION SOUND]
(Chairman Yoo)
Oh dear, I
keep forgetting the key
[Door lock activation sound]
I changed it to a new model
[The door opens and closes with a click]
[CHAIRMAN YOO'S LAUGHTER]
(Deok-hwa)
Grandfather, Uncle
[DEOK-HWA'S EXCLAMATION]
Uncle is here
I asked you to come pick me up
But you were just here
(Chairman Yoo)
Don't interrupt when adults are talking!
(Deok-hwa)
Grandfather, did you cut off my card?
Isn't it true that Grandpa cut it off?
(Chairman Yoo)
My secretary cut it off, you brat
(Deokhwa)
Ah, I just got totally screwed
How did I charm him?
If it's going to be like this, why did you make me a third-generation chaebol...?
Uncle, where are you going?
Where are you going?
(Chairman Yoo)
[Knocking on the table]
Ah, didn't I tell you to fix your way of speaking?
Ah, just stay still, Grandpa
(Deokhwa)
Is that it?
Is it about looking for a groom for Uncle?
No, you idiot
If you’re going to get married internationally, why can’t you say so?
Why can’t you say it?!
[SIGH]
When you come back, there will be this child, right?
Uncle, exactly
when, what day and time are you going?
[THE ALARM CLOCK RINGS]
[THE ALARM CLOCK SUDDENLY STOPS]
[LIVELY MUSIC]
[POURING WATER GENTLY]
[SLAMMING THE LID OF THE RICE COOKER]
[THE SOUP IS BUBBLING]
Eat breakfast, one man and two women
[CLATTERING THE LID SHUT]
Eat rice!
(Gyeongmi)
Hey, shut up, the bowl is
ringing, setting up a table like that and
campaigning
Seriously (Gyeongsik)
Why seaweed soup?
Whose birthday is it today?
(Gyeongmi) Wow, is she making
seaweed soup because it's her own birthday?
That's right (Euntak Aunt)
Oh dear,
what's so proud about the day you
were born after eating your own mother?
You don't even know it's embarrassing
because you haven't learned anything?
(Gyeongmi) She learned it from
mom, she’s been with mom for 10 years?
(Euntak Aunt)
Just eat your rice.
[THE DISH IS SET DOWN WITH A CLATTER]
Thank you for the birthday wishes, Auntie.
[AUNT EUN-TAK'S ABSURD BREATHING]
[A HOLLOW LAUGH]
That's why they say you shouldn't raise
a black-haired beast.
(Aunt Eun-tak)
Being affectionate is also a sickness, you know.
Oh, only the dead girl is pathetic.
I raised her as a single mother with great effort.
That's a bit too harsh, don't you think?
[Eun-tak closes her bag zipper quickly.]
What's harsh about it?
(Aunt Eun-tak)
To you, she's mom, but to me, she's my sister.
(Eun-tak)
That's right, emotionally and by kinship,
I'm closer.
(Kyeong-mi)
Does mom even know what she's saying?
Just eat your meal.
Where are you running off to?
[Putting on shoes quickly.]
I'm not running away; I'm going to school.
(Kyeong-sik)
If you take an umbrella, you'll die.
(Aunt Eun-tak)
Come to the bank with your passbook after school.
You know what will happen if you don't bring it today, right?
I don't have a passbook.
How many times do I have to say this...
(Euntak Aunt)
Then where is that bankbook?
Where is your mom's insurance money?!
How would I know that?
Aunt took everything away
even the deposit money!
(Euntak Aunt)
Oh, why are you talking so much
since morning, oh
Stop the nonsense and bring it
if you don't want to get beaten
The bankbook that was safely in the bag
disappears as soon as we go to the bank
Then who else could it be if not you?
(Kyungmi)
That girl is definitely possessed.
Yeah, a ghost is attached to your back
What? Crazy, hey!
[CALM MUSIC]
"Happy Birthday"
(Chairman Yoo)
By the way, Nari
Are you leaving alone again this time?
(Kim Shin)
It seems so
No woman I have met
has seen the sword
I’m relieved though
(Chairman Yoo)
When you suffer because of the sword
I hope the bride appears quickly
And when we meet like this
I hope no one knows
[smiling]
It's just human greed, you know.
(Kim Shin)
I'm glad too
That you're still by my side
And the drinks are plentiful
For tonight, I just want to live it up
[I SMILE SLIGHTLY]
Shall we make a toast?
[WE LAUGH TOGETHER]
[THE WAVES CRASH HARSHLY]
When I was nine
I promised myself I would never do something like this
But I'm just in a hurry
So I ask for your understanding
Please help me find a part-time job
And do something for my aunt's family.
Please make sure I get a boyfriend, I beg you, meaningful
[SOUND EFFECT]
(Eun-tak) Please help me get a part-time job, and do
something about my aunt's family and my beggar-like situation...
Even 10 won would
[BE APPRECIATED, SIGH]
What am I doing?
Who am I asking for rain?
Where is God, the
[SKY IS THUNDERING]
[I BLOW AIR THROUGH MY MOUTH]
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
[BOUNCY MUSIC]
Could it be that it’s
even going to rain here?
(Eun-tak) [sniffling] Is this
a shower or a monsoon?
Is the rain going to stop?
I only have two umbrellas
but why does it keep raining and causing a fuss?!
[I’M SOBBING]
(Kim Shin)
Is it you?
[Euntak’s surprised breath]
Oh my, you startled me
Me?
[EUNTAK’S COUGH]
(Euntak)
Me?
Are you talking to me?
Oh, you, is it you?
What do you mean?
Are you the one who called me?
Me? I didn’t call you
You called me
How the heck did you summon me?
(Euntak)
How did I?
I’m really saying I didn’t call you
You definitely called me
Think about it, how you called
Desperately?
It wasn’t me, I just see an uncle in front of my eyes
Last time, on the street
I accidentally made eye contact
[A SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
That uncle, right?
What do you mean? What does it mean to see?
He’s a ghost, isn’t he?
I can see ghosts
- He’s not a ghost
- At first everyone says that
What on earth are you?
What is it? It usually has to be visible
But you can't see anything?
What should be visible?
Twenty years old, thirty years old, your future
I guess there’s no future
(Euntaek)
By the way, were you a shaman before you died?
Or a con artist?
[FUNNY MUSIC]
Talking about the future
What, what? What kind of, what kind of person?
Please go to a good place
(Euntaek)
It’s not good to wander around for too long
But what is that flower?
Why are you talking to me when you're saying go away?
(Eun-tak)
I got it, go ahead
Buckwheat flower
[smiling]
That's not what I'm asking
Why are you holding it?
(Eun-tak)
Give it to me, it doesn't suit you, uncle
[AN ABSURD SIGH]
It's the first time I've heard that
It's really the first time, really
It's okay to give it
Today's my birthday
A very gloomy birthday
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
(Eun-tak)
I usually get grass on my birthday
When I was nine, I got cabbage
But what does the buckwheat flower
symbolize?
The waves of
[LOVERS CRASH DOWN]
Why were you crying?
Because of the part-time job, my aunt's
family, or my boyfriend Which one of the three?
How would I know that?
(Kim Shin) I heard
you, what does it mean?
Sometimes, I grant
someone's wishes, Are
you saying that I grant someone's wishes?
Like a genie? Or, a guardian deity?
[PLAYFUL MUSIC]
Really? No wonder
(Euntak) When I first
saw you, I felt a bit
different from other ghosts.
Are you really
my guardian deity?
I never said I was your guardian deity.
My mom said that
people are born with their own dictionaries
(Euntak)
In my dictionary,
no matter how much I search, 'happiness', 'luck'
I can't see those words at all
[SNIFFING]
You know what I mean?
I don't know
(Euntak)
It means something like, won't you lend me around five hundred?
If cash flow is a bit difficult,
just let me know this week's lottery numbers
That meaning is included, too
Say goodbye to the family this time
(Kimshin)
You won't be able to see them for a while
Work hard at the chicken shop, and you'll be fine
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
(Euntak)
Huh? Excuse me!
What about my boyfriend?
Hello? Hey?
Oh, really, how petty, seriously
Is it someone familiar?
It seems that way
(Grim Reaper)
I've heard rumors
(Kimshin)
There's a lot of fluff in my rumors
What brings you to my place?
Do you live here?
(Deokhwa)
All this furniture is optional,
just walk in with your body...
[DEOK-HWA'S AWKWARD SMILE]
When did you come in, uncle?
[KIM-SHIN RATTLES THE TEACUP]
- Explain.
- (Deok-hwa) No, uncle, that is...
(Deok-hwa)
Anyway, it's been 20 years, right here.
So with those 20 years,
how much is the 세?
It all started from that pure curiosity,
that's what I mean.
Do you even know what that is when you brought it in?
- You...
- (Deok-hwa) Saying that to the tenant!
They said they were going to open a teahouse.
(Dukhwa)
Oh, I'm sorry, our uncle
hasn't had much social experience
- (Dukhwa) Please have some coffee
- (Reaper) Uh
[The reaper drinks the tea noisily]
(Dukhwa)
Well...
[In a small voice]
I haven't received the money yet
(Kim Shin)
I saw a new car in the yard
It's the tenant's car
(Reaper)
It's not my car, right? I've already
given all the money
Since that's how it happened,
I'll return the money, so please leave
I understand how it happened, but
The stamp has already been put on the contract
[HUMOROUS MUSIC]
[I BLOW OUT A BREATH]
[The Grim Reaper's sigh]
I hope this isn't an important document
(The Grim Reaper)
The one just hanging is a copy; the original is with the real estate
The belongings will come in tomorrow
It's an auspicious day
If you've finished, go
The kindness I offer extends only to coffee
[The Grim Reaper's snicker]
Go inside and pack your things
(The Grim Reaper)
If it's belongings for 20 years, it's already too late to start packing now.
Will you dare to break the taboo
of the goblin and the blushing face?
You probably know well what a contract with a lion is like.
(The Grim Reaper)
Instead of this house,
you could take that friend who just left...
I can't do that.
(Kim Shin)
There are plenty of empty rooms, so use one.
Just think of it as my house.
- It’s my house.
If you can chase the goblin away
from the goblin's turf,
Let's see you give it a try.
[PROFOUND MUSIC]
(The Grim Reaper)
It's barbaric to an extent.
[While slicing meat]
This is a vulgar diet I've only heard rumors about.
[SIGH]
Ah, mistake.
Spraying on my own
[A SCOFF]
[THE SEASONING CONTAINER FALLS OUT]
(Kim Shin)
Ah, I also made a mistake
Saying that I would spray it on you
[I CLATTER THE FORK DOWN]
You?
Didn’t we just sort out the titles?
(Kim Shin)
This, that, hey, you
[EUN-TAK MUTTERS]
Lovers?
[EUN-TAK TOUCHES THE FLOWERS RUSTLING]
[HE SMILES SLIGHTLY]
Tch
Lovers, what about that?
[HE SCRATCHES WITH A PEN]
[LIVELY MUSIC]
“Part-time job”
(Eun-tak)
Hello
[smiling]
You're the boss, right?
[clearing throat]
Ah, my name is Ji Eun-tak
I'm really bright and positive
Incredibly bright and positive
Bright and positive
As long as you give me any tough tasks
I can accomplish them all
No matter the tough tasks...
[SIGH]
[LABORED BREATHING]
Watched me for a part-time job, damn it
Guardian deity? Oh my, this guy
[ROUGH BREATHING]
I should have at least gotten a phone number
[EUN-TAK'S SIGH]
Uh, uh
[EUNTAK'S URGENT MOAN]
[SHE BLOWS AIR THROUGH HER LIPS]
- (Kim Shin) See,
it's you - Ah, you
[SURPRISED ME WITH THAT EXCITING MUSIC]
Ah, why do you keep following me?
(Kim Shin) I’m not
following you; you called me
again (Euntak) I’m not
saying that, if I had that
kind of talent I wouldn’t be
going through this hardship.
How could I? What, do
you shake a bell to call me?
What do you expect me to answer that?
You keep insisting,
that's why I said I didn't call
(Euntak) By the way Are you
really a guardian deity, mister?
What kind is it?
Well, shame, probation, internal credit, you?
Is the chicken place that uncle mentioned
maybe a poultry farm?
Poultry farm part-time job?
- No
- Then where is it?
You make people expect it will happen for no reason
- You really what you did to me...
- No
I didn't call you
It's you, you, it’s definitely you
I've never done this before
Is it really me?
Really?
(Euntak)
If that's true, what am I then?
Ah, I figured it out
What is it?
Tell me everything you see
- You're in a school uniform
- (Euntak) Again
You're pretty
[SOFT MUSIC]
The school uniform
Is that all?
Um, you don’t see wings or anything like that?
(Euntak)
I guess I'm a fairy
Tinkerbell
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
Hey, I just made a joke
Ah, phone number, damn it!
(Priest)
In the name of the Father, and of the Son, and of the Holy Spirit, Amen
Let’s pray.
We thank God
who grants us grace.
I wish to take a step closer to you
Please show me mercy
[Lively music]
Always...
[I LIGHT THE TORCH]
[I BLOW WITH MY MOUTH]
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECTS]
[JOYFUL BREATHING]
(Euntak)
I knew
I knew how to sing it
But singing it here
is a bit not right, isn't it?
Are you scared?
(Euntak)
They say they're really nice people
Don't flatter, where's the god?
I came to see where you are.
[KIM SHIN'S DISPLEASED BREATH]
Why aren't you just going up in flames and walking away?
(Kim Shin)
You can't do that here
Just think of it as a kind of demilitarized zone
Don't follow me
What are you going to do about my wish?
None of the three have been resolved, right?
I'm going to solve it this time, even the part-time job
(Eun Tak)
Not that, my boyfriend
You should put in some effort too!
(Kim Shin)
Tsk
(Eun Tak)
Wow, I really shouldn't be treating you like this?
(Eun-tak)
I know the way now, I
[mobile phone manipulation sound]
I got the number exactly
[EUN-TAK BLOWS AIR THROUGH HER LIPS]
[APPLICATION SOUND EFFECT]
[EUN-TAK'S EXCITED BREATHING]
(Eun-tak)
Oh, I thought this wouldn't work
(Kim-shin)
If you thought it wouldn't work, why are you doing it?
(Eun-tak)
Uh, ah, wait a second
[meaningful sound effect]
[exciting music]
Did you catch me just now?
(Eun-tak)
Ah, I can't take it anymore, ah, it's hot
[EUNTAK BLOWS AIR THROUGH HER LIPS]
I thought it was cold because it was blue.
Originally, the temperature of the blue light
is the highest, you liberal arts student.
You should study a bit during this time.
[EUNTAK'S BREATH IS EXASPERATED]
Even though I lost my parents and had to fend for myself,
I never dropped out of first place...
It’s fine.
Hey, instead of saying something like a guardian deity
could you just give me five hundred and clear out?
I have something to do, you know?
What is it?
Ah, your clothes are a bit solemn.
Tomorrow is the memorial day of someone I know.
But why are you going starting today?
Is it in the countryside?
There, today is tomorrow.
When are you coming? Tomorrow? The day after tomorrow?
I have something I really want to ask.
(Kim Shin)
Uh, hurry up.
[EUNTAK'S SIGH]
I know this question will sound strange
but I hope you don't misunderstand and hear me out.
Since you understand, go ahead, what is it?
At first, I thought you were
a grim reaper.
[Exciting music]
(Euntak)
But if you were a grim reaper,
As soon as I saw him, he probably took me away.
Then I thought, "Oh, it's a ghost."
But the uncle had
a shadow.
(Euntak)
So I thought about it.
What on earth could that uncle be?
So what is it, me?
A goblin.
[TENSION-BUILDING SOUND EFFECT]
(Euntak)
Uncle, are you maybe a goblin?
What are you?
What on earth are you?
It's a bit awkward for me to say it out loud,
but I'm a goblin bride.
You know I can see ghosts, right?
(Euntak)
Since the moment I was born
I was born with this, you know?
I think it's because of this
that the ghosts
call me the bride of a goblin.
You see this? This
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
[A FAINT MOAN]
You see this?
[ROUGH BREATHING]
Prove it
Prove that I'm the bride of a goblin?
(Kim Shin)
Uh
How?
(Euntak)
Well, do I fly high?
Or do I turn into a broom?
[SNICKERS]
Do it.
I'm really serious right now
Me too
Tell me what you see
[I SMIRK]
Are you getting revenge?
Tell me everything you see
- You're tall
- (Kim Shin) Again
- Your clothes look expensive
- Again
[SIGH]
- About mid-thirties?
- (Kim Shin) Again
You don't mean you want answers like "you're handsome," right?
The answer I want
You should have had that
If what I see in you is all there is
Then you're not a goblin bride.
You have no utility value to the goblin.
(Kim Shin)
It’s unfortunate that I can’t see ghosts,
but since I'm living a life that’s essentially a bonus,
live gratefully.
You simply broke the rules
and got involved in human life and death,
causing side effects.
What if I don’t want to bear it?
There’s always the method of just dying as originally destined.
[AN ABSURD SOUND OF BREATH]
You really...
I got it;
let me ask that question again.
Sir, are you perhaps
- a goblin?
- No.
- No?
(Eun-tak)
Then what is it?
Why does an old man judge whether I have value or not?
You want to improve by at least 10 won, right?
(Kim-shin)
Someone who worries about a beggar-like situation
only by 10 won.
Live in reality, not in rumors.
You're not a goblin bride.
[A DISCONTENTED SIGH]
(Eun-tak)
Wait a minute
[Meaningful sound effect]
(Eun-tak)
That conversation isn't over yet...
[Kim-shin's surprised moan]
[LIVELY MUSIC]
[THE DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
(Kim Shin) Did you just come
through that door? Following me?
Oh, how did you get in?
You grabbed the handle
and followed Mr. Min...
But why is it like this here?
(Kim Shin) Hey, that's why I'm asking right
now. How did you pass through that door, anyway?
Oh, was it Paju? The
English village there?
(Eun Tak) Ugh, but even if
it was there, it's still strange.
What the heck is going
on? Where exactly are we?
Canada?
Is it Canada?
(Eun Tak) If it's Canada...
That, the land of maple leaves?
The one with the auroras?
(Euntak)
Is this really a foreign country?
Wow, Uncle, you had this ability too?
You have it too, what are you really?
(Euntak)
This is really Canada and
if Uncle's abilities are like this
I’ve made up my mind
- What?
- I’ve decided, I
(Kim Shin)
What, what?
I'm going to get married, to you, Uncle
(Euntak)
No matter how much I think about it
I really think you are a goblin
[smiling slightly]
I love you
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
(Euntak)
Is this it? A red carpet for me?
It’s an honor to walk together, right?
(Kim Shin)
What on earth are you talking about?
(Euntak)
I’m going to be your bride 200 years later
(Kim Shin)
It seems like you'll keep calling me
I want to appear intelligent and flawless anywhere, anytime
Did I seem manly?
- (Kim Shin) Deokhwa
- Is something bad happening?
Who says I’m going to be Uncle's bride?
(Fortune Teller)
Be careful of the man with the hat, the black hat.
(Euntak)
Am I going to die?
I'm only just nineteen?
I died at nine and I died at ten
That's death
[THUNDER CRASHES]
Subtitle: Choi Hyeran