[THEME SONG]
(Ghost)
New face
What I mentioned before
That there's some know-how that has been wandering around the underworld for a long time
(Euntak)
Ah, that...
(Ghost)
Twenty years ago
I heard you even ran away after meeting a grim reaper
[Heavy music]
Has it been about 20 years?
I encountered some deceased person
but they were a spirit with no information
Really?
When I was nine years old, I had a similar experience...
(Grim Reaper)
It seemed like they had been wandering this world for a very long time
They didn't seem to be afraid either
(Grim Reaper)
It was strange to see a ghost that didn't fear the grim reaper
for the first time
[TENSE MUSIC]
[TENSE SOUND EFFECTS]
[THERE'S A CRACKLING SOUND]
Nice to meet you
You're that dokkaebi bride
[EERIE SOUND EFFECTS]
[THERE'S A CRACKLING SOUND]
[A PAINFUL GROAN]
Yes, me too
Now, please stop lingering around
in someone else's business place
(Euntak)
Customers won't come, yes
Since we have to do business now
Please all go out
Cold-hearted girl
Starting with you, hurry up
[Grim sound effects]
(Ghost)
Unfriendly girl!
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[HEAVY MUSIC]
[THERE'S A CRACKLING SOUND]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[EUNTAK IS RUSTLING]
[A SIGH OF RELIEF]
[A SIGH]
It feels a bit...
In 20 years of horror life,
I've never seen anything like that
[TENSION-BUILDING SOUND EFFECTS]
[GASPING BREATHS]
Ah, let’s forget, let’s forget
I'm so busy I don’t even have time to care about ghosts
Hmm
If we cram it into 4 days like this
I need to postpone my part-time work hours a bit.
[A SIGH OF CONTEMPLATION]
[RUSTLING THE NOTEBOOK]
[EUNTAK'S SNICKER]
Yunseo?
I'm suddenly so pissed off.
I'm busy trying to survive, Yunseo?
[A SIGH]
[GENTLE MUSIC]
[EXHALING BREATH]
(Reaper)
I'm
the reaper.
[A SIGH]
(Sunny)
I want to see you.
I don’t want to see you.
How do seven cups always fall perfectly?
[SUNNY'S SIGH]
(Sunny)
Knowing that seven cups would spill
I still
started with 'I want to meet'
[SUNNY'S SIGH]
I want to meet
I don't want to meet
Have you ever seen a peach blossom?
(Lion 1)
I have
I got hit hard once after going to a shaman's house
That scar lasts a long time
The one from earlier is better
Right? The one from earlier is better, right?
But you
Have you never thought about wanting to find your memory?
Never.
What is the memory that we have forgotten?
Isn't it the same as a memory that doesn't exist?
(Grim Reaper 1)
Why bother with something that didn't exist in the first place...
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
[A KISS IS GIVEN]
I
miss that
(Grim Reaper 1)
Don't do that
We're all sinners
Thinking about what might follow that longing
I know
Even though I know
(Grim Reaper)
Each step of this longing
Even though I'm so afraid of where it might lead
I
miss it again and again
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
Why do I feel like I've had too much to drink today?
I got caught, I'm a grim reaper
to Sunny.
You're doing well, keep it up.
In this dead of winter
Where did the peach blossom branch come from?
[PLAYFUL MUSIC]
Really?
What should I do now?
It must be really confusing
What should I do about it?
(Kim Shin)
Since it has come to this, why don't you hold my hand a bit more?
Is my face there or not?
I said I got caught, didn't I?
Since I've been caught, just grab it tightly
Is my face there or not?
You don't know what you're talking about
Do you know how tough it is to see your past life?
(Grim Reaper)
Who would be forced to be shoved in like this, in an instant
The face I only saw in pictures
When it becomes lively, it's so beautiful that
I lose my mind...
My sister
I mean
(Grim Reaper)
That, young and foolish-looking
face I saw
That young king
I guess that idiot only thought
about himself
Our useless brother
Isn't even on his mind.
(Shinigami)
I'm here, why?
(Euntak)
Ah, no, it's next time
[Mysterious sound effect]
[Euntak's astonished breath]
(Euntak)
Ah, give it back
Why are you causing a fuss over someone else's notes?!
(Kim Shin)
Why is my writing in someone else's notes and causing a fuss?
What is this?
Did you forge documents again without me knowing?
Hah, really, pretending not to know
(Euntak)
It's a love letter, a love letter that you wrote
(Shinigami)
You wrote a love letter?
(Eun-tak) I wrote it, you
know, about first love, and
how grand the love story is makes
me curious about the backstory.
I thought I'd ask the
uncle for some help,
but what's the front story?
This isn't Yeon-seo, is it?
You like it when it's not
(Eun-tak) It's quite a classic,
'After living for a hundred years,
one day On a day that feels just
right', well, huh? That's
not the content, is it?
(Eun-tak) That content
is correct, though.
Oppa Deok-hwa read it all, 'After living
for a hundred years, one day' [meaningful
music] 'On a day
that feels just right'
It can't be
(Kim Shin)
Even if Deokhwa came back to life
I can't read it
That was a word I kept alone
that was written nowhere
(Kim Shin)
After living for a hundred years, one day
On a day that's just right
I hope I can confess it was my first love
(Grim Reaper)
Yeah, that's not the content
(Euntak)
That's not it
Deokhwa oppa definitely interpreted it for me
From Yeonseo's side
Remember when
you blew away dozens of cars?
Did you perhaps tell Deokhwa
that I could help you with memory?
No
(Deokhwa)
Uncle at the end of the road, let’s go somewhere
But how does he know
(Grim Reaper)
He just suddenly asked me to go, right?
Now that I think about it
(Euntak)
Deokhwa oppa even helped me find maple leaves
That I completely lost
(Deokhwa)
Guess which neighborhood this maple leaf is from
What is it?
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
(Euntak)
Oh, that's pretty cool?
(Dukhwa)
Wow, that's pretty cool?
[A GASP OF REALIZATION]
Why didn't I know?
It turns out she was the one
putting the goblin's house on the real estate market
[SIGNIFICANT MUSIC]
(Kim Shin)
Was I a king, a god, or just myself?
[TEARS DROP QUIETLY]
(Euntak)
This character means 'to hear'.
(Dukhwa)
I found that girl, she's at the ski resort now.
They say your boss is
our uncle's younger sister in her past life.
(Dukhwa)
Shall we
have a drink?
(Samsin)
Finally, the goblin and the goblin bride have met
It's destiny
(Samsin)
Why is Wangye doing this again?
What should happen when someone who lives with a sword stuck in them meets the one who stuck the sword?
Why are you at my house?
Are you living here?
That too is destiny
I hear you're looking for a house
There's a limit to joking around
(Samsin)
What on earth are you thinking?
Love so specially
[Thunder rumbles]
(Samsin)
Kim Shin has been punished for 900 years.
Still not enough?
The weight of a life is like that.
[KIM SHIN'S STRAINED GROAN]
(Samsin)
You shouldn't have created sin in the first place
You should have created a perfect world,
right?
Then people wouldn’t be seeking God
[UNPLEASANT BREATHING SOUNDS]
(Samsin)
Each and every child is marked with love
Stop tormenting them already
Take your hands off that child’s eyes
Let them recognize each other, no matter what choice they make
[SIGH]
It's disappointing
It was nice to be handsome.
[RHYTHMIC MUSIC FLOWS OUT]
Finally, you've come
(Kim Shin)
Deokhwa, you...
[Mysterious sound effects]
[Meaningful music]
[SILENCE FLOWS]
[MAJESTIC MUSIC]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
(Kim Shin)
Who are you? Let's introduce ourselves.
[People scream]
(Man 1)
Chilseong, Cheonsin, Cheonjishinmyeong!
(Kim Shin)
Do not beg anyone
for the gods are not listening
(God)
The gods are still not listening
Grumbling
There must be a meaning to the god erasing memories
(Grim Reaper)
If I remember, I do as I should
If I don't, I don't as I should
It's all the will of the god
With mere guesses
I have always been listening
There was also an opportunity to plead for death
(God)
Then
Why am I still alive?
I have never erased memories
I just made the choice to erase them myself
[Meaningful sound effect]
Even so
Does it feel like the god's plan or a mistake?
The god is merely a questioner.
Fate is the question I throw
The answer
You all should find it
The farewell to this child
You all
Then I'll take my leave
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECTS]
[Rhythmic music plays]
[People cheering]
Why are the uncles here?
When did you come?
(Deokhwa)
Why am I collapsed?
Awesome
Did I just black out?
Just from one drink?
Whoever you are, just hit me once.
[Deokhwa's Surprised Groan]
[The Grim Reaper's Surprised Groan]
[Deokhwa's Surprised Groan] (The Grim
Reaper) Why are you doing that to the kid?
This person has no sin -
(Kim Shin) This person?
- (The Grim Reaper)
Oh, hey (The Grim
Reaper) I'm sorry for repeatedly
saying let's go somewhere...
(Deokhwa) Yes?
Why are you like this,
uncle from the last room?
(Kim Shin) Is that something to say
right now? Are you really Deokhwa? Huh!
Hey, I, butterfly, butterfly,
butterfly! Mr. Butterfly!
Uncle, are you drunk?
(Kim Shin) Come here,
are you not coming?
Ah, wait a second, time, time, let go
I'll say it, I'll say it
Hey, let go, let go, hey, let go
[KIM SHIN'S STRAINED GROAN]
[EUNTAK BLOWS AIR THROUGH HER LIPS]
(Euntak)
Ah, it's hot, ah, it's hot, hot
Ah, but it really tastes good
That man is a grim reaper, right?
[EUNTAK COUGHS]
How did you know?
(Sunny)
I saw it
A very strange moment
I happened to
have a connection since I was young
(Euntak)
I'm sorry for not telling you
But Kim Woobin, for a grim reaper
you're really kind and gentle...
Isn't there a woman ghost who comes obsessively?
I thought of that first
It doesn't match my conditions
The man is too inclined, right?
In the living and the afterlife
(Euntak)
Ah, how could you think that
[SUNNY'S SIGH]
I thought of this too
If that person is a grim reaper...
The person claiming to be my older brother
must have really lived for nearly a thousand years
Is that right?
So you’re 'mine'? Goblin couple?
Strictly speaking,
I am 'outer', though
since I'm out in the world
Ha, it's crazy
[SUNNY'S ABSURD BREATHING SOUNDS]
(Euntak)
But, sir
Even if you linger in front of my house like this
the chances of meeting Kim Woobin are quite slim
His job involves frequent late-night work
Just contact him.
(Sunny)
Hearing the words 'Shall we break up'
How should I get in touch?
If I get a call, right?
I guess I'll reluctantly accept it
Just cooperate
(Euntak)
Yes
But, boss, I'm sorry
Right, do that
I haven't said anything yet
Since you became a college student
Aren't you asking to adjust your part-time work hours?
Wow, amazing
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
Boss, you are a person, right?
[EUNTAK'S AWKWARD SMILE]
Welcome
[BRIGHT MUSIC STARTS TO PLAY]
[SPARKLING SOUND EFFECT]
(Lion 1)
Oh, you surprised me
It's been a long time since I've been startled by a person, hey, right?
(Lion 2)
Me too
But what’s with the chicken place? Out of the blue
(Lion 3)
That person from just now lives in our building below
It would be nice if we could sell to someone we know
(Lion 1)
Yeah, right, um, let’s eat quickly and go, okay
Oh, it’s chaotic at the beginning of the year
so I’m really struggling, sigh
(Sunny)
Enjoy your meal
(Lion 2)
We didn’t order this.
(Sunny)
It's a service, since a new menu came out
You must be working hard
(Lion 1)
Oh dear, really, thank you for recognizing that...
[LION 4'S GASP]
(Lion 4)
The taste is amazing, right?
Why are you all like this?
- (Lion 3) Eat, eat
- (Lion 4) Yes, dip it in the sauce
[TENSE SOUND EFFECTS]
(Lion 2)
What is it?
The deceased shows up in front of the grim reaper without fear?
It's been a while
Have you been living as a grim reaper during that time?
What are you talking about?
Do you know me?
I know it all
Don't mess around
(Chorus)
Aren't you curious about who I am?
Why I stand so confidently in front of you
But more than that
Aren't you curious about who you are?
Go and take that woman's hand
The owner of the shop who just came out
(Chorus)
They say that the grim reaper takes those who committed great sins in their past lives
Your sins must be inside that
Also
I too will be within those sins
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
(Shin)
I have never erased my memory
I just chose to erase it myself
Still
It seems like a divine plan
(Shin)
Or does it seem like a mistake?
[SIGH]
What are you thinking so much about?
Thoughts that shouldn't be
Why do you think them knowing you shouldn't?
Because if I don't do it today, I think I'll do it tomorrow
Please don't do that
(Lion 3)
The atmosphere is not good right now
Regarding the Kim case from Janghang-dong
A directive has come down from the underworld
What did you say?
'Do not forget that you are sinners'
(Grim reaper 3)
Ha, I’m really feeling uneasy for no reason
This is the list for this month
Did you give an answer?
Did you give a question?
I handed over the list?
[SAD MUSIC]
I’m back
(Grim reaper)
It’s after three hours
The cause of death is myocardial infarction
Even for the last farewell
I’ve said everything I wanted to say while living
Until the end
I don’t want to see you looking sorry for me
You take care of the farewell instead of me...
Don't worry
Be sure to be reborn
In the next life
Don't be tied to anyone
Live freely
(Kim Shin)
I was grateful
I was really grateful
[SIGH]
[The door opens and closes softly]
What’s the matter?
Have the black clothes ready
(Grim Reaper)
The obituary for Chairman Yoo will come soon
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC]
Let me take a look at the author
[THE DOOR OPENS SOFTLY]
[Eun Tak's sigh]
[Kim Shin is sobbing]
[KIM SHIN CONTINUES TO SOB]
[THE RAIN IS POURING DOWN]
(Deokhwa)
♪ You don't know my heart
It's too much, too much ♪
Ah, gosh, it's too much
Oh my, my back
Just wait till I become the boss, really
I'll come to work here every day and have company dinners every day
I'll definitely send you off in a model taxi, I will
I'll compliment your outdated clothes so much
That you'll end up wearing those clothes all the time, I will
[THE DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES WITH A BANG]
Deokhwa
(Deokhwa)
What is it?
Is Grandpa watching me work, very openly?
You need to go together, right now.
I still have a long way to go until quitting time.
I've prepared the clothes, so
please change in the car.
What clothes?
[SAD MUSIC]
[TREMBLING BREATH]
"Yushinwoo"
(Kim Shin)
Every moment in this life was precious.
Here, I sleep.
Yushinwoo
[TEARS DROP SUDDENLY]
"Yushinwoo"
[HEAVY MUSIC]
(Euntak)
So this is it.
Immortality.
[EUNTAK'S SIGH]
Chairman Yoo will keep looking back.
'It's really
concerning, isn't it?'
So
the remaining person has to live hard
Sometimes it's okay to cry
But also to laugh a lot
And to be brave
That's
what respect is for the love received
Warm things
Would you like something to eat?
Deokhwa
I'll bring him and we can eat together
(Euntak)
Ah...
(Deokhwa)
What should I do?
I couldn't even show filial piety
[sniffling]
I'm sorry
If you go without waiting for me like this
What should I do, uncle?
I'm sorry, grandfather.
[Kim Shin pats Deok-hwa's back]
[Deok-hwa sobs]
What should I do now?
What should I do alone now?
(Kim Shin)
Why are you alone?
Uncle
Yeah, uncle is here
Let's stay together with uncle
Don't worry about anything, okay?
Uncle
[DEOK-HWA CONTINUES TO SOB]
(Kim Shin)
Get up, let's eat something
(Grim Reaper)
Even if the apple is a rabbit?
(Kim Shin)
Should I do 'Gold, come out, tick-tock'?
[DEOKHWA'S SIGH]
(Grim Reaper)
Should I do that thing where I swipe against the wall?
(Euntak)
Brother, please take my camera
You liked this, right?
[Sighing]
It's fine
My grandfather picked this out for you
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you in advance
I wonder if I should have given you time
to sort out your feelings
I regret it
But there is order in the world...
(Deokhwa)
I know
My family has been dealing with the goblin spirit
for several generations now
[DEOKHWA'S SIGH]
(Dukhwa)
Thank you all
Then I have things to do
(Dukhwa)
I was worried my grandfather would be concerned the whole time
[I SMILE FAINTLY]
You know our grandfather's personality
I know
Mr. Kim has been appointed as the CEO of the company
Grandfather had everything ready
That's good
Anyway, I'm still not prepared
[I PLACE THE DISH DOWN WITH A CLATTER]
Right
I'll learn to work well from the ground up
That's what our grandfather would want
Yeah
Go game
I will learn.
So, my uncle's brother, my father.
My grandfather will try to do well.
Like our grandfather.
[SOFT MUSIC]
Yeah.
[A SIGH]
(Chairman Yoo)
One day, someone who writes 'the god to be trusted' in the Kim family name will come.
They will say, 'I have come to find my belongings.'
Then give it to them.
Everything I left behind belongs to that person.
That person will walk through the rain and go with blue flames.
Then know they are Kim Shin.
[Footsteps echo]
[Significant music]
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECTS]
(Three Gods)
You went?
(Deokhwa)
Do you know that person?
(Three Gods)
I know, it’s a child with nothing but goodness
So it's a child that brightens the world
Your fortune comes from your own heart, don’t forget
Yeah, well, it’s not really a child
Do you want to have a drink with me?
(Three Gods)
Drink with beautiful people
You’re beautiful
I said to drink with people
[THE THREE GODS SMILES SLIGHTLY]
Hello
What is it?
[A RIDICULOUS GROAN]
What are you doing so much?
Deokhwa is coming.
[The Grim Reaper's Sigh]
(Kim Shin)
Oh, a bit of pepper
(Grim Reaper)
I'm jealous of Deokhwa, he has an uncle
[sprinkles the pepper]
Don't worry about it
These days, I feel envious and nostalgic and stuff
Just say it plainly, what I envy is your uncle
(Kim Shin)
He's a really handsome uncle
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
[TENSE MUSIC]
Why?
When did you say you became a reaper?
(Grim Reaper)
It's been a little over 300 years, why?
[THE GRIM REAPER PUTS DOWN THE POTATO KNIFE WITH A THUD]
Did I get something on me?
Just
For a very brief moment
An unfamiliar face that I couldn't see before is stuck to you
Who? What face?
A face that shouldn't be seen by my eyes
[DEOKHWA'S SIGH]
(Deokhwa)
Uncle!
Ah, whether you sit down, help, or go in
Why do you keep fiddling around?
I am feeling proud that you are useful
(Deokhwa)
Huh, really
As for being the third generation of a conglomerate, it's only right
Overtime work is also considered part of the management class...
Uncle, what's wrong?
[HEAVY SOUND EFFECT]
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
[I RUMMAGE THROUGH MY POCKETS]
(Euntak)
Today is the first opening, first college student
Today's opening party, so a short skirt
No
I'll be back
(Kim Shin)
Deokhwa will take me
I have another engagement today
If anything happens...
(Euntak)
I know everything
Perfect, right?
One is missing
(Euntak)
Ah...
I know what it is
[AHEM]
[SOFT MUSIC]
(Kim Shin)
I know why I close my eyes, but then I don't
(Eun Tak)
Huh?
It's perfect now
This is from that maple country
(Eun Tak)
Oh, that's a bit moving?
But what does it say?
In French
it means 'the destiny determined by the heavens'
(Kim Shin)
An absolute destiny that transcends the realm of humans
It's a word I like, 'destiny'
How did you know?
(Kim Shin)
No meetings, no blind dates
No romance
Taehee oppa is not allowed
Any man within a 30-centimeter radius of this necklace
is not allowed
What I think destiny is, is that
Ah, really
So that's why I went to college
There’s no room, is it decided by the heavens?
(Kim Shin)
It’s late, go and come back
I will be back
[SOFT MUSIC]
[MOBILE PHONE OPERATION SOUNDS]
[MOBILE PHONE NOTIFICATION SOUNDS]
(Euntak)
Safely and brilliantly
I arrived at school.
I’m worried that you might go to hell because of me.
I will send you off.
Prior engagements are fighting for me.
Sigh, I’m wearing the necklace well.
I took pictures so that no men appear around.
You look pretty.
[THE SOUND OF A CELLPHONE OPERATION]
[THE DOOR OPENS WITH A CLICK]
[WOOSHIK’S TENSE BREATHING]
[FOOTSTEPS ECHO]
[SOFT MUSIC]
[A SIGH]
[NERVOUS BREATHING]
(Subordinate)
[sniffling]
I heed the command of the General.
Please forgive me.
[THE SUBORDINATE IS CHOKED WITH EMOTION]
I will follow soon to meet you.
[The subordinate stabs deeply with a knife]
[The subordinate's strained groan]
[A PAINFUL GROAN]
[THE SUBORDINATE SOBS]
[THE SOLDIER'S SHOUT]
[WOO-SIK'S CLEAR THROAT]
[WOO-SIK CLEARS HIS THROAT]
The path must have been misaligned
For me to be alive like this
It must have been very lonely
Please forgive me
- (Staff) Mr. Kim Woo-Sik
- (Woo-Sik) Yes
(Staff)
Mr. Choi Sang-Min, Ms. Lee Ji-Yeon, come in
[Man 2 responds]
- Yes
- (Woman) Yes
[THE DOOR OPENS WITH A CLICK]
[THE DOOR CLOSES WITH A CLICK]
(Wooshik)
You said it stuck?
[GASP OF EMOTION]
Thank you, really thank you
[gentle music]
[A MOAN OF EMOTION]
(Wooshik)
Honey
[WOOSHIK'S WIFE'S SURPRISED GASP]
It stuck
[Wooshik's wife sobs]
(Child 1)
Dad
(Wooshik)
Oh my, our daughter
[LAUGHTER FROM WOOSHIK AND HIS WIFE]
Shall we eat Jajangmyeon, huh?
[A SURPRISED MOAN]
It's a house provided by the company
For me?
Yes, because you did well in the interview.
[CAR REMOTE CONTROL
OPERATING SOUND]
(Kim Secretary)
This is a vehicle provided
by the company. (Woosik)
Me?
(Kim Secretary) Yes, you did really
well in the interview. (Woosik) No..
.
(Kim Secretary)
This is the name of the boy who will
be born on May first. He will be a great person who
brightens the world for generations to come. (Woosik)
My child?
Yes. (Woosik) I, but I've
been wondering who you are..
. Ah, I apologize for
the late introduction.
I am Kim Do-young, the
president of Cheonwoo Group. The president?
Oh, oh, I'm sorry I didn't
recognize you. (Woosik) I, but, so...
Why are you giving me such an undeserved thing?
Did you save a nation in your past life?
Me?
Yes
[CELL PHONE RINGTONE]
[CELL PHONE OPERATION SOUND]
Hello
Where are you right now?
What time is it right now that you’re not coming home in this rough world?
It's 5 PM now
And the sun is still high in the sky
Please stop nagging me
Stop nagging? Where are you?
(Kim Shin)
I've been asking since earlier!
Me?
(Eun Tak)
You’d be shocked if you knew where I was
[EUN TAK BLOWS AIR THROUGH HER LIPS]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
[EUN TAK SMILES SLIGHTLY]
I'm right here, in a cramped and narrow place
(Kim Shin)
You absolutely
Uh, over there, over there, over there, over there
One, two, three
[Guide voice]
Act cute
[CAMERA SHUTTER SOUND]
Oh, that turned out well
(Eun Tak)
Oh, look at you smiling in the midst of all this chaos
When will you get out of there?
I don’t know
Maybe in about 5 minutes?
Why in about 5 minutes?
In the meantime
there might be something that makes your heart flutter
In a cramped and narrow place
Don't let that happen, okay?
But it probably will
[EUNTAK RUMMAGES THROUGH HER BAG]
(Euntak)
Like this
Eight thousand won rounded up
comes to five thousand two hundred ten won
See, it's heart-fluttering, right?
[KIM SHIN CLICKS HER TONGUE]
Ah, how are you going to pay back this money
in such a cramped and narrow place?
With that money, hurry up and pay back the sweet potato cost
to our boss
They told you to pay it back quickly?
I want to see my sister, but since there's
the current situation with the boss.
It's awkward to go, and if I
don't go, I miss you, right?
(Eun-tak)
So, to pay back for the sweet potato price
You made it an excuse to see my face
Do you want to go with me to my part-time job?
I do want to see you, but your boss is scary
I’ll go next time, next time
[EUN-TAK'S LAUGHTER]
Oh, amazing, real siblings?
Just go out
(Kim-shin)
Ah, ah, already?
Why?
It’s really cold outside
How's school? Is it doable?
But you know Tae-hee oppa
What a jerk...
Did you ask about him? You asked about school, right?
No
Taehui oppa is going to America, the Major League
Goblin
is said to recognize people who will become great
I was going to say that's cool
It feels like I'm bragging, but
I had been recognizing for a long time that Jeongsung would become a great person
Hwanghee was a representative of that
Myeong Saseong, that friend too, really
.[Euntak clicks her tongue]
I understand
Sigh, the adults are saying something
I'm busy
[Bright music]
(Euntak)
I was late for my part-time job, you know?
It's narrow and cramped here
What does Hwang Hee mean?
I’ll be back
Um, well, okay
If anything happens, call me
[THE DOOR FLIES OPEN]
It's very troublesome since it's so narrow and cramped
'Narrow and cramped' is the same thing
Ah, I want to come every day
(Child 2)
Lightning bolt!
[EUNTAK LETS OUT A GROAN]
[LAUGHTER]
(Euntak)
Come here, come to your sister
[EUNTAK'S LAUGHTER]
[TENSE MUSIC]
[TENSE SOUND EFFECTS]
It's late
Go straight home, Grandma is waiting.
[Mysterious sound effect]
(Jungheon)
I see you again.
I think I didn't greet you properly back then.
[NERVOUS SOUND EFFECT]
I am called Park Jungheon.
Seeing your face, you already know me.
I don't know.
(Jungheon)
Kim Shin.
Didn’t he tell you?
The one who killed me is that guy.
The punishment Kim Shin is receiving
grows heavier with the weight of a life.
Inside that is the price of my life too.
What do you want?
There is no such thing
I'm just trying to tell an interesting story
(Jungheon)
You, or rather Wang-yeo, would know
That black blade piercing Kim Shin's heart
Was granted by Wang-yeo
The beginning and end of this tragic fate
Is none other than Wang-yeo
Do you know who that Wang-yeo is living with now?
How would I know that?
Wang-yeo is now
Living with Kim Shin
Ha, what nonsense...
[TENSION-BUILDING SOUND EFFECT]
That's right.
(Junghun)
The nameless grim reaper
That person is Wang Yeo
If those two come to recognize each other
What do you think will happen?
Ah
It seems that whether Kim Shin will kill me or save me
Depends on your hands
As Kim Shin's death depended on your hands
[JUNGHUN'S EXCLAMATION]
Now I see, you are
A child that governs death
I misunderstood
The grim reaper we know
Has a name
Kim Woo-bin
[The door closes with a click]
[Laughter]
[JUNGHUN TAKES A BREATH]
(Junghun)
Did you ask what I want?
I want their downfall
[TREMBLING BREATH]
[HEAVY MUSIC]
[EUNTAK SCRIBBLES WITH A PEN]
(Deokhwa)
What are you doing? Not moving aside
Let's just take one for ourselves
(The Grim Reaper)
No, I was sitting first
[HEAVY MUSIC]
(Junghun)
Wangyeo is currently
Living with Kimshin
[SIGH]
Ah, I’m losing my mind
(The Grim Reaper)
Guitar missing person
Ah, ah, me...
[SIGH]
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
I'll eat well
(The Grim Reaper)
I'm sorry for surprising you
(Euntak)
Is something wrong?
Did you come on purpose?
I'm frustrated
and there's nowhere else to talk
What is it?
About the boss?
In many ways
if you commit a great sin in your past life
you become a Grim Reaper
What sin?
I don't know that either
But somehow
it feels like I'm part of the history
of Kim Shin and Kim Sun siblings
[Heavy music]
In that history
There are three people
who committed a great sin.
(The Grim Reaper) Kim Shin, who
beheaded thousands of enemies.
Such a Kim Shin and
The king ordered the
death of Queen Kim Sun.
To persuade such a king.
Kim Shin, the one who drove Kim Sun
and her younger brother to their deaths.
Park Joong-heon
Kim Shin is
Still alive.
Kim Sun-eun was reborn as Sunny.
Then I am
Wang Yeo
Or could it be Park Joong-heon?
This is my thought up to here.
(The Grim Reaper) The
nameless Grim Reaper
He is the king.
(The Grim Reaper) But
Either of you, I am.
That must be Kim Shin's enemy.
Either one of them, I'm.
With Sunny.
I guess we won't
be able to meet.
[A SIGH]
[SUNNY'S FORCEFUL MOAN]
[PUT THE KEY IN CAREFULLY]
[SUNNY'S SIGH]
[Surprised] Oh my,
be surprised, oh my
Uh, I almost hit you.
I'm sorry, it seems
I startled you.
Uh, yeah, a bit.
What should I do?
The door is closed.
That's right.
See you next time.
[TENSE MUSIC]
[MYSTERIOUS BREATH]
(Ah...)
Yes, come again next time
[meaningful sound effect]
(The Young Prince)
Absolutely not.
Do not bring any medicinal
potion into the empress's chamber.
The king above the common
people, the god above the king.
(It is said that the god
refers to Kim Shin.)
[MUSIC THAT HEIGHTENS TENSION]
[SIGH]
[MOBILE PHONE VIBRATION SOUND]
chi
[CLEARS THE THROAT]
[MOBILE PHONE OPERATION SOUND]
Hello
(Grim Reaper) Let's meet.
Are you saying we
should break up?
(Grim Reaper) This is
in front of Sunny's house.
(Sunny) Just wait a minute!
I'm going crazy.
[I GRAB THE COSMETICS]
[A GROAN OF CONCERN]
[A SIGH]
[GASPING BREATH]
What should I do if you
suddenly come like this?
(Sunny) I'm at home, so
I'm showing my bare face.
I came out to get my ring back.
We still have that excuse left.
Why does your
expression look like that?
Did you come here because
you wanted to see me?
That's right.
- But?
- (The Grim Reaper) However
I don't know who I am.
With a fearful heart
I back down.
What are you doing now?
I'm the one who is
completely wrong.
[A SIGH]
Please let this be the answer.
I hope.
- Don't do that - To
me who is not alive
There is no name.
(Grim Reaper) To me like that
[TENSE MUSIC]
Greetings
Thank you for asking.
Don't do that.
(The Grim Reaper) The
Grim Reaper's kiss is
It makes me
remember my past lives.
In your past life
I am afraid of what
I might have been.
But I hope you only
remember the good memories.
Inside it
I wish there were
memories of your brother too.
I wish it would be good.
(The Grim Reaper) And
If that person is Kim Shin
It would be nice.
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
Your brother has
made progress again.
Which one of us
would you prefer to live?
- Your Majesty - (Young
Prince) Please answer.
(Young King) Or has the
calculation already been made?
Well, whether I live
or my brother lives
I have nothing to lose.
You are ugly.
Do you want to die?
Why do you look like that?
[SNORT]
Already, a portrait has
emerged in your heart.
Bring the empress's jewelry box!
[THE VALUABLES ARE SPILLING OUT]
Why don't you
carry it on your body?
Do you think I told you
to put these things here!
I can no longer know.
Is the barbarian from the frontier the
enemy? Is your brother the enemy...
Park Jung-heon is the enemy.
[TREMBLING BREATH]
[A SIGH]
The enemies couldn't
kill your brother.
I will kill today.
Your Majesty!
(Young Prince) Your
brother's crime is
It's treason.
So wear this and
be like an empress.
Welcome the treacherous brother.
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
Whose side are you on?
Have you ever been
on my side even once?
Have I ever truly been
in your heart even once?
Have you ever loved me,
even for just a moment...?
Are you there?
[SIGH]
[A SIGH]
Do not stand by his side.
That’s it.
That is the only
way you can live.
You will have to choose.
Whether to live as my woman
As the sister of
a great criminal.
Whether to die
The woman who loves the emperor
She is the sister
of the criminal.
[TREMBLING BREATHS]
What is this?
Things I've seen
What is it?
It's your past life.
[A GASP OF SURPRISE]
By any chance
In your past life
Is Kim Shin here?
[TREMBLING BREATH]
By any chance
In your past life
Do I also exist?
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
[TREMBLING BREATH]
[SOBBING]
Wait a moment.
Can you look into my eyes?
Leaving only the moments
that sparkled with happiness
It's hard and
Forget all the sad moments.
(The Grim Reaper) Whether
in a past life or this life
And
I forget too.
[SNIFFLES]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
(The Grim Reaper) Only you
I hope it's a happy
ending even like this.
[TREMBLING BREATH]
[SOBBING]
"Closure"
"Opening"
(Sunny) Are you there, brother?
Why are you staring
at my store again?
What is it today?
Decorative charm?
Medicinal candy? Socks?
Today is not like that.
(Kim Shin) The price
of my sweet potatoes...
Really now.
Let's say that was
me who shot it.
But, brother.
Your Majesty, really
Did you say I'm ugly?
No matter how much I wander
the battlefield, I'm still a brother.
Why didn't you reply even once?
Truly
Truly, you...
(Sunny) [Sobbing] I'm sorry
for realizing it too late, brother.
The promise to be happy
I couldn't keep it.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC]
I'm sorry, brother.
[FOOTSTEPS ECHO]
[A STARTLED BREATH]
[KIM SHIN'S TREMBLING BREATH]
[SUNNY IS SOBBING]
[SHAKING BREATH]
ripe persimmon,
flower shoes, silk
Thank you.
[Kim Shin's trembling
breath] [Sunny sniffles]
[KIM SHIN'S TREMBLING BREATH]
[THE SIGHS OF
KIM-SHIN AND SUNNY]
(Sunny) Now, you must come
to see this ugly sister often.
"Ji Eun-tak, 20 years old"
[THERE'S A KNOCKING SOUND]
End room uncle, if you’re
not busy, please help me.
[SMILES GENTLY]
[DEOK-HWA PLACES THE
GO STONE DOWN SHARPLY]
[THE GRIM REAPER IS
CLACKING THE GO STONES WELL]
Is something wrong?
Just
It's taking a bit longer.
Did you fight with
your uncle again?
No
Before that
Since that day, sometimes.
When?
[SIGH]
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
[I BRUSH IT ON
BRISKLY WITH A BRUSH]
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
[LABORIOUS MOAN]
(Sunny) What's
wrong? Are you hurt?
[THE GROAN OF THE
GRIM REAPER IN PAIN]
[GROANS OF PAIN]
"King's Daughter"
(Duckhwa) [Sighing] On that day
It's not because of our uncle.
We were at the temple at that time.
At the temple?
(Donghwa) Yes,
uncle has lit the lantern.
You do that once a year.
Those who owe a debt to their uncle's heart
They say they commemorate him like that.
It was a two-letter name.
With Kim Sun.
King, what was it, with
the Chinese characters?
[THE GO STONE IS PLACED DOWN]
What happens if
this is the case?
donkey
(ghost) Hey
Huh, look at this?
You're pretending
not to see again?
Hey, you nasty girl!
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[CREEPY SOUND EFFECT]
[EUNTAK COLLECTS BOOKS]
It's not that I'm
pretending not to see.
[SIGNIFICANT MUSIC]
He really can't
see me right now.
Me too.
(Eun-tak) Yes?
I'm excited to pick you
up from school, me too.
Ah...
Mr. Kim Shin is coming to pick me
up at that school, and I'm so excited!
[EUNTAK SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(Kim Shin) Sure, I got it.
I have something to think about.
But is there something good happening?
You've been a bit off since earlier, right?
I ask early, too.
My sister, our Seoni
remembered me.
(Euntak) Really? Really?
Ah, that's good.
But how?
Ah, I didn't ask that.
(Kim Shin) That's right, how
did the past life come to mind?
Why does your
expression look like that?
So
Could you please pull
over the car for a moment?
(Eun-tak) Please don't get angry
and listen to what I have to say.
I’ve been 고민 중이었거든요 too.
What is it?
The uncle is a bigger
person than I had thought.
I believe you, really.
What is going on?
I am
(Seung-tak) I came across
some deceased person.
It seems it's definitely
Park Jung-heon.
[TENSE MUSIC]
You
How do you know Park Joong-heon?
I'm sorry, but
I heard the conversation you had
with the Grim Reaper back then.
(Euntak) At first, I thought
it was just an evil spirit.
I'm not sure what
the purpose is.
It feels like all the strange things
happening around me are somehow connected.
It seems like the boss remembers
their past life because of that too.
You did well in
talking, thank you.
I'll take you home for
now, so stay put at home.
The goblin's house
site is the safest.
Yes
[TENSE MUSIC]
[GLOOMY SOUND EFFECTS]
[ tense sound effects ] [ a
cracking sound is heard ]
[CACKLING]
[PAINFUL MOAN]
[Dark Music] [Jeongheon’s
Strained Moan]
[LABORED BREATHING]
I’ve been avoiding for 900
years, and yet here we meet.
It's futile.
Don't worry.
I will get rid of it right away.
One
I have been
avoiding the year 900.
Now I must answer the
reason I caught your eye.
As expected, he comes
from a lowly noble background.
Even after 900 years, you
still don't possess insight.
It's amusing to see someone unable to
recognize an enemy right next to them.
I intend to let you
know personally.
As expected, your tongue is
still cursed even after 900 years.
I will first pull out my tongue.
(Kim Shin) Then I
will tear apart the body.
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
I will do them now.
[ROUGH BREATHING]
[TENSION-FILLED MUSIC]
You and I have been
through 900 years.
That mere sword of
water cannot cut me.
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
(It's been a while) I have
been living as a guardian deity.
Did you really think you
had become a god of heaven?
[INHALE]
I will kill you no matter
what. Don't get in my way.
[TENSE SOUND EFFECTS]
[SMILES SLIGHTLY]
[TENSION-INDUCING SOUND EFFECT]
(So foolish) That is how
one loses their life so trivially.
During those 20 years
when you were rotting away.
It grew so much that
I couldn't recognize it.
opening
If you mention her
name one more time...
(Chungheon) Do you know who
that grim reaper beside you is?
Lower the sword.
The one who plunged that
sword into your heart is that person.
That person is 바로.
King Yeoda
[HEAVY MUSIC]
Crazy sound
(As I said) Your foolish sister
I have fallen for that
person in this life as well.
Alas
[TREMBLING BREATH]
You can't get your
revenge after all.
(Kim Shin) You cried, right?
Why are you crying?
I'm not crying either.
But who is she? The
woman in this picture.
[ tense music ] ( Grim Reaper ) I
have no memories, only feelings.
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
I was just really sad.
My heart hurt so much.
(Kim Shin) A really
handsome uncle
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
(Grim Reaper) Have you
ever seen a ring like this?
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[MYSTICAL SOUND EFFECTS]
"Kim Sun, Wang Ye"
[HE/SHE PRESSES THE SWITCH DOWN]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
In your previous life
Is that person in the afterlife?
Have you seen that
person from the afterlife?
Hey, brother.
What kind of nonsense is this, coming
into someone else's business like this?
(Sunny) I said I remember everything from my past
life, so I guess you think I’m really Kim Sun...
That guy
Is it really Wang-yeo?
I have to go home...
(김신) He asked if
that person is Wang Ye.
[HEAVY MUSIC]
[A SIGH]
You are
In this life as well
You're protecting that fool.
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
[A SIGH]
[HEAVY MUSIC]
(Grim Reaper) Was that so?
Was I Wang Ye?
The feelings that
remain without memory
Don't forget that
I am the queen.
Give it to yourself.
Was I a bee?
[DARK MUSIC]
(The Grim Reaper)
As expected, I am
It seems to be the worst memory.
From you too.
Kimshin, from
that person as well.
(Kim Shin) Can
you hear my voice?
I can hear your voice too.
very vividly
[MUSIC THAT ELEVATES
THE ATMOSPHERE]
[MILITARY TRAINING]
General Kim Shin
I meet Your Majesty.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
This beautiful dress is
(Wang-yeo) There is no master.
perhaps
Are you looking for it?
Then
Take it.
[THROWS THE CLOTHES ASIDE]
It is a royal decree.
[SIGH]
Subtitle: Choi Hye-ran