[THEME SONG]
[CALM MUSIC]
[IT RUMBLES]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
I saw it from the first time, this sword
So what am I now?
Am I still not the goblin bride?
No?
I think it might be right
Really?
Then do I
get a utility value, is that what happens?
Then are you not leaving anymore?
For now
I might have to prepare to leave further
What does that mean?
It means you are the goblin bride
I don't think that's it
I saw it from the beginning
Why did you pretend you couldn't see it all this time?
At first, it was out of courtesy
Then I was scared
In detail
(Euntak)
I thought it wasn't polite to ask someone I just met about their pain
Then if I said I could see it
I felt like something would happen
So I didn't say anything
Isn't it immediately saying let's get married? Then what about my university?
Am I possibly becoming a goblin?
Above all, I wonder if I have some money.
Pretending not to see was after that
I was upset
It's short, the period
What should I do now? As a bride?
The first thing you have to do as a bride is
Now, just wait here
[KIM SHIN'S URGENT BREATHING]
(Kim Shin)
Look at that guy with the sword
That guy pointed at the sword, like this
I got it, so go out
That guy is looking at the sword
That guy is my bride
I’m going to die now!
(Reaper)
Ah, but? Then isn’t that a good thing?
Weren't you looking for a bride to die?
A bride that will let you return to nothingness
a universally beneficial bride
That's right, almost a lifetime
Then what's the problem?
Why, do they say they will kill you?
I'm not in the mood for jokes?
(Grim Reaper)
Exactly how are you not in the mood?
Well, is he happy or scared
to see the sword?
I don't know
(Kim Shin)
Now I can finally end this tedious immortality
I feel both relieved and...
Well, it wasn't always
boring I still want to live
a bit more (the Grim
Reaper) Just say the word, if
[WORSE COMES TO WORST, I'LL
TAKE YOU WITH GRAND MUSIC]
It's a kid I had to take anyway, well,
because of the
paperwork I might have to
stay up for a few nights,
but did it sound like that?
Oh, Kim Shin's
[URGENT BREATHING]
(Kim Shin) It's accurate, I'm
finally happy that we have
[FORMED A FRIENDSHIP, THE DOORBELL RINGS]
Death is calling me
(the Grim Reaper) If it's to
the point of ringing the
doorbell It's a kind death.
Calm down, you haven't said anything harsh that
you would normally hold a grudge over, right?
(Kim Shin)
There is a way to die as originally intended
Since it's a life lived on a whim...
It's just a side effect
I'd rather just die, that feels cleaner
[sighing]
Yeah, let's do that
I told you to wait a moment
Can't you wait for that?
(Kim Shin)
You really have no patience!
(Grim Reaper)
Go harder
You die once, not twice?
I'm sorry, but I can't wait any longer
Ever since I found out I'm the Goblin's bride
I've been waiting for you the whole time
For a very long time
(Euntak)
Aunt has left home
But she took the deposit and left
So that means I have no home or place to go
So I was thinking
You said you won't leave either
[A PITIFUL SIGH]
(Grim Reaper)
You really decided not to leave?
(Euntak)
I'm going to grow up in this house
Otherwise, adoption is fine too
I’ll grow like a cactus
I’ll take care of myself, please
I agree.
(Heentak)
If I were to speak for myself
I wanted to be an ordinary
high school senior in South Korea,
but
I became an orphan at the age of nine
and have been living in neglect...
(Grim Reaper)
I know this story
[in a small voice]
I've watched this drama
[KIM SHIN'S FRUSTRATION MIXED WITH A GROAN]
Without a mother, under a sky without a mother
I’ve endured the nagging of my aunt and siblings
for nearly 10 years
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
I hope it ends with a happy ending
(Heentak)
I finally realized.
There is no god
This mishmash of a life, where all sorts of misfortunes are thrown in
In the midst of absurdity
I met the uncle
As if by fate
So please save me, I beg you
[SIGH]
Hey, you’re asking for help
And even after seeing who lives in this house
You still want me to let you in?
[SIGH]
If it's not this house
It's at least dying in an inn or of starvation
Whether I die this way or that way
(Euntak)
I just want to die beautifully in this house
They say it's dark under the lamp.
From today, please be my lampshade, uncle.
This uncle won't let me get carried away.
[A FAINT SIGH]
(Reaper)
Ah, I'm sorry
But there's already a friendship between us...
(Kim Shin)
Hey
You just stay inside for now.
Be in the living room, sit quietly.
(Eun Tak)
Yes
[KIM SHIN'S SIGH]
[THE DOOR CLOSES WITH A CLICK]
Look at me.
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
[EUN TAK'S EXCLAMATION]
[AMAZEMENT]
(Kim Shin)
What kind of friendship can't even last 5 minutes?
How can I say that?
Ah, is it a secret that you asked me to take you?
- You didn't know, right?
- (Kim Shin) Did you do that on purpose?
To a poor and pitiful kid who has nowhere to go
Ah, so that's why you left me out there?
It's cold outside?
You absolutely can't come out
What, what should I do? Is there a way?
[KIM SHIN'S SIGH]
(Kim Shin)
There is a way
It's a bit secular though
(Kim Shin)
I'm number two among one, two, three, five hundred
Why are you looking at me like that?
(Eun-tak) Hmm
What does it mean?
Put this money
(Euntak)
away
When I was talking about that
I was the me who didn't know much
Now
I've seen this house
So what does that mean
It's a perfect house to raise a child
[Lively music]
(Euntak)
Let's have our baby and
Live happily together
What type are you?
What, what, what, what is it?
Wife type, a virtuous woman?
(Euntak)
Sexy? Professional?
Ah, should I change it up every day?
You say you don’t like me, really don’t like me
I’ve made all sorts of noises, cancel
(Euntak)
Sir, you are really handsome
You’re really cool
Since I saw you, I don't really look at the stars
Why look at the stars? I can just look into your eyes
Sir, can you hear my big thoughts right now?
What are you doing, huh?
Even though you heard everything
I’m sorry, I keep
thinking too loudly inside, don’t I?
That’s a lie
What do you mean it’s a lie?
You said you could hear all my thoughts
back then, but
that's a lie from there.
So how did you know when
I was kidnapped back then?
I just felt it (Kim Shin)
I
don't know exactly, but I think
[IT'S BECAUSE OF THE MARK ON YOUR NECK]
Absurd breath.
Fraud (Eun-tak)
I was really
afraid you could hear my thoughts, so I thought
really small about you and split it up and
hummed songs in between and while looking at the
autumn leaves, I made excuses saying, 'I'm not
thinking about you' 'I'm thinking about the autumn leaves.'
When I think about my thoughts,
I was also being cautious, you know?
[I'M BEING BRAVE]
What? What do you mean?
While you were doing that, you slyly thought about me,
Why confess? It’s confusing.
What’s so confusing?
I am indeed a bride.
No, so should I unpack my things or not?
[EUN-TAK QUICKLY GATHERS THE ENVELOPES]
(Eun-tak)
I'm confused right now, that’s why.
It doesn’t seem like I’m confused.
(Kim Shin)
Just put the money down; don’t unpack.
(Eun-tak)
Ah, is there perhaps a number 4?
It must be something better, right?
(Deok-hwa)
Grandfather!
Huh?
(Eun-tak)
Why is he here, Grandfather?
(Deok-hwa)
Why are you here with him, Grandfather?
(Chairman Yoo)
He’s the grandson I mentioned.
That child will stay one floor below,
So if you need anything,
you can ask for anything, okay?
Me? Me?
Oh, there are several people in Grandfather's secretary room,
(Chairman Yoo)
Don’t you want to use the card at all?
(Dukhwa)
Among them, I am the most capable
I will serve you
My name is Yu Dukhwa
(Chairman Yu)
As you can see, he can't be trusted
If there are any unpleasant matters
You can contact me like this
(Euntak)
Ah, thank you
Is it the chairman?
The chairman's biological grandson, third-generation chaebol
[HE SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(Chairman Yu)
This must be tiring for you
Then I will take him now
(Dukhwa)
Ah, why? I have something to talk about with him.
[DEOKHWA'S PAINFUL MOANS]
Grandfather, grandfather
Ah, I will go, I will go
(Euntak)
Goodbye
[The door opens with a click]
[THE DOOR CLOSES WITH A CLICK]
(Euntak)
Sweet room
Amazing
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
[EUNTAK'S COMFORTABLE BREATHING]
Ah, it's good
It's good
It's a sweet room
I'm alone in a nice sweet room
(Euntak)
Tch
It's so spacious
It's scary to be alone
(Deokhwa)
But grandfather, who is that?
(Chairman Yoo)
You don't need to know
Just make sure you don't make things uncomfortable
and focus on serving them comfortably
[DEOK-HWA'S SIGH]
Something very important is in that person's hands
Important? What important thing?
[THE CAR DOOR CLICKS OPEN]
Your card
(Deok-hwa)
This is ridiculous
No, I'm the chaebol
[The car door slams shut]
Why is my card in the hands of some high school kid I've never seen before
Ha, seriously
(Deok-hwa)
Uncle, uncle
Well, grandpa has some girl...
Uncle, what's wrong? What's going on?
(Kim Shin)
This is a nervous breakdown
[Heavy music]
This is bipolar disorder
This is insomnia
So why are you taking that?
I'm extremely on edge right now
I was happy, sad, lonely, and radiant
I can't sleep
Why are you being lonely and radiant?
I've lost weight
[I'M TAKING MY MEDICATION PROPERLY]
What on earth is wrong with this guy, our uncle...
[SIGH]
(Deokhwa)
Why is uncle acting like this again?
The symptoms are the same.
If tears flowed the first time I saw a woman, it would be the
[SIGH OF THE GRIM REAPER]
What could that be?
[I TAKE MY MEDICINE WELL]
[I CHEW MY MEDICINE INTO PIECES]
(TV host)
Hello, viewers. Today, we will have a
family medicine specialist with us to take some
time to understand mental health.
(TV’s three
spirits)
Yes, while physical health is
important, many people tend to overlook mental health, right?
Bipolar disorder, neurosis, and insomnia are chronic
diseases that cling to modern people like a shadow.
First, the symptoms of bipolar disorder include
(Samshin)
impulsive buying.
If someone close to you suddenly buys a lot of things, be suspicious.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC]
Another symptom is
[KIMSHIN'S VIGOROUS SHOUT]
Excessive confidence develops,
[TV sound flows out]
Who wants to go to the sauna with me?
If you're not confident, don't.
[KIMSHIN'S SNICKER]
(Deokhwa)
Wow, this is really excessive.
End room uncle, let’s tie it up.
[The door opens with a click]
(Grim Reaper)
Challenge.
[THE GRIM REAPER’S STRAINING GROANS]
(Deokhwa)
Ha, I really...
[A SIGH]
(Samshin)
A typical symptom of neurosis is
health anxiety.
These days, I feel like I have a stomach ulcer
because my stomach has been upset continuously.
Just give me that.
[THE GRIM REAPER EXHALES HEAVILY]
You won't die even if you don't have a stomach,
you just can't eat.
The priest said you have to pull out your sword to die,
you
(Kimshin)
Ah, so I should die?
(Grim Reaper)
Ah, it was a consistent topic, but suddenly
[Smiling]
Unexpectedly?
(Kim Shin)
If someone heard, they'd think I'm the only strange
one
I'm the only narrow-minded one, someone like me should just
die
There's no value in living, why not just go over to her
and talk?
[ABSURD BREATHING]
Go draw the sword and kill me
I'm someone who deserves to die!
I’ll cry, really?
[Choking up] I’ve been
barely holding it together...
[SIGH]
[KIM SHIN SOBS]
Ha, should I just go out?
[THE DOOR SWINGS OPEN]
[GASPING BREATHS]
(Euntak)
Where's the bus stop?
[The sky rumbles]
Where is it?
[THE SKY RUMBLES]
Is the uncle feeling gloomy?
[THE RAIN IS POURING DOWN]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
(Eun-tak)
But it's funny
If you're gloomy at this timing,
it's going to hurt my heart
If you don’t like it, just say you don’t like it
Why make others uncomfortable,
why is there rain on the way to school?!
[EUN-TAK'S FRUSTRATED SIGH]
[THE SOUND OF AN APPROACHING CAR ENGINE]
[CAR HORN]
[THE CAR DOOR OPENS WITH A CLICK]
(Eun-tak)
Hello
(Deok-hwa)
I'll take you to school, get in
Ah, please speak casually
No, I don’t want to
I’m afraid you might tell my grandfather
I won’t tell
Even if you don’t tell, someone will
[CHEERFUL MUSIC]
[THE STUDENTS ARE BUZZING]
(Deok-hwa)
What are you doing? Get out, we’ve arrived
You can’t stay here
Just drop me off at the intersection ahead
Absolutely, never
(Deok-hwa)
To be a chaebol means to actually
Driving a sedan up to the school
I need to draw the public's attention
[DEOK-HWA CLICKS HIS SEATBELT OPEN]
[THE CAR DOOR SWINGS OPEN WITH A BANG]
[AN AWKWARD BREATH]
(Deok-hwa)
If you don't get out, we'll do it again tomorrow
Are you really not going to do it tomorrow?
(Deok-hwa)
Every day is boring
I've already attracted all the gazes
(Student 1)
Isn't that Ji Eun-tak?
Hurry up and go
Are you Ji Eun-tak?
(Eun-tak)
Yes, I’m sorry for the late introduction?
I am Ji Eun-tak...
(Duk-hwa)
Then you, that Shaba Shaba I Shaba
[Lively music]
You cried a lot, right?
Then that goblin book back then...
Oh, were you acquainted with our uncle?
Sigh, all the puzzles have been solved
Uncle?
Oh, what happened to your aunt?
That fine, that’s gold, no, fine, that
Fine, gold...
[THE BIRD CHIRPS]
Oh, what fine does our aunt have to pay?
[DUK-HWA'S SIGH]
I don't know.
I’m just curious about how our uncle punished us.
[THE GOLD AND SILVER SHOP OWNER'S BEWILDERED BREATHING]
Where did this come from?
Ah, why are you asking that?
(Gold and silver shop owner)
Yes?
Oh, if you’re going to buy it, then buy it, huh?
If you’re not, then don’t?
[THE GOLD AND SILVER SHOP OWNER'S EMBARRASSED GROAN]
[LAUGHTER]
It's just that this is such a good item.
[SMILES SLIGHTLY]
I received it as an inheritance, an inheritance.
Why does your face look like that?
I got hit by my mom.
[Playful music]
(Kyung-mi)
Please hit it a lot because it's
poor (Aunt Eun-tak)
This crazy...
That one barely got hit, it needs to be hit
more (Aunt Eun-tak) Shut up, you dog...
[In a small voice] What did I do, do you want me
to shut my mouth? [Kyung-mi's displeased breathing]
[LAUGHS AWKWARDLY]
[THE AWKWARD LAUGH OF
THE JEWELRY STORE OWNER]
Wait a moment, this is precious We need to prepare
properly to see it, okay? [Aunt Eun-tak's laughter]
[THE LAUGH OF THE JEWELRY STORE OWNER]
[THE JEWELRY STORE OWNER'S COUGH]
- (Aunt Euntak) Die, die, die, die - (Kyungsik)
Ah, why, why are you hitting me? [Kyungmi murmurs]
(Aunt Euntak)
Just get out, out, get out now
(Kyungsik)
Shut your mouth, girl
I'm so embarrassed,
damn it [Aunt Euntak drags the chair]
[Kyungmi's discontented groan]
(Aunt Euntak)
Stealing!
[Slamming the desk]
No, this is my nephew's, what I brought from the
drawer How many times do I have to say it, huh?!
(Kyungsik) That's stealing, Mom (Aunt Euntak)
Shut up, you bastard [Kyungsik's groan of pain]
Let's share it equally
You liked
it the most, you bastard [Aunt
Euntak's angry
breathing]
(Police)
Sit down (Aunt Euntak)
Ah, me!
[AUNT EUNTAK'S SIGH]
(Police) So this gold bar
belongs to your nephew?
(Aunt Euntak)
Yes, but why did
you lie earlier at the jewelry
store saying it was inherited?
(Aunt Euntak)
Ah, what lies am I telling?
When did I say I received
it as an inheritance?
Our nephew received it.
Their mom
So, our sister died
(Police)
Yes, it's okay, got it.
What is the date of birth and name of that nephew?
(Aunt Euntak)
That's right, he is now a high school student
in the 3rd year.
What is his name...
What is his name? Hey, what's his name?
- (Kyungmi) Eunji?
- (Kyungsik) Eunhee?
(Aunt Euntak)
Oh, these idiots really...
Are you not paying attention?
(Police)
Are you serious, damn it!
You came here to mess around right now? Tsk
[KYUNG-MI'S COUGH]
Now, listen carefully, okay?
So, you're saying that right now
your high school senior nephew, whom you don’t even know the name of,
made this at the Bank of Korea
(Police)
And right now, that New York Federal Reserve Bank
had this gold bullion that was just stolen!
So you're saying you just went ahead and stole it like this?
Isn't that right?
No, we didn’t steal it!
Oh, if you really don’t believe me,
Shouldn't you just go
home and ask him directly?
(Police) I asked, repeatedly
Give me the address, the address!
Ah, the address, Seongbuk-gu, Seoul...
Wait a minute, Seongbuk...
(Euntak's aunt)
Seongbuk-gu, Seoul...
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC]
What is it!
(Euntak's aunt) Hey, what was
the address of the house we lived in?
Did we have a house we lived in?
Where did we live?
[THE POLICE'S RIDICULOUS LAUGHTER]
Ah, these freaks, what is
this? This, this, this, this, this!
(Dukhwa)
Is he really our uncle the priest?
Why is he our uncle the priest?
Well, it's God's prank
Ah, that's why uncle is depressed
It's not his style?
Tsk, God was really playing around
[Sounds of flapping]
(Dukhwa)
But, uncle in the last room
That plate you just spilled
It's something our uncle treasures
Uncle says he bought it himself
during the time of Louis XIV...
[IT'S FLAPPING]
[SIGH]
He said
Dukhwa
I won't mention it
Ah, don't make such a serious face
It's scary
(Dukhwa)
Is it because of that woman?
You said you cried when you first saw her
Think carefully
Was it not your first time?
Ah, men shouldn't do that
Take responsibility
Even if uncle doesn't remember that day
That woman might remember
For that matter
Yes
She was very bright
It's Sunny
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
Her hair is like
Flipping like this and her lips...
This, like this...
This, this, what is this...
She was really a woman
I had never seen before.
Oh, what's with the
conversation going that way?
What do you mean by
'like this with the lips'? Huh?
Oh, what did the lips do?
[Tension-building sound effect]
[Rustling]
I won't ask.
Oh my, is it
already this time...
[SIGH]
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
[CARDIAC MONITOR BEEP]
[Cardiac monitor warning
sound] [Calm music]
[SIGH]
(Grim Reaper) What
are you wearing?
Is it a ceremony or a funeral?
Oh, is that why they
say marriage is a grave?
I’m feeling a bit solemn right now.
(Kim Shin)
I hope you answer my questions honestly.
You’re also involved in international affairs, right?
Oh, is your English not good enough for that?
[SNORT]
[English]
Wait, what did you say?
[Korean]
That’s good enough.
Unfortunately, I need your help.
Why, will you die if you go abroad?
[SLAMS DOWN THE PEN]
[SIGH]
This is too much, seriously.
Why are you ghosting me?
Why aren’t you coming?
Why aren’t you contacting me?
[SOUND OF FRUSTRATED BREATHING]
[CALM MUSIC]
[EUN-TAK'S HEAVY BREATHING]
(Eun-tak)
Open the door!
[Knocking loudly on the door]
It’s in front of the house, why are you avoiding me?
Come out, I know everything inside!
You’re not coming out, right?
If you don’t come out
I’m going to blow this out.
What this is
is a really long and big candle.
I will blow it!
I can’t guarantee where it will be blown out!
It’s going to be really rough and embarrassing
when I blow it out!
[SIGH]
[Choking up]
Am I still 'waiting for now'?
Until when is it 'waiting for now'?
[A SIGH]
[EUNTAK'S SIGH]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
[CALM MUSIC]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
[THE DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
It's been a while
You haven't aged at all
[THE DOOR SWINGS OPEN]
[THE DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
I told you the answer to question 17 is 4
but you wrote down 2
No matter how much I solve it, it's still 2
Even if I know the answer, it’s still true.
(Child) So I couldn't
bear to write it down.
That was a problem I couldn't solve.
No
You solved it very well
(Kim Shin)
Your life is only correct by your own choice.
Ah, so that's the kind of problem it was.
You became a lawyer
And helped many people in need
I want to repay you for the sandwich you gave me back then.
And I had no other choice.
I found out you were there.
An ordinary person
Can't forget the moments of miracles.
I know.
I handed sandwiches to thousands of people.
One, there are few who move on like you.
(Kim Shin)
Ordinary people
stop at that miraculous moment
and don't ask for help one more time
knowing that you are there
as if they have entrusted the miracle
Your life is changed by you alone.
For that reason, I have always supported your life.
I knew you would do that.
Where am I going now?
You just have to go out the door you came in.
The afterlife is a U-turn.
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[THE DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
(The Grim Reaper)
Just by looking, it seems like you're going to a good place, right?
That's right
Thank you for today
But why do this kind of work?
You don't have to do it
It's not like someone is forcing you like me
You really don't have to
But if I don't do this job, I won't be cool
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
[The door slams open and shut]
What would you expect
[THE ELEVATOR ARRIVAL SOUND]
[THE ELEVATOR DOORS SLOWLY OPEN]
[THE ELEVATOR DOORS SLOWLY CLOSE]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
(Eun-tak)
Where have you been? You weren't home.
(Kim Shin)
Did you come home?
(Eun-tak)
Why am I the one avoiding you?
(Kim Shin)
It's not that I was avoiding you, I was busy.
You were the one who was busy avoiding me.
(Eun-tak)
I see you don't even have a job.
Is that maybe what it is?
- Simple
- What?
(Eun-tak)
Then what is it?
Avoiding the goblin, saying it's not true
Avoiding it when you can't see the sword, and avoiding it even when you can see it.
It's pathetic, really, adults are pathetic!
Just try to run away
I will burn all of this
(Kim Shin)
You’re really pretty
(Eun Tak)
I’m serious right now?
Me too
But where did you, someone without any money,
get all this straw?
(Eun Tak)
From Yu Deok-hwa oppa
(Kim Shin)
This guy
Can’t I just live at that uncle’s house?
There are plenty of empty rooms
How would you know if a room is empty or occupied?
From Yu Deok-hwa oppa
This guy
(Eun Tak)
You said to wait for now.
For a while
is usually from one hour to a maximum of half a day.
How many days has it been, this?
In the meantime, it even rained.
I was feeling down, because of me?
No.
You can talk.
I've been preparing my mind for the past few days.
(Euntak)
I’m ready to accept whatever you say.
Why do you have to be ready?
(Kim Shin)
I’m in a situation where I have to be ready.
(Euntak)
What are you getting ready for?
(Kim Shin)
You don’t need to know.
[HE OPENS A CAN OF BEER]
[THE REFRIGERATOR DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
(Kim Shin)
What's for dinner?
Why, did you eat?
I can see the black
The uncle still isn't showing up
I didn't mean for it to be like this
(Eun Tak)
What kind of resolve do I need to have?
Don't do it alone, let's do it together!
Do you want to eat steak? Should I order room service?
Seeing you beat around the bush...
I'll let it slide, I'll
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
It doesn't feel like a beef day today, let's eat something else.
[SHE SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(Eun-tak)
The expensive things in the room
were tempting me, but
I didn't give in
Um, this is the taste
(Kim-shin)
Is that enough?
Choose whatever you want
I can buy everything from here to there
[LAUGHTER]
Lump sum
[THE ITEMS CLATTER AS THEY FALL]
(Eun-tak)
Ah, stand up straight for a moment
How do two cans of beer end up like this?
Should I buy you a toothbrush? From here to here
(Kim-shin)
Ta-da
Microfiber, uh
[KIM SHIN'S SMILE]
(Eun-tak)
Please stop going, just stop
(Kim Shin)
No, I'm going to see you home
(Eun-tak)
Am I really a priest? Really a priest?
First of all, what about that?
(Kim Shin)
Uh
Then I can't meet any other guys?
[KIM SHIN CHUCKLES]
Well, I wouldn't really recommend it
(Eun-tak)
Then what am I supposed to do about my third wish?
Part-time job, auntie's place, boyfriend, boyfriend!
That kind of thing will never happen in this life.
(Kim Shin)
Don't get your hopes up
(Eun Tak)
Why?
Because I don’t like you
Tch, how can that be?
[Calm music]
Mister, do you like me?
No
Your 'no' seems like a yes
(Eun Tak)
How have you been living all this time? What have you been doing?
(Kim Shin)
I've been living waiting for you
It's noisy
[In a small voice]
I said it softly
Then when you're feeling down, does it rain,
and when you're in a good mood, what happens?
(Kim Shin)
Pass
Is it possible that, like, flowers are blooming and stuff?
[EUNTAK SMILES SLIGHTLY]
No, next question
- Can you fly?
- (Kim Shin) It’s a piece of cake
(Euntak)
Show me next time
(Kim Shin)
Got it
How many brides am I?
[KIM SHIN SIGHS]
First and last
Let's say the first is fine
But how do you know it’s the last?
Because I decided so
What if
I say I won’t be a bride, what happens then?
(Kim Shin)
Uh...
[CALM MUSIC]
I can't draw this sword
Only you can do it
(Kim Shin)
[Clapping his chest]
I need to draw this sword, I
[SIGH]
I...
This, becoming pretty
I'm not pretty right now
Ah, is this maybe that thing?
(Euntak)
In fairy tales, why
When the cursed prince meets true love
He returns to his original form, that?
The frog prince goes from frog to prince
Beauty and the Beast goes from beast to prince.
The goblin brushes the snow...
[WHISPERS]
Let’s just leave it for next time, next time
when we need a broom
[LAUGHTER]
(Kim Shin)
You don't know what you're talking about
If I laugh in this situation right now,
I'm the crazy one
[SIGH]
Yeah, next time
Not today, today I'll just laugh with you
When the first snow falls?
First snow?
We’ll need a broom
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah
When the first snow falls
[EUNTAK SMILES SLIGHTLY]
I wonder when the first snow will come this year?
(Woman 1) This looks good here - (Woman 2)
Let's take a picture together
- (Woman 3)
I'm going to the back (Woman 2)
We have
to take a nice picture, ready [camera
shutter sound]
(Woman 1)
Look, what is this?
[calm music]
[camera shutter sound]
[CAMERA SHUTTER SOUND]
- (Woman 4) Pretty - (Woman 5) Yeah - (Woman 5) Wow, what is this place?
- (Woman 4) Want to take a picture together?
(Woman 6)
Oppa, take a
picture of me (Man 1)
One,
[TWO, THREE, EUNTAK SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(Woman 6)
It's amazing, really
[Camera shutter sound]
[DEOKHWA'S SIGH]
(Deokhwa)
Did something good happen overnight?
In this autumn, and overnight
these flowers bloomed like
this house, that house, all brightly
They bloomed very prettily
With snow and rain as weather anomalies
what can we muddle through?
What about the flowers, the flowers!
Uncle, you drank, didn't you?
'What about the flowers, the flowers'
'Uncle, you drank' are
all three sentences in informal speech?
Ah, shall we comfortably call each other brother?
Shall we?
Brother, what did you do with whom yesterday...
- You brat!
- (Deokhwa) I can’t remember, no!
Ah, what are you going to do!
It’s not because of the alcohol, it’s the anxiety medication
I’ll stop taking my medicine...
(Deokhwa)
Why did your voice suddenly turn cold
I can't figure it out
[KIM SHIN'S PAINFUL GROAN]
(Kim Shin)
What’s that?
(Deokhwa)
It’s an empty seat, let’s sit there
[DEOKHWA'S STRAINING GROAN]
Why are we meeting in a place like this?
Who?
(Reaper)
It's the last episode
I can't miss the last episode of a morning drama
(Man on TV 2)
Everyone carries at least one scar in their heart
[EXCITING MUSIC PLAYS IN THE BACKGROUND]
(Woman on TV 7)
A scar? Do you know what a scar is?
For me, separation will come sooner than death
Last night, I told you
I would buy you snacks, right?
[THE SOUND OF THE TV FLOWS IN]
I didn't, though?
Don't think carelessly, think carefully.
Don't just think about waking up casually.
Let's wake up properly from the alcohol.
(Grim Reaper)
Did the film cut again?
Two cans of beer?
(Kim Shin)
It's not because of alcohol, it's because of the drugs!
(Deok Hwa)
Uncle, what's wrong? That's scary.
[TENSE SOUND EFFECT]
Is there something here?
(Woman on TV 7)
Eun-bi, she's Hye-jin's daughter.
[Exciting music]
(Man on TV 2)
What?
(Together)
Awesome!
- (Man 3) Wow, is that your daughter?
- (Man 4) Was it a daughter?
(Woman 8)
Oh my
- (Man 5) That's too much, seriously
- (Man 6) I really didn't know
(Man 3)
That's amazing
(Deokhwa)
Are we going home?
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
[KIM SHIN'S SCREAM]
Eunbi is shocked that Hyejin is her daughter now?
[PLAYFUL MUSIC]
[SUCKING ON A DRINK]
What's this? What is this memory?
What do you mean? What's going on?
(Euntak)
If...
What will happen if I say I won't become a bride?
(Kim Shin)
I can't pull out this sword
Only you can do this
[KIM SHIN'S SCREAM]
(Kim Shin)
Crazy goblin!
[KIM SHIN'S SCREAM]
Ah, what should I do?
(Deokhwa)
Why? What's wrong?
(Kim Shin)
I told her all about pulling the sword
(Deokhwa)
Uncle, what are you looking at?
Is it that bad?
(Grim Reaper)
Well, since it's come to this, think positively
Even if you die now, it’s a good match.
You should talk like that
I'll blow up the hat!
[THE GRIM REAPER'S LAUGHTER]
(Deokhwa)
[smiling awkwardly]
A stranger, a stranger
Others, others, men
Goodbye, I'm leaving first
[AN UNSATISFIED SIGH]
(Kim Shin)
Sure
(Deokhwa)
Ah, uncle, why are you really like this?
Who are you?
Do you know that person?
Ha!
Uncle
Wow, did you hear that in the midst of it all?
[SMILING SLIGHTLY]
Uncle
[UPBEAT MUSIC STARTS TO PLAY]
(Sunny's friend)
Oh my, she's pretty even if she smeared poo on her face.
(Sunny)
That's all in the past, tsk.
It turned into something precious.
(Sunny's friend)
What are you talking about?
It's still firm, it's alright.
(Customer)
Sister, what's that shadow?
The color payoff is really good.
I'll take one of those.
(Staff)
Yes, please come this way.
I sold one for you.
Thank you.
(Sunny's friend)
But do you have plans today?
Where are you going all dressed up?
Did you maybe get a boyfriend?
I'm getting pretty to come to life
Waiting for a call, right now
It's not coming, but
Why?
I guess it's playing hard to get
Am I being pushed away?
I was reaching out
[SIGH]
[DREAMY MUSIC]
[SURPRISED BREATHING]
[SURPRISED MOANING]
(Euntak)
But why does the boss
always just look out the window?
What's out there?
Waiting for something
For what?
I don't know
I've been waiting for someone like that my whole life
For a guest?
No, for you
A prince on a white horse?
(Sunny)
I don’t like younger guys
If it’s going to be someone, I’d prefer a prince on a white horse
[EUNTAK’S FAINT SMILE]
[SUNNY’S SIGH]
[CALM MUSIC]
(Euntak)
But the uncle doesn’t have an epitaph
(Student 1)
What?
Did you pick it up?
He gave it to me
(Euntak)
Give it to me
(Student 1)
Who?
The guy who drove you this morning?
Or the dude we saw in front of your house?
(Student 1)
Wow, you really socialize
without prejudice in various ways.
Do you even know what
this business card is?
[Enigmatic music]
(Eun-tak)
It’s written
here, Chairman Yoo Shin-woo (Student 1)
So
you’re the one being
fooled, you idiot.
Ah, what, those guys are
close with this chairman?
(Student 2) Let it be, what kind of fear
would someone who’s dating an older man have?
Why?
What?
(Student 1) Aren’t you
gonna roll your eyes?
What is this?
What’s this cigarette?
(Teacher) Yeah, it’s your first
time seeing a cigarette, right?
[STUDENT 1’S PAINFUL GROAN]
You’re insane, you’re crazy.
At school
Even in the classroom, huh?
No, teacher
[smiling]
Oh, come on, hey, give me a light
[THE TEACHER'S RIDICULOUS BREATHING]
What did I say?
Light?
(Teacher)
You’re done for
Come out, follow me
(Student1)
Teacher, no
This isn't mine
This is Ji Eun-tak's
Ji Eun-tak was trying to smoke
So I took it away
Check them, this is Ji Eun-tak's
(Yuna)
Hey, Park Soo-jin, that's yours, right?
Ji Eun-tak doesn’t even smoke
Stop it already, since last time
Hey, class president, are you crazy? Do you want to die?
(Teacher)
You want to die, you do
You know where the teacher's office is, right?
Go
- (Student1) Oh...
- (Teacher) Keep going, keep going
[STUDENT1'S SIGH]
(Ghost1)
To take revenge on the kid who bullied you
Blood revenge
[Ghost1's eerie moan]
(Ghost2)
I did it, right?
Oh dear, hey, that little brat
how can you be so wicked?
[smiling] It’s so refreshing
to my insides, hey, you say
you're lonely Why don’t you
take someone with you, huh?
(Ghost 3) [scoffing]
What kind of curse is that?
- (Ghost 3) That kid is dead -
(Ghost 2) Dead (Ghost 3) I don’t
want to wake up, grandma (Ghost
2) Oh, right, what (Ghost
4) We did well, right?
(Ghost 2) I’m smoking...
[EUN-TAK’S NERVOUS BREATHING]
[in a small voice]
Yes, thank you all.
[THE LAUGHTER OF GHOSTS]
(Ghost 2)
I gave it.
[THE SURPRISED MOAN OF THE GHOSTS]
[Tire screeching sound]
- (Ghost 3) We'll go first.
- (Euntak) Why? What, what
[THE CAR DOOR OPENS WITH A CLICK]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
You said you don't drive much.
Oh, just trying to show off that I have a car.
You have a license, right?
What do you take me for?
You looked like a drunk person yesterday.
I didn't make any mistakes yesterday, did I?
You don't remember well, do you?
Can't you see the awkward look on my face?
Did you have a hangover cure? Aren't you hungry?
Why do you only ask me
such questions?
Can't you just eat something before meeting me?
(Euntak)
You're asking because you want to eat together, right?
If you don't want to, just say so.
What is it that you want to eat together, beef?
Beef?
Wow, I didn't expect that
I think it's a really good idea.
[SNICKERS]
[GEAR SHIFTING SOUND]
(Kim Shin)
Wait a minute.
[KIM SHIN UNBUCKLES HIS SEATBELT]
[THE CAR DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
[A BIRD CHIRPS]
[Mysterious sound effect]
(Kim Shin)
We've arrived, get out
[LIVELY MUSIC]
(Eun Tak)
Elegant, elegant, elegant!
[EUN TAK'S LAUGHTER]
(Kim Shin)
As a thanks for the gift of the maple leaves
(Eun Tak)
Awesome
To repay with maple leaves in maple soup
Mister, is this your honeymoon?
Get in again, let's go
(Eun Tak)
No, no, go this way
I know Quebec pretty well
(Kim Shin)
Well, the cow is over this way
(Euntak)
Huh? What did you say?
[SOFT MUSIC IS PLAYING]
I will eat well.
(Euntak)
Oh, there are a lot of swords, swords
(Kim Shin)
Put it down and talk, put it down
[Smiling]
Oh, look at that.
(Kim Shin)
Eat, you said you were hungry
(Euntak)
Yes
(Kim Shin)
Well, while eating
Don’t misunderstand what I’m saying, just listen
I’m really curious, really
(Kim Shin)
This sword
I wonder what the handle looks like?
No way
Are you suspicious of me?
(Gyung-shin)
Ah, why are you angry?
Especially for questions like this
I tend to be the cautious type who makes sure
That's the doubt
(Eun-tak)
There's a tiger on the sword handle
A tiger, right?
Yeah, right?
The white tiger, the white tiger, isn't the tiger really cool?
Of course
[EUN-TAK IS SMACKING THEIR LIPS]
(Eun-tak)
But you know
I did a bit of research on you, sir
But no matter how much I looked, I couldn't find that story?
What story?
The story about the sword being stuck
(Euntak)
Why did you get stuck in black?
Yourself? Someone else?
The person who thought it would never happen
Ah...
That's a really painful story
Then it’s fine
How old are you? Exactly how many years old?
939 years old
Ah...
That's an even more painful story
I'm sorry
(Euntak)
Still
I hope you live long
Not aging, having a lot of money
and meeting a bride like this
[EUNTAK SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(Kim Shin)
Do you want to live long?
Even if you stop and everything else flows away?
Hey, uncle
(Euntak)
Uncle, I think you'll always be here
so I feel like I can live a long time
[EUNTAK CUTS THE MEAT GENTLY]
[CALM MUSIC]
[HE SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(Euntak)
Uncle, considering your huge past,
you seem really bright
(Kim Shin)
It's almost a thousand years
What? Am I sad for a thousand years?
I humbly accept my fate
and live boldly as a courageous goblin
[EUNTAK SMILES SLIGHTLY]
Where is the sorrow that lasts for a thousand years?
Where is the love that lasts for a thousand years?
(Eun-tak)
I vote for 'there is'
Which side will you choose?
Is it sorrow, or is it love?
Sad love?
If you don't believe me, do you want to wager?
(Kim Shin)
Where did that wager talk come from...
How far have you investigated?
What else do you know?
(Eun-tak)
Having been alone for a long time
I get lonely easily, I have a bad temper,
I'm quirky,
I like dark and humid places...
He, mainly researched bad things...
(Euntak)
Humans bring blessings and anger
Do not form a family
So I wonder if that's why I was left in the hotel
It's not abandonment, it's a measure
(Kim Shin)
Think a bit yourself
What kind of thought?
If you don't want to, you don't have to do it
There's no need to
What?
Goblin bride
What's the ulterior motive?
Ah, as I hear, it seems like
You are hoping for what I don't want to do, right? Keep going?
(Euntak) Why are
you saying this now?
Ah, you don't like
being the Goblin's bride?
Or is there another woman?
Even if there's no other woman
You don't want it, so just don't?
'I see the sword, I draw the
sword,' right? What's the order?
Whether I’m a bride or not
I need to draw that sword
to prove it, so let's
see if it gets pretty (Kim
Shin) Hey, hey, uh...
Hey, talk over there, over
there (Euntak) If you
say 'Gold come out,
ttukdak' With the Goblin's club
this much (Kim Shin) Why should I?
(Euntak)
Come here
[Kim Shin's surprised moan]
(Kim Shin)
Hey, I don't have a bat
(Euntak)
You don't have a bat?
What kind of goblin doesn't have a bat?
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
(Euntak)
Wow! Wow, cool, wow
Wow, suddenly water becomes a sword
(Euntak)
Oh, that's pretty cool
Oh, that's awesome
This is a twist, with the bat
(Euntak)
Ah, I see
This 'A couple's fight is like cutting water with a knife' is
what this means
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
(Kim Shin)
That's not it
Right
A water fight is definitely fitting for a honeymoon
(Euntak)
Stand still
[EUNTAK IS SPLASHING WATER]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
[Mysterious sound effect]
[Euntak's cheer]
It must be nice to win against a high schooler
Do you use that ability to win against a high schooler?
Why, can't I use it?
I mean, I have no abilities?
You can do everything, uncle
(Euntak)
Huh? I don't have anything except seeing ghosts?
But I'm a goblin bride?
I wish it would be so?
'Gold, come out, clack clack' this much
Can you do that?
No
(Euntak)
Ah, just wait here for a moment
- Why?
- Because I have something to take care of
(Euntak)
Since I don't know when I'll come back
You can wait well, right?
Ah, and since you said you always keep your books
Keep them close
[Zipping the bag shut]
If you leave me behind, I will summon you
So keep that in mind
(Kim Shin)
I’m not leaving you behind
[Emotional music]
Why? Is it because I’m the Goblin's bride?
[Rustling of a letter]
[Sound of elevator arrival]
Please make sure to deliver it
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
(Eun-tak)
Mister!
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
(Kim Shin)
'The magnitude of mass
does not correlate with volume'
[LAUGHTER]
[EUN-TAK SNIFFS]
'That girl, as small as a violet'
'That girl, fluttering like a petal'
'Pulls me in with a mass greater than
the Earth'
'Moment'
'I am like Newton's apple'
I rolled down to
her without mercy.
'With a bang'
'With a thump'
[BLOOD DRIPS]
[EUNTAK'S RAPID BREATHING]
Red carpet jackpot, it was you, right?
Totally amazing
Uncle
(Kim Shin)
'The heart continued a dizzying pendulum motion from the sky to the ground'
Uncle, are you angry?
(Kim Shin)
'It was my first love'
[A SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
(Kim Shin)
It was dazzling
Because the day was nice
Because the day wasn't nice
Because the day was just right
Every day was good
(Kim Shin)
And
No matter what happens
It's not your fault
Mister, is it possible...
Are you really turning into a broom?
[SMIRKS]
That's not going to happen
Thank goodness
[SNIFFS]
So, now we're drawing
[A RESOLUTE BREATH]
Subtitle: Choi Hye-ran