[THEME SONG]
[Crickets chirping]
(Euntak)
Okay, then I'll draw.
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[EUNTAK'S FLUSTERED MOAN]
No, why isn't this being caught?
(Euntak)
Tsk, even though I see this, why isn't it being drawn?
Did, did you put strength in your hand?
Wait a moment, I'll try again.
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[EUNTAK'S PUZZLED MOAN]
(Euntak)
Earlier, you definitely said, 'No matter what happens, it’s not your fault'...
No going back.
Hey, so that means
that you are the Goblin's bride...
Ah, so I said there’s no going back.
Just stay still for a moment, so
I'm the one who's more flustered right now, okay?
(Kim Shin)
Hey, just stay still
How can I stay still more than this?
Hey, give me that vow, I'll burn it.
Wait a moment!
[KNOCKS THE BAG]
[REALIZING BREATH]
I got it
I think this might be it, I know.
What is it?
The prince from that fairy tale
The cursed prince, that one.
Ah, what is that?
[TENSE SOUND EFFECT]
A kiss.
[KIM SHIN'S SURPRISED MOAN]
[SOFT MUSIC]
[MYSTICAL SOUND EFFECT]
(Eun Tak)
It's just that it was too rushed
so please understand.
Open your eyes.
This is all open, you know.
[SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(Kim Shin)
Hey, what are you...
Are you crazy?
What do you mean I'm crazy?
To someone who's done their best
to make the uncle look good
(Eun Tak)
Do you know why I did it? I did it because I wanted to.
It's a loss for me too.
You've probably done
a lot until now, but I...
Ah, it's fine.
- Hey, what about me?
- It's my first kiss!
(Euntak)
This shouldn't be done like this.
Come here, let me try it one more time.
[Kim Shin's surprised gasp]
Talk over there, over there.
(Euntak)
I can't see anything right now?
If I can't even touch in this situation,
the old man will probably tell me
to throw it all up.
In this crisis,
what can I not do?
What are you doing? What's with this worldly attitude?
What are you going
to do if it doesn't work?
(Euntak) If it doesn't
work again this time
Just one thing.
- (Kim Shin) What is it?
- True love.
[KIM SHIN'S SIGH]
(Eun Tak)
If necessary, I should do that too.
Rather than getting this bag taken away from me,
I'd rather love you, sir!
[EUN TAK'S PAINFUL GROAN]
I'm sorry.
You even made it snow and worked hard.
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[PLAYFUL MUSIC]
(Eun Tak)
Wow.
(Kim Shin)
'Wow'?
(Eun Tak)
What should I do now?
(Kim Shin)
What do you mean, what?
- You're going to chase me away, right?
- (Kim Shin) I won't chase you away!
(Eun Tak)
Really?
You can't forget about the signed document either
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
They say 'a man's word is worth a gold nugget'.
(Eun Tak)
You can't be a mean adult either
[Mysterious sound effect]
(Deok Hwa)
So, are you saying our uncle
won't be coming back?
No, are you saying our uncle
has left this world?
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
Living immortally
is merely reaching mortality at last
Don't miss him too long.
Death is just
another world outside the door, so someday you
will open that door...
(Deokhwa) [sobbing] Oh, uncle,
don’t go, uncle [The grim reaper's sigh]
I don’t need the card, I really
don’t need that card, please come
back, uncle
[door lock operation sound]
[THE DOOR OPENS WITH A CLICK]
What is it?
(The grim reaper) Why is the
author coming in through that door?
(Deokhwa) [sobbing] Uncle, uncle,
[UNCLE, THE DOOR CLOSES WITH A CLICK]
(Kim Shin)
Deokhwa,
(Duk-hwa)
Ah, uncle, you’re back again?
[Kim Shin pats Duk-hwa]
You’re back again?
I love you, uncle
(Kim Shin)
Yeah, yeah
So, about that
Can you give the card back to me?
[DUK-HWA IS SOBBING]
[Playful music]
(Duk-hwa)
Huh?
You heard me, why are you acting like you didn’t hear?
(Duk-hwa)
Uncle
[DUK-HWA SNIFFS HIS NOSE]
It’s just a new world behind the door
Since you’re on this path, walk it boldly, uncle
(Grim Reaper)
Duk-hwa seems really worried about his uncle
Yeah, don’t worry about us
Can you give me back the house deed?
(Grim Reaper)
How on earth did you handle this situation?
(Kim Shin)
Ji Eun-tak
What?
Wanna return the perfume, five hundred, and the bag before you go up?
(Duk-hwa)
Uncle, did you really give that girl
so much?
(Eun-tak)
No, I don’t want to, you said you wouldn’t chase me away
(Kim Shin)
I told you to return the perfume, bag, and five hundred
I never said I would chase you away
Sir
[AWKWARD LAUGHTER]
I love you
I said I love you
(Eun-tak)
[in a small voice]
Isn't it?
[DEOK-HWA'S MOAN]
I love
[KIM-SHIN'S SURPRISED MOAN]
- Uncle
- Shut up!
- Love
- You brat!
(Kim-shin)
By any chance
Did you burn that scroll?
I burned it
(Kim-shin)
Ah, this person is taking it too far
[LAUGHTER]
Are you nervous?
(Chairman Yoo)
That's the penalty for saying goodbye so meticulously
I'll gladly accept it
(Chairman Yoo)
The scroll will be carried through Deok-hwa on a bright day.
I will send it after strictly managing it, so
don't worry too much
Thank you, and I'm sorry
Then, Nari
(Chairman Yoo)
I am sorry to Nari
Now, what do you think about not wanting to die and wanting to live?
Because of you, somewhere in this world
to someone who has lived rightly
wouldn't it be nice if a strange and beautiful fortune
or a miracle were to happen at least once
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
[SECRETARY KIM'S PUZZLED BREATH]
A man who does not age
[SECRETARY KIM'S SIGH]
[CALM MUSIC]
(Kim Shin)
At twenty-nine, you
are still shining
But by your side
I am not
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[EUN-TAK'S FLUSTERED MOAN]
No, why isn't this working?
(Eun-tak)
Sigh, it’s visible but not coming out, why?
Has the future changed
Has the prophecy changed
Either way
It's good to be back
Without speed
[A SIGH]
(Grim Reaper)
The missing guitarist
Tell me in detail, what happened?
(Eun-tak)
Ah
The start was quite nice
[Exciting music]
The buckwheat field spread out under the moonlight
The early first snow is falling
(Eun-tak)
Anyway, so I grabbed the sword
[Mysterious sound effect]
But this
It only looks like I can hold it, but I can't actually hold it
Somehow, I made it back alive
I thought one of the two wouldn't make it back
Exactly
I thought I would leave it in the buckwheat field
But it turns out I'm bringing it back
(Grim Reaper)
The other missing person doesn't know right now
[SIGH]
What happens when you draw the sword
Should I tell you?
[A pondering breath]
Then the goblin might get so angry it could die
Then this house is mine
What are you thinking?
(Euntak)
If you see me like that, uncle
I feel a bit scared
(Grim Reaper)
I can see the sword with my eyes, but why can't I grab it?
Well, those are such friendly thoughts
That's right, me too
I wonder why?
As the goblin said
Am I really not the goblin bride?
(Euntak) Will a real bride
who can wield a sword appear?
Is she pretty?
[SIGH]
There's no order in picking.
That's right.
I mean, you won’t be treating her badly or anything, right?
There’s a bond built over time.
[KIM SHIN CLICKS HIS TONGUE]
[A BIRD CHIRPS]
(Kim Shin)
With one more family member, living expenses are tight.
We’ve run out of meat, geez.
Should I start keeping a household account?
With how I feel, I'm wondering how to do the dishes.
(Eun Tak)
I, I will do it!
I really want to do the dishes!
(Kim Shin) You?
[Euntak's agreeing breath]
Well, it's true that it's the age where one
would want to do the dishes for a while.
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
[AWKWARD SMILE]
[LAUGHTER]
[KIM SHIN'S SIGH]
(Kim Shin) The laundry is piled up
like a mountain, it's a big problem.
In this situation, it's not always
easy to take it to the dry cleaners.
Do I have to throw away all the clothes?
Me
(Euntak)
As soon as I finish doing the dishes
How about doing the laundry once?
(Kimshin)
Really?
If that's what you mean, please wash it by hand
[EUNTAK'S SIGH]
(Kimshin)
Ugh, the house needs to be clean
so studying will go well
By the way, when are we going to clean the room?
With a student preparing for exams at home,
there's quite a lot of worry
[SIGH]
I think you did that on purpose?
(Euntak)
No, I didn't.
I got all wet, so it must be visible
(Euntak)
It's going to dry by evening, right?
It seems like you're doing it on purpose?
Why, do you not want to do the laundry?
If you have any complaints, just say it
(Euntak)
Ah, complaints, you spoke well
It seems you think I'm not a bride right now
Let's not judge so hastily
(Euntak)
If you keep treating me like this
You'll regret it later, seriously
I am a bride, you know.
"Why does it only show up but not get caught?"
Did you do that?
All the time I spent with you
was dazzling, right?
"Because the day is nice, because the day is not nice,
because the day is just right"
Oh, even today
(Euntak)
See?
Yes?
(Kim Shin)
Even now, without speed, it's dazzling
(Euntak)
But why am I being scolded?
That's that
How is that that?
It's all dazzling and stuff
(Euntak)
So let's not do this
Let's find another value.
If that's the case,
then the uncle is my boyfriend
I'll be your girlfriend, uncle
I don't want to
Then just a friend?
(Kim Shin)
I don't want to
Then just a resident?
(Kim Shin)
Then starting today, pay rent, fifty a month
Water, electricity, and gas are separate
(The Grim Reaper)
Did he demand money?
[Euntak's annoyed groan]
(Euntak)
Yes, from today, we're enemies
On the narrow bridge
we'll have a day to meet, now
[UPSET GROAN]
Why is this chaos happening because the black one isn't caught?
Shouldn't there be something stronger than a curse?
For example, something like true love?
I've already done all that.
What have you done?
[SIGH]
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC]
A kiss, you know?
[KIM SHIN'S SURPRISED MOAN]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
(Euntak)
Ah, that startled me.
(Kim Shin)
You just casually talk about...
Talking about kisses with anyone, huh?
Were you that kind of person?
(Euntak)
I didn’t talk about that
But the uncle just did
Didn’t you mean to do it?
Weren’t you trying not to?
A kiss
Did you?
Even if you do, it’s still my story, so why is the uncle making a fuss?
(Euntak)
Strictly speaking, this is my kiss
(Kim Shin)
Hey, where is the "yours" or "mine" in a kiss?
Even if it’s there, half of it is mine
(Euntak)
Ah, got it, I’ll take half then
Okay, forget it, I don’t need it
If you don't like it, that's fine, I'll take it all.
(Kim Shin)
Fine! You're really greedy.
[KIM SHIN AND EUN TAK'S SNICKERS]
[THE DOOR SWINGS SHUT WITH A CLICK]
Somebody
can't even call because they don't have a business card
but they themselves are very
[Sound of knocking]
[The Grim Reaper’s sigh]
[A SIGH]
(Kim Shin)
Why?
(The Grim Reaper)
Right, so it's one thing for you to come back to life
But what about the other omitted individuals?
Aren't we supposed to let them go?
- (Kim Shin) Huh?
- (Grim Reaper) Why, don't you like it?
Just let me go and we can live
happily together, like we always have,
who have you been
living with all this time?
[A SIGH FROM THE GRIM REAPER]
I don't think I'm a goblin
bride, so I have to let you go, I!
It's someone who knows our
true identities, what do you think
they'll say when they go out?
Let me go, um (Grim Reaper) If
you give me five hundred I
can see you're not the kind of
person who would ever do that, what
did you learn from watching drama?
(Kim Shin) Once you start giving, it's
over Do you want to keep being threatened?
Are you doing this because you don't want to let me go?
Hey, I don't want to let you go
I want to let you go so badly, right now?
(Kim Shin)
What?
(Grim Reaper)
Other missing persons couldn't catch the sword
You like it, right now?
Honestly, being able to see more without dying
(Kim Shin)
Hey, why is that good, what's good about it?
You must be crazy
I waited for 900 years, does that make sense?
(Grim Reaper)
Yeah, then, I’ll take you, out of friendship
Aren't you tired of that guy?
He just kisses you whenever he wants
What kind of friendship do we have
It's all about friendship!
Cheering for me to die
Is that friendship?
Look at this
(Grim Reaper)
You like it, right now, for not dying
No
I just have a promise to keep
What should I do, I signed the contract?
(Kim Shin)
A man's word is as good as gold
I'm just trying to keep a promise
Being a man
When you gave me the house deed,
Were you not a man?
[SNEER]
(Shin Kim) Hey, when
the goblin gets angry, huh?
Hey, hello, lion, lion?
[THE DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
Lion
[The door creaks shut]
[SOFT MUSIC]
[CICADAS CHIRPING]
(Euntaek)
Eul responds to the summons of Gap every year on the first snow day
Because Gap will be waiting
(Kimshin)
What are you doing here instead of being in your perfectly fine room?
Are you protesting?
I just have a snack that's close by
After you stopped having reasons to be nice to me
the snacks ran out
It's petty to bring food.
(Kim Shin) These
days, things are
tight, so honestly, snacks for exam
[STUDENTS ARE A LUXURY.
EUN-TAK'S ANGRY BREATHS]
(Eun-tak) Let's not
provoke each other;
I'm a senior about to take the college
entrance exam, and everything in the
world feels irritating
right now. (Kim Shin)
[ARE YOU ANGRY RIGHT NOW?]
Eun-tak's angry breaths. (Eun-tak)
What kind of guardian deity would come to
aid when it's right before the college
entrance exam - ah - (Kim Shin) Why, what?
Mister, do you happen to know the
answers to the college entrance exam?
Uh, but when is the college entrance exam?
I don't know that, but do
you know the answers?
Uh, should I call them for you?
[EUNTAK'S HAPPY BREATHING]
(Euntak)
Yes!
First, let's solve this all
Yes
By the way, the college entrance exam is next Thursday
[EUNTAK WRITES QUICKLY WITH A PEN]
Hey, but
That, uh, last time about the first...
(Euntak)
Ah, right
I was going to talk about that first
[AWKWARD LAUGHTER]
Well, don’t feel pressured
Of course, it was my first kiss
(Kim Shin)
Hey, you were going to talk about the first snow, right? The first snow!
(Euntak)
Ah, the first snow
Don’t talk about it
Don’t say anything regarding the 치읓
- The kid got the first problem wrong
- I said don’t talk about it
- Aren't you feeling peckish?
- I said don’t talk about it!
Why is there so much car noise these days while I'm studying?
Is the bed usable?
(Kim Shin)
I prepared mostly meat to make you feel secure
Is what I want really a lunchbox?
Can you memorize it?
(Kim Shin)
I’ll just call out the answers in order, so listen carefully.
- (Kim Shin) First, the language area
- (Eun Tak) Ah, I hate you!
[ANGRY BREATH]
Please go inside
Should I memorize ten or so? My mind is wavering
The train is coming
Absolute power requires etiquette
Well, if you really want it...
Ah, it's fine
Anyway, it's probably a problem we all know
(Kim Shin)
Oh
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
[ELEGANT MUSIC]
(Kim Shin)
Should I pat my shoulders a bit to be natural?
I'll casually check the time a bit
Just in case
Is time stopped right now?
[THE CLOCK IS TICKING]
No
[EUNTAK'S SURPRISED BREATH]
(Euntak)
What should I do, what should I do, I'm doomed!
It's been 30 minutes!
Don't worry, did you forget that your boyfriend is a goblin?
You said you didn't want him, boyfriend
That was a lie, come with me
[SOFT MUSIC]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
(Kim Shin)
Ah
Good luck on the exam!
[THE DOOR SHUTS QUIETLY]
[TIRE SCREECHING SOUND]
(Male 1)
Damn, crazy bastard, do you want to die?
[Mysterious sound effect]
[Tense music]
Where did you go?
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
Keep your eyes wide open.
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
[Car horn]
[Tire screeching sound]
[SOFT MUSIC]
[PEOPLE ARE NOISY]
(Student)
Mom! Mom!
(Female)
You’re here? Oh my...
[Laughter of students]
[Euntak's lonely laugh]
[THE MATCH IS LIT]
[SORROWFUL MUSIC]
(Eun-tak)
I’m back
Phew, it’s tough
Today I thought so much that I'm completely exhausted...
(Deok-hwa)
Did you do well on the exam?
(Grim Reaper)
I come up with the ideas
and the money is provided by the interest; what was bought is Deok-hwa
[sniffling]
Wow
It’s cake
[SOBBING]
[EUN-TAK IS SOBBING]
Why are you crying? Did you fail the exam?
[sniffling]
No, it’s not that
I’m just happy
[EUN-TAK IS SOBBING]
[THE GRIM REAPER'S DISCONTENTED BREATHING]
(Seon-tak)
I'm completely happy today
So I should make a wish
If you're with me today
It’s a free pass anywhere
Please make sure I get to see a movie with the Goblin uncle later
And popcorn, for sure
(Deok-hwa)
Hey, this girl, what about me?
Thank you for the cake, brother
(Seon-tak)
Maximum discount rate fifty
[EXCLAMATION]
[Puts in the exam ticket]
[Sniffles]
[A MOAN OF RESISTANCE]
[Blows air through lips]
[Mysterious sound effect]
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
(Together)
Huh?
There's something like that, don't try to know
- Why are you doing that?
- Huh?
(Kim Shin)
You said to watch a movie, eat popcorn
Go, your wish has come true
Really? Just a moment
I'm going to drop my bag in the room, just 10 seconds
[Eun Tak's hurried footsteps]
You guys go too, to the room, to the house
(Deok Hwa)
Ah, why? I want to watch a movie and eat popcorn too...
(Kim Shin)
No
Wow, if it's going to be like this, then why did you call me?
[The door opens and closes quietly]
Isn't the CSAT and everything just an excuse?
Let's watch a movie together.
If you created the college entrance exam, I’ll give you credit.
(Grim Reaper)
Look at me for a second.
What?
Why?
[THE GRIM REAPER SLIDES A CAKE OVER]
I have something I'm curious about.
[Smirking]
It’s probably not more than me.
(Grim Reaper)
You
Where did you get your business card?
(Deokhwa)
What?
(Grim Reaper)
I’m talking about the business card.
It’s a rectangle, mostly white,
and has sharp four corners...
(Duk-hwa)
Well, I’m a proper third-generation chaebol, so I come out of the
company. But why do you want my business card?
I want it (Duk-hwa)
Huh? [Grim Reaper's Sigh]
[THE GRIM REAPER'S PUZZLED BREATH]
And there's something else I'm
curious about, is it really this close?
(Sunny)
If he is really
Yoo Duk-hwa of Cheonwoo
Group, then he is my lord
[(SUNNY)
THE LANDLORD’S SIGH]
(Grim Reaper)
You say you’re some
lord or something, landlord, oh,
yes
You have just one property, so why?
"Store Closure"
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
[DOOR LOCK ACTIVATION SOUND]
[SIGH]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
(Man 2)
[In a drunken voice]
You know, people, I...
Huh? Where are you going? The store is closed?
Oh, I'm on my way there right now
[SIGH]
Yes, we're closed
My boyfriend is waiting, so please come back later
(Man 2)
Come on
You have to open the door
How about just one more drink, huh?
[Mysterious sound effects]
[Man 2's scream]
[TENSE MUSIC]
[MAN 2'S PAINED GROAN]
(Sunny)
No, wait a minute
Right now
Did you just fly away?
Whoosh, boom?
[GASPING BREATH]
Why? Are you a bird?
(Man 2)
Why am I like this?
Why am I here?
What I'm saying is
I'm going crazy
Why do I keep seeing things like this these days?
Um, please be careful going in
[SUNNY'S FRIGHTENED WHIMPER]
(Eun-tak)
Can you do something like this too?
(Kim Shin)
Do you think there's something I can't do?
What, what should I pull out for you?
Just say rabbit, raccoon, anything
(Euntak)
It's a lighter, uncle, I want that lighter.
[KIM SHIN'S SOLEMN BREATH]
[Lively music plays]
[Machine operating sound]
(Kim Shin)
What did you say? I didn't hear you.
I didn't talk to you.
[MACHINE OPERATING SOUND]
[THE COINS CLINK AS THEY ARE INSERTED]
(Kim Shin)
Ah, this time it was really a waste, wasn't it?
(Euntak)
Let's stop it.
What’s the point of getting the coins out?
You can't even get one lighter out.
Let it go, let it go.
(Euntaek)
I haven't caught it yet
The movie time is almost up
(Kim Shin)
Hey, just, just let go
I'm going, I'm really going now, I'm going
[KIM SHIN SLAPS THE MACHINE]
[In a small voice]
Don't make a fuss
and put people in a difficult position
If you're scared, just say it
But still, it's been 19 years in the horror business
This much is, what
You can handle it, right?
[KIM SHIN SNICKERS]
Oh, here we go
[Tense music starts playing]
[Kim Shin clears his throat]
[A SCREAM IS HEARD]
[KIM SHIN'S SCREAM]
(Kim Shin)
Ah, I'm scared
[Kim Shin's scream]
[People's astonished murmurs]
(Kim Shin)
I want to go out, I want to go out
[Kim Shin shouts]
(Eun Tak)
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
[The audience murmurs]
[KIM SHIN CONTINUES TO SCREAM]
[KIM SHIN'S RAGGED BREATHING]
[EUN TAK'S ANGRY BREATHING]
[KIM SHIN'S GROANS OF PAIN]
[KIM SHIN'S CLEARING OF THROAT]
(Kim Shin)
[Rustling popcorn]
Look at this
The first snow has fallen at the cinema
[EUNTAK'S ANGRY BREATHING]
[KIM SHIN'S AWKWARD BREATHING]
(Kim Shin)
Ah, sorry, I'm sorry
[EUNTAK HUFFS]
(Euntak)
I couldn't see a single scene because of you, not a single scene
I don't even know what movie it is
(Kim Shin)
Wasn't the zombie too scary?
Ha, the future of Korean cinema is bright
Just go ahead and order
(Euntak)
You must be hungry after shouting and crying and all.
I'm not hungry because I've eaten
popcorn, so don't worry about it.
Sure, then I won't
worry about it.
(Kim Shin) Just
one of those in large.
[Funny music] (Clerk)
Yes, I understand.
[KIM SHIN EATS IT SLURPINGLY]
[KIM SHIN'S SATISFIED MOAN]
[SUCKING ON FINGERS]
I substituted the problem number 7 in
the repair area
(Euntak) into the
equation and then placed
lettuce on the x-axis...
No, that's not it.
I almost fell into
a trap there (Euntak).
Is it delicious?
(Kim Shin) Oh,
this large size is
really completely
large (Euntak).
Eating that much is not
good for your health; didn't
you have juice in large before?
(Kim Shin) How many servings of beef did
you eat before that? Are you in good health?
(Euntak)
Damn it
(Kim Shin)
It's really delicious, but you should eat it too
(Euntak)
How much is this? You can't just eat two, knowing everything
How long are you going to scold me like this?
Giving and taking it all back, the bag was pretty
I've never seen five hundred before
If you weren't going to give it from the start
(Kim Shin)
I'll do that next time
(Euntak)
Even when you give it, it's really weird
Like you’re definitely someone who isn’t next to me
Do it later when you grow up
A card for Deokhwa oppa
A house for the Grim Reaper uncle
Just what I want only
It's just like a farewell gift.
Right?
(Euntak)
Farewell gift
Mister, if you pull out that sword
We were planning to leave, right?
[TRANQUIL MUSIC]
That's right
(Euntak)
But why?
(Kim Shin)
I think I've said it once
When the bride appears
We need to be ready to leave even further
Where to?
Europe? Canada?
Even now?
Do you still want to leave?
No, I don't want to leave
But if the bride really shows up...
That choice will not be mine anymore.
Ah, right.
Are you going with that real bride?
Will you send me off?
No.
(Eun-tak)
I won't let you, so you can just leave me behind.
When the real bride appears,
No, I'll be leaving before that.
Just go when I’m not around.
Without me knowing.
[I TAKE A BREATH]
[A SIGH]
(Deok-hwa)
Did your uncle buy you something delicious yesterday?
(Eun-tak)
No.
(Dukhwa) Why, are you still
living in that house, Kongjwi?
Yes, the goblin is a
stepmother, and how many
stepmothers are there in life, really
(Dukhwa) Isn't it
strange? Our uncle, just by
watching girl groups,
seems like a gentleman
whose thousand years of
anger disappears, but you know?
Since he met you,
this girl, he's just
been angry all the time, it means
you’re quite not his
type, that girl group?
[A SIGH OF DISBELIEF]
(Euntak) They say when
you go to college, you lose
weight and become pretty,
that's what the adults said.
This damn gentleman
Just wait until I get into college, seriously
[EUNTAK SNAPS HER FINGERS]
[ANGRY BREATHING SOUNDS]
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
[THE SOUND OF CRAWLING OPERATION]
(Euntak)
Oh, college oppas
[EUNTAK SMILES SLIGHTLY]
[THE BALL HITS THE BAT WITH A BANG]
[TENSION-FILLED SOUND EFFECTS]
[THE BALL IS CAUGHT]
[EUNTAK'S SURPRISED BREATH]
[SOFT MUSIC]
Are you okay?
Taehui oppa?
(Taehui)
Ji Euntak?
Wow, how long has it been?
I almost didn't recognize you
[AWKWARD LAUGHTER]
That's right, I've changed a lot, haven't I?
(Euntak)
I've been through a lot
a whole lot
And I've become prettier
[Soft music]
I've grown a lot taller
[TAEHUI'S LAUGHTER]
[AWKWARD LAUGHTER]
[EUNTAK'S SHY BREATH]
Oppa, are you attending this school?
I took the writing exam here today
[LAUGHTER]
[NERVOUS LAUGHTER]
[HEAVY MUSIC]
[PLEASANT BREATH]
Representative, over here
Is that brat there?
That kid who's called a representative
[ROARS]
[THUNDER RUMBLES LOUDLY]
(Deokhwa)
Get up and eat something.
Your hair is a mess.
Almost broke my wrist.
(Deokhwa)
Who?
Your body is all twisted.
I thought it was a twisted bread.
(Deokhwa)
So who?
I should have just let you play the piano.
(Kimshin)
That way, the two of them wouldn’t have met.
(Deokhwa)
Who met whom?
(Euntak)
I’m back.
[HE’S ALL ENERGETIC]
[SOFT MUSIC]
[EUNTAK’S LAUGHTER]
[THE BALL HITS THE BAT WITH A THUD]
[THE BALL GOES PING]
[YOUNG TAE-HEE HITS THE BALL]
[YOUNG EUN-TAK'S DISPLEASED BREATH]
[Tense sound effect]
[Kim-shin's surprised groan]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
(Young Eun-tak)
Huh?
No, oh my, what is that fool
uncle doing? [Kim-shin's cheers]
Oh, it's annoying [the ball hits
the bat with a
[PING]
(KIM-SHIN)
WOW, I HIT IT, KIM-SHIN'S LAUGHTER]
[YOUNG TAE-HEE HITS THE BALL]
Tae-hee oppa really
became a baseball
[PLAYER, HOW COOL, LAUGHTER]
(Euntak)
Oh
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
(Euntak)
Do you want to eat ice cream?
I don’t want to. I'm eating it alone?
I paid for this, didn’t I?
(Euntak)
I didn’t say anything.
(Kim Shin)
It’s raining
I really want to eat ice cream
Because it’s raining
(Euntak)
I told you I didn’t say anything.
(Kim Shin)
Then why are you just standing there holding that without saying anything?
Put that spinning thing down while I'm still being nice
(Euntak)
This is a Bluetooth speaker
(Kim Shin)
Take your hands off.
Do you know how to use this?
(Euntak)
You can take pictures with it
[SNICKERS]
I'm going to take a picture of me eating this with it, so don’t touch it
What, why?
(Euntak)
It's really petty to bring food, seriously
Why did it rain?
Why do you feel that way? Are you depressed?
Are you asking because you don’t know?
What, that thing that doesn’t catch a break?
Is that my fault?
(Euntak)
I did my best!
Is it true that the sword
is drawn in the first place?
No, even if we kiss, it won't do
We both said "I love you," but it still won't work,
what more can we do?
You weren't sincere (Kim
Shin)
It was a very secular "I
love you," was it sincere for you, uncle?
(Euntak)
It was a very
self-interested
"I love you," anyway
your personality is really weird, do you think it's good?
I'm still young, young,
young, what about that?
I won't age, but you will I'll keep being
young and beautiful, but you're not young, right?
(Eun-tak)
And I met my first love
There’s no time for the uncle to be beautiful in my eyes
[Lively music]
What, what love?
(Eun-tak)
Uncle, are you good at baseball?
Our Tae-hee oppa is really good at baseball
Did you see? Me playing baseball?
I’m going to be surprised when I see it, this
Ah, I’m not even a resident anymore
.'This' is it?
Ah, yes, I will withdraw now
(Eun-tak)
Please take good life photos with this
Don't, hey, don't ask me to take a picture!
[A GASP OF BREATH]
This is real
Who is Tae-hee? With me
(Baseball team member)
Hey, Choi Tae-hee
[Kim-shin breathes out]
Who’s looking for you
[Bright music]
[Sound of footsteps echoing]
I’m Choi Tae-hee, who are you?
You
Were you going to look like this?
(Tae-hee)
What?
(Kim-shin)
You’re the best-looking here, damn
That’s right
But
Uncle, you’ve seen me before, right?
You’re seeing me now, right?
No, I see, I see
[Exciting music]
(Taehee) Have I really
never seen this before?
When I was this small?
[YOUNG TAEHEE HITS THE BALL]
[KIM SHIN'S SURPRISED GASP]
[KIM SHIN'S STRAINING GASP]
[A SIGH]
You can't even hit that?
(Young Taehee) Try doing your waist
[LIKE THIS, LIKE THIS, YOU RIDICULOUS BREATH]
Enough, you do well, because I'm
better at it (Young Taehee)
First
of all, you shouldn't hold the bat
like that, hey, 155 cm Kim, I've
lived my whole life with this bat...
Ah, that's enough.
You'll be shocked if you find out who I am,
so just mind your own business.
Then, do you want to make a bet with me?
[AN ABSURD LAUGH]
That's ridiculous.
Who are you making a bet with right now...
Really, don't regret it, you.
And don't you regret it either, uncle.
(Young Taehee)
Ten hits with the ball,
the winner gets to have a wish granted.
Sounds good.
[KIM SHIN'S STRAINED MOAN]
(Kim Shin)
Come in!
[Kim Shin's moan]
[HITS THE BALL WITH A BANG]
(Taehee's mom)
It's a thief!
[EXCITING MUSIC]
I don't know when that thief came in,
but they took the piano away completely.
They really got rid of it.
(Taehee's mom)
How could nobody in the neighborhood see
someone taking something that big away?
It's really ghostly supernatural.
It's supernatural.
[SOUND EFFECTS OF WIND CUTTING THROUGH]
(Taehee)
Back then, I won the bet,
and asked to get rid of my piano,
because I really have no talent,
but my mom wouldn't give up.
I said I would become a baseball player.
But the piano
really disappeared.
(김신) But?
Isn't that the guy
from back then?
No.
I think that it’s
probably not right.
If it's that uncle from back
then, he really hasn't aged at all.
[TENSE MUSIC]
(Kim Shin) For that reason
the child recognized me.
So what?
(Kim Shin) Is that
all you can say?
I didn't ask to hear
that kind of response.
Do you think I'm refining
this vulgar thing together?
If you don't erase your memories
There will be ominous rumors
about a man who does not age.
I have to leave this place.
Let's live in harmony, shall we?
You say you've never done that?
(Kim Shin) That's not
how you live your life.
Helping each other
and living, huh?
What help can there be from a goblin
that can't erase even one memory?
Oh, really, let's
wait and see, where.
(The Grim Reaper) [Snickering]
Just wait and see, Chi
(Kim Shin) Bread
[Blowing air through the
mouth] (Grim Reaper) Hey!
(Kim Shin) Well, weren't you
going to cook and eat it anyway?
[SNICKER]
[SIGH]
[TENSE MUSIC]
[EUNTAK RUMMAGES
THROUGH THE BAG]
Ah, good, perfect.
[The switch turns
on] [Euntak's scream]
[EUNTAK'S FLUSTERED MOAN]
What brings you to this room?
(Euntak) Um...
To clean
It was outside the
vacuum cleaner.
Put aside what
you're sitting on.
[I CRUMPLE THE PAPER]
One more page.
[HUMOROUS MUSIC]
[MYSTERIOUS BREATHING SOUNDS]
I think I've only signed once.
(Eun-tak) Really? But
why are there two sheets?
Oh my, what a world!
(Kim Shin) You have forgery of official
documents, breaking and entering, and theft...
( Eun-tak ) Ah, that's
so petty, seriously.
For girl groups, even a thousand years
of fury is said to disappear completely.
I apologize for not knowing
that you were that type.
Um, this is mine, so
please give it to me.
I came to get this back.
You really don't know.
Huh? Didn't I say to read
it? When did I say that?
[THE RIDICULOUS BREATHING
OF EUNTAK AND KIM SHIN]
(Gimshin) Wow, look at him/her?
Look at this, look at this
I can't tell what's the
original and what's a copy.
In the midst of this, there are
talents and I can't even praise them.
That's really big,
what is it going to be...
[CLICKING THE TONGUE]
[THE PAPER RINGS SOFTLY]
[IT RALLIES]
You're not just treating the book
roughly, are you? Is it someone else's?
Ah, I'm so pissed off, damn it. Just try
to catch me on something, really, damn it.
Look at this, this.
I scribbled on
someone else's book.
Oh my, first love?
That's right.
It must have been.
It does everything you
can do with a broom.
It's the last first kiss.
(Eun-tak) You
really can't write well.
[MOBILE PHONE RINGTONE]
[NERVOUS BREATHS]
[CLEARS THE THROAT]
Hello, oppa.
[GRAND MUSIC]
[I EXHALE]
It's okay.
[MOBILE PHONE VIBRATION SOUND]
[THE URGENT GROAN
OF THE GRIM REAPER]
(Kim Shin) What do
you want me to do?
The phone is ringing.
So what?
Please answer the phone.
The more I avoid it,
the more it might kill me.
(The Grim Reaper) But I still don't have
a business card, so I can't receive it.
I have nothing to say
after receiving it, just once.
Why do you have nothing to say?
(Kim Shin) [Imitating the Grim
Reaper] 'Don't you recognize my voice?'
It's not a voice that
you could forget.
[Playful music] Are you
saying not to help each other?
You say you don't need it? The grim
reaper who can't see an inch ahead.
Ah, fine, shit.
But where did the
other missing person go?
He can't help you either.
(Kim Shin) In front of the
ice cream shop down there
Haha, hoho, hehe, hihi
I'm in the middle of frying.
Are you roasting sesame seeds?
Why are you outside
when you have a house?
Ah, go away, I don't
even want to explain.
[SURPRISED BREATH]
[URGENT MOAN]
(Euntak) I thought about
it, and it's so amazing.
How did you just happen
to meet oppa there?
Me too
How have you been, brother?
Well, I don't know.
Sometimes while thinking of you?
[EUNTAK'S SMILE]
Brother, really.
[The door opens and closes quietly]
(The Grim Reaper) Other missing persons
[EUNTAK'S SURPRISED MOAN]
[CELL PHONE VIBRATION SOUND]
(Grim Reaper) Please
answer the phone.
Are you crazy?
(Euntak) What if you
follow me all the way here?
Who are you?
(Is that) your father?
[HEAVY MUSIC]
You, your words are harsh.
What is the name of
someone who speaks harshly?
(Brother) Oppa!
Don't say your name Don't
look, lower your gaze, quickly
[ANGRY BREATHS]
I can't answer the
phone right now, so
(Grim Reaper) If you don't
answer the phone for me
Asking for the author's name.
I'll write it down well.
Solve it.
(Eun-tak) I got it.
Oppa, wait a minute.
(Taehui) Oh
[SIGH]
Those who speak
harshly, take a seat.
(The Grim Reaper) Yeah, that, playing
the piano Are you playing baseball?
How do you know?
(Eun-tak) If a girl receives it, she'll
misunderstand it even more. Ah, I don't know.
[CLEARS THE THROAT]
Ah, ah, ah
Hello
Isn't that Kim Woo-bin's phone?
That's right.
Ah, Manager Kim Woo-bin is
currently away for a moment.
Is that person a liar?
Ah, it's the department head.
What kind of company is this?
You get promoted in just one second?
Okay, I know
everything next to me.
The cafe I saw before,
tomorrow at 1 PM.
Come as a manager or
as a director, just come.
Please convey that
I'll kill you if you're late.
[CALL TERMINATION SOUND]
[EUNTAK'S PUZZLING BREATH]
[EUNTAK'S SHOCKED MOAN]
What happened,
what did they say?
[A SIGH]
Talk while looking
at each other's faces.
(Eun-tak) Tomorrow at 1
PM, the cafe we saw before.
But the person who just called.
I've heard this
somewhere a lot, maybe...
(Grim Reaper) Wait, let
me ask my question first.
Ah, what is the question?
[LIVELY MUSIC]
(Euntak) After the phone
number and name comes the age.
Blood type, single,
married, level of wealth.
Dating experience,
ideal type, etc.
I don't know what to
ask, prepare everything.
Aquarius, no, no.
(Grim Reaper)
Sagittarius, Sag...
(Grim Reaper) Age 34
Lunar birthday, the 5th
day of the 11th month.
Sagittarius, AB type, unmarried
The house is on lease, the
car will be soon if needed.
In the past, neat; the
business cards are still...
I missed you.
[SUNNY'S RIDICULOUS
BREATHING SOUNDS]
Ha, really, me too.
He's a funny guy, really.
Is it good? You were
avoiding the call like that?
Ugh, I don't think you would like
someone without a business card.
Ah, then 'I don't
have a business card.'
You can just talk when
you answer the phone.
Huh? You can send
it by text. [Soft music]
From now on, surely...
Do you have a
business card, Sunny?
Why my business card?
I'm curious about what
kind of person Sunny is.
My face is my business card.
It's written right on your
face, isn't it? Beautiful person.
(Grim Reaper) Ah
Yes
That's right.
Really
I want to receive it.
[LAUGHTER]
See? It's so much fun
when we meet like this, right?
Getting to know more
and becoming closer.
[SUNNY'S SIGH]
[HE/SHE IS SLICING QUICKLY]
[As he placed the knife down
sharply] What do you like, Woobin?
It's Sunny.
I'm going crazy.
Not that, well, hobby,
something like that.
It's Sunny.
[A SIGH]
I understand.
Sunny's actions
are unpredictable.
I am drawn to it as
blindly as I am to dramas.
(The Grim Reaper) Sunny's
unpredictable actions are
You need to unleash
your imagination and
My clumsy actions
They are all wrong answers.
The new hobby of a person
named Sunny that I recently acquired.
It seems like a divine plan It
also seems like a divine mistake...
That's right.
[A SIGH]
How do you speak so well?
Do you, by any
chance, have a religion?
Sigh, there must
be something else.
Contact me again
when you're ready...
(Sunny) Uh, no, it's
okay if you don't have it.
Just sit down before I kill you.
[CLEARING THROAT]
[BREATHLESS SIGH]
(Sunny) What’s up with this guy?
(Grim Reaper) 34 years old, birthday on the
lunar calendar, 5th day of the 11th month
(Sunny) Ah, no Ah, I
won't, I don't have to do it
Just sit there.
I'll treat it like I'm
looking at a pictorial.
[SIGH]
(Sunny) What do you like?
(Grim Reaper) Well,
I’m a vegetable, then.
(Sunny) Huh? What is it?
I have to go that way.
Then what about me?
(Weren't we on our way to eat?)
No, you didn't even feed me.
You ate one hot dog.
Overeating is the
root of all diseases.
[RIDICULOUS BREATHING SOUND]
I see the person who
makes me the sickest is here.
(Sunny) Okay,
where are you going?
We're going for a
company dinner.
If you miss it, there's a fine.
Ha, what, this kind of guy...
Really clumsy actions
are all incorrect.
(Sunny) Everything is wrong.
The problem is too difficult.
(Lion 1) Let's eat
and die, cheers!
(Together) Cheers!
[The lion 2 lets out a breath]
(Lion 1) Oh, just eat a little bit.
[THE LAUGHTER OF LION 3]
[ tense sound effects ] (Man
1) Damn it, I’m going to report it.
Take a look!
I'm trying to die, damn it.
Does she know what she just did?
That will definitely have
problems within a month.
What should I do, senior?
It's your fate, what can you do?
I’m done, I really need
to go to the bathroom.
(Me too)
[THE LIONS TOAST]
[THE JOYFUL ROAR OF THE LION 2]
(Lion 1) [exhaling] Oh, the
general manager is here.
Let's wrap things up, okay?
Calculate.
(The Grim Reaper) Yeah
I drank a lot.
Huh?
[THE GRIM REAPER RUMMAGES
THROUGH THE CLOTHES]
Huh?
Why is that?
Isn't there anything?
membership fee
[TENSE SOUND EFFECT]
(A man 1) Ah, damn.
I'm going to take a look, okay!
I feel like I’ve been wronged.
The man I just bumped into.
I see.
Ha, what should I do, senior?
(Lion 4) They'll really be in trouble in many ways,
for sure [The Grim Reaper's awkward breathing sound]
(Lion 1) Hey, this won't do.
Put on your hat, go out in turn.
Let's move slowly one by
one without being awkward.
But is this allowed?
(사자3) If you use your abilities
personally outside of official duties
I need to write a statement...
I won't let you use it,
so don't worry, okay?
[LION 3 SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(Lion 1) From the 23rd
batch, go out quickly, okay?
[Playful music]
[Mysterious sound effects]
[The Lion's Cough] (Lion 1)
There is a way for everything.
What can we do? Is there a way?
You'll know soon, yeah.
[LION 1 SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(The Grim Reaper)
Hey, you, Lee 씨
[LION 1 GIGGLES]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[A SIGH]
[IRRITATED BREATHING]
[Call connection tone] [Sigh]
I need your help.
[KIM SHIN'S SIGH]
(Police) Are you going
to vouch for their identity?
You need a guarantor to go out.
It seems there is a
misunderstanding.
I did receive the call, but
I don't know the interest.
I've never received help.
Well, I don't know how to help.
(Police) Did you come
after receiving a call?
[A SIGH]
(Land of the Dead Guide)
Let's pretend we know.
I will help too.
Taehee oppa, in terms of memory.
I just know well.
(Kim Shin) Eating
without paying...
It’s a truly unheard-of
and outrageous charge.
Where should I sign?
Ah, I am such a person.
[CHEERFUL MUSIC]
You
Do you have a business card?
[THE SIREN IS WAILING FROM AFAR]
[THE GRIM REAPER SNORTS]
(Grim Reaper) What happened,
why do you have a business card?
(Dukhwa) End room uncle
Eat tofu.
Did you know? The
interest has a business card.
Business card?
Of course I have it.
(Dukhwa) Everything in our
company belongs to my uncle.
Hotel, trade, ship Refining,
construction, furniture, dayo
Did you not know?
Ah, hey, it's fine, I
didn't say anything.
(I am a big person.)
(Uncle) Tofu, tofu, hurry up.
[Smiling] I really
wanted to try this.
Uncle or niece That's
enough, move aside, damn it.
(Dukhwa) But that uncle Why
does he always walk like that...
I noticed, I noticed
I knew, I knew
At that time, you said that if I reached
out, I would see something, that.
Reincarnation of humans
[SURPRISED BREATH]
If you touch it, you
can see your past life.
Then what about uncle?
Uncle, don't you have
any special skills like that?
My specialty is being alive.
(Dukhwa) There's
nothing but the rain, right?
Uncle, tofu, tofu
[THE PAPER RINGS]
[PLAYFUL MUSIC]
[KIM SHIN'S SIGH]
[AMAZING BREATH SOUNDS]
Ah...
[CALL WAITING TONE]
(Grim Reaper) Looks like the other
missing people haven't come in yet.
Are you meeting that friend?
(Euntak) Hello
Where are you right now?
What time is it now that you
haven't come in, in this harsh world?
(Eun-tak) It's 7 PM right
now I'm busy at the moment.
[CALL TERMINATION SOUND]
Yes, hello...
[SIGH]
[MOBILE PHONE OPERATION SOUND]
[DIAL TONE]
[KIM SHIN'S SIGH]
[Guidance voice] Power is off
Connecting to voice mailbox.
A beeping sound followed
by call charges being applied...
Ah, me...
[TENSE SOUND EFFECTS]
(Goblin) The ghost that
sees the goblin bride, hand
Where?
(Uncle!)
Uncle
(The Grim Reaper) Your uncle
is not here, he has gone out.
(Dukhwa) Oh, really?
Then please pass
this on to my uncle.
You left something in the
car and keep forgetting it.
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
You got your card taken away What do you
mean by being sweet and obedient about it?
If my grandfather brings it, he said
he would give me pocket money.
Humans are
(Dukhwa) Capitalism is this scary
and convenient, Uncle at the end.
(Grim Reaper) But this, you
got a card and I got a house.
What you gave to your grandfather
must be much more expensive, right?
Is that so?
(Duk-hwa) I don't
know what it is either.
Since I don't know, shall we take
a look? There's no uncle either.
Oh, beautiful, beautiful.
[A GASP OF SURPRISE]
[HEAVY MUSIC]
(Dukhwa) Who is it? Is it
my uncle's ex-girlfriend?
It looks just like an antique.
That's right, isn't it?
[TEARS DROP SUDDENLY]
End room uncle, why is that?
[STRENUOUS GROANS]
[SOBS]
[TEARS FALL]
(Three Gods) It truly had to be a
heartbreaking beginning of love.
It's sad, isn't it, that
thing called fate?
Love is not a sin.
They may not have
committed a crime.
[A SIGH]
(사자4) What crime
have I committed?
Are you suddenly
raising the rent like this?
It's really difficult if you suddenly raise
the monthly rent by a hundred thousand won.
(Samshin) Ever since the bachelor moved in
I keep seeing the grim reaper in my dreams.
[THE LAUGHTER OF LION 4]
(Lion 4) Yes
Ah, and the bathroom keeps
leaking water When on earth...
Really? Then don't wash.
You're pretty even
if you don't wash up.
[Surprised breath] [The
goddess smiles slightly]
[SWEET MUSIC]
(Kim Shin) You sing really well?
(Eun-tak) a bit
How did you know and come here?
(Kim Shin) No matter how hard you
try, you're still in the palm of my hand.
What about the chicken restaurant?
Did you get fired from your part-time job?
I've increased my
part-time job hours.
The wedding singing
gig is good, you know.
But
Watching a wedding
makes me feel a bit strange.
What's wrong?
Just
Ah, I guess I won't have a
mom to light a candle for me.
Ah, I guess I won't have
a dad to hold my hand.
I don't have any friends
to take pictures for me.
Since I have no friends, there won't
be any money for the celebration either.
What, that kind of thought?
(Eun-tak) [smiling
slightly] Isn't it funny?
So
I think I was obsessed
with the uncle priest.
It feels like I'm
getting a family.
The family that I don't
have is like destiny.
I thought it was coming to me.
Oh, why are you crying?
Do I have to say I'm sorry?
No.
[SOBS]
If you think about it, the one
who should apologize is me, well.
(Seung-tak) You know...
I'm really sorry, uncle.
I can't take out
the sword for you.
I was going to keep talking, but
Lately, every time we
meet, we end up fighting.
[THEY SMILE FAINTLY]
The timing is a bit off, but
Since we're on the
topic, I should do it.
I'm currently increasing
my part-time job.
I'm preparing step
by step, you know?
So, could you wait
just a little until I go out?
Don't bully me.
I'll be ready until I go out.
Student discount
Please give me a 50%
discount on the bullying, okay?
[LAUGHTER]
No discounts will be provided.
50% is absolutely not okay.
(Eun-tak) chi
[In a small voice] 45 percent
[WE LAUGH TOGETHER]
[Tense sound effect]
[Kim Shin's moans in pain]
[TENSE MUSIC]
Why, does it hurt?
[Kim Shin's labored breathing]
Is it because of the sword?
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[Kim Shin's labored breathing]
[Eun Tak's trembling breath]
[HEAVY SOUND EFFECTS]
[Kim Shin's labored breathing]
[Eun Tak's trembling breathing]
[TENSION-BUILDING SOUND EFFECT]
Uncle
[LABORED BREATHING]
The sword is caught.
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[A GASP OF SURPRISE]
(Euntak) Wait a moment
[ROUGH BREATHING]
Wait a moment, I’ll
take it out for you.
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[PAINFUL MOAN]
Ah, it's moving.
[TENSION-BUILDING MUSIC]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[THE LED SIGN CRACKLES]
[TIRE NOISE]
[HEAVY MUSIC]
(Kim Shin) The
prophecy was right.
I knew the future
I saw was correct.
Because of this child, now I am
End this immortal curse.
I can return to nothing.
Human lifespan is only
about a hundred years.
Trying to look
back one more time.
Is it my immortal life?
Is it your face?
Ah…
It seems to be your face.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
(Eun-tak) See,
I'm really a bride.
It was a fate
like this, destiny.
That's awesome.
[EUNTAK SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(Grim Reaper) Who
on earth are you?
Does it hurt like this?
I feel like I've
seen it somewhere.
(Grim Reaper) How did
you remember your past life?
(Dukhwa) Having lived for
a hundred years, one day
On a moderately suitable day.
(Kim Shin) After living for
a hundred years, one day
On a suitably fine day.
It was first love.
I hope to be able to confess.
I seek permission from the sky.
Subtitle: Choi Hye-ran