[THEME SONG]
[HEAVY MUSIC]
(The Grim Reaper)
It seems I
am the worst memory
from you
and from him, Kim Shin
(Kim Shin)
Can you hear my voice?
I can hear your voice clearly
very vividly
[Soldier 1's shout]
[Soldier 1 swiftly slashes with a sword]
[TENSION-BUILDING SOUND EFFECT]
General Kim Shin
I greet your Majesty
after 900 years
I meet the Emperor
What has blinded my eyes
is it the 900 years of time
or the hatred of the gods?
(Kim Shin)
I couldn’t recognize you even though you were so close.
You are
Wang Ye.
In the end
Am I the one?
Am I
Wang Ye?
That youthful and foolish face
[Heavy sound effect]
[Displeased breath]
In the end
Is it me?
The battlefield has always been hell
We returned from there
The enemy couldn't kill us
Those subordinates of mine
[HEAVY SOUND EFFECT]
My young sister
My innocent relatives.
[HEAVY SOUND EFFECTS]
I was hit by a sword and an arrow in front of me
By imperial command
The young and foolish emperor
With that one word he spat out
Me
You're saying it was me?
[I CHOKE UP]
Am I
Really the king?
[KIM SHIN GRIPS MY NECK TIGHTLY]
[SHAKY BREATHS]
[ROUGH BREATHING]
[The reaper's labored breathing]
[Kim Shin's sigh]
[KIM SHIN'S SIGH]
(Kim Shin)
I still remember every minute, every second
Of that living hell every day
Since I have no memory, you don't
It must be comfortable.
Even after 900 years
(Young Wang-ye)
When did the heavens ever favor you?
[The heavens rumble]
The heavens are still on your side.
[FADING FOOTSTEPS]
[SOBBING]
[SOFT MUSIC]
(Grim Reaper)
What exactly have I
done?
What memories have I erased?
What choices have I made?
"Kim Sun, Wang-ye"
How cowardly have I
been?
[SHAKING BREATH]
(Eun-tak)
What happened?
Did you meet Park Jung-heon?
I met him, Park Jung-heon and Wang-yeo too
(Kim Shin)
Pack lightly and come out, let's go
Where to?
We're going to Chairman Yoo's family home
Yes, just 10 minutes
(Kim Shin)
Ji Eun-tak
Why aren’t you asking anything?
Did you know?
That he is Wang-yeo
It was what the deceased said
I didn’t understand the intention
I thought it wasn’t something to relay recklessly
(Eun-tak)
But whether I convey it or not
If it’s a fate to miss, then it will miss.
If it's destiny that we should meet,
I thought we would.
I'm sorry.
Pack your things and come out.
[THE DOOR CLICKS OPEN AND SHUT]
(Kim Shin)
I'm going to stay here for a while.
Let the staff members take a break for now.
Okay, but why is my uncle staying here?
We'll each use a guest room on the second floor.
No need to worry.
Okay, but why is my uncle staying here?
(Eun Tak)
I'm going to the CEO's house.
I'm worried.
The CEO must be confused about everything.
Okay, then I’ll ask you
for a favor - if
something happens...
- (Euntak) I know, just
relax, Deokhwa oppa will take you.
Me?
[THE DOOR SWINGS OPEN WITH A CLICK]
(Deokhwa) Ah, what is it? Why did you come out
of the house? [The door swings shut with a click]
Did you fight with the
uncle in the last room?
No, even if we fought, why would the
uncle in the last room be kicked out?
Why did he come out himself?
Isn't it consideration?
The Grim Reaper doesn't
have anywhere to go, ah,
[THAT PART IS REALLY SAD, SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[A SIGH MIXED WITH IRRITATION]
[THE DOORBELL RINGS]
[A SIGH]
[MOBILE PHONE OPERATING SOUND]
[Guidance Voice] The power is off
It will connect to the voice mailbox.
After the beep, call
charges will apply.
[THERE IS A BEEPING SOUND]
(Kim Shin) You are
In this life as well
I’m protecting that fool
[SIGH]
Brother
Where are you?
(Eun-tak)
I left home, with me
Then what about that person?
I think they might be at home
[SIGH]
So they’re still alive
They probably weren’t alive to begin with
[EUN-TAK SMILES SLIGHTLY]
[NERVOUS LAUGHTER]
That’s right
But
Do you remember your past life, sir?
(Eun-tak)
How do you remember it?
[SOFT MUSIC]
Sexually
(Euntak)
Yes?
I mean, do you want to have a drink, soju? Beer?
[SUNNY EXHALES A BREATH]
(Sunny)
Ha, part-timer
Humans have four lives, right?
I thought about it
and I feel like I'm in the fourth life
Why?
At least I know two lives
(Sunny)
In this life, I've met you, brother
and Jungin as well
What about you?
I wish this is
my first life
Why?
The second life, the third life
Will I meet my older brother in the fourth life?
[SUNNY'S SIGH]
You should have seen that stubbornness of yours during the Goryeo Dynasty
Why come back when you know you’re going to die?
Just live your own life
[SHE GRABS THE BOTTLE OF LIQUOR]
[SHE POURS THE LIQUOR SMOOTHLY]
[SUNNY PUTS DOWN THE BOTTLE OF LIQUOR WITH A THUD]
[SUNNY'S SIGH]
(Lion 1)
No, if you do one part of the water bill
I’m really so unfair, right?
Ever since the woman from downstairs
came, it costs 4,000 won more.
They said they moved out of the apartment rental, how pitiful.
Then what about me?
I barely saved up the deposit
and I finally became independent for the first time in my life.
Well,
whether it's the first or the fourth,
they're all precious, right?
What are you talking about?
And the water supply is frozen,
so there's no water coming out at all.
But why should I take on part of the blame?
So,
it's sad, fate.
(Three gods)
In the end, will I have to pay such a high price?
[A FRUSTRATED GROAN FROM THE LION]
(Lion 1) I really
shouldn't be like this.
What is your name?
Give me cash,
cards aren't accepted.
[I EXHALE MY BREATH]
[HEAVY MUSIC]
Notify that I died gloriously.
I will inform you of my grief.
(The Grim Reaper) You will die.
I don't want it
(Kim Shin)
Those two didn’t come to the graduation ceremony
but seem to have come to see someone
who is at the graduation ceremony
[SIGH]
(Lion 1)
It's Mr. Kim from Janghang-dong
It's a rumor, but
Well, I heard that in some ghost's whisper
he held the hand of a dying deceased
I wonder if that ghost is perhaps
the other missing person that you overlooked, senior
Are you listening?
Senior
Oh
What did you say?
[SIGH]
Why have you been like this lately?
What does it matter that
there are missing pieces?
[TENSE MUSIC]
[URGENT BREATHING SOUNDS]
(Middle) Were you here?
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
Seeing your face,
You finally caught
[THAT HAND, SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
(Middle) Yes, what did you see?
What crime was there inside?
I was not in there (Lion
2) Only that woman was
there, she was a queen
from an ancient era.
Was I in there?
Or perhaps beside her, Was there
a hand handing over the potion?
[The sound of cracking]
(Jungheon)
Thin and white like you
[THE YOUNG KING STRIKES THE TRAY]
(Jungheon)
Do you know what is in that medicinal concoction?
My sin is your sin
No
No, it can't be
(Jungheon)
The owner of the hand that hands over the concoction is you
How pitiful this is
Without having any memories
You can't even recognize me
[SHIVERING BREATH]
No
It can't be
(Jungheon)
Don't worry
I will surely keep your secret
Above all, if it becomes known that you used your ability for personal gain
Isn't it going to be troublesome?
(Jungheon)
So let's keep your sin and my sin
A secret
[SHIVERING BREATH]
[LAUGHTER]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
Indeed, you were Kim Sun
[CLEARING THE TABLE WITH A CLATTER]
(Jungheon)
In this life, you must die in my hands
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
Missing guitarist
It's a familiar face.
(The Grim Reaper)
I felt it 20 years ago
You are an evil spirit
Taking away the dark hearts of humans
Surviving by stealing the malevolent energy
(Jungheon)
It's me
I just raised my hand to their black desires
[TENSE SOUND EFFECT]
[CAR ENGINE SOUND]
(Woman)
Ah, it's a thief! It's a pickpocket!
(Jungheon)
Was it me who closed my eyes
[TIRE SCREECHING SOUND]
[TENSE SOUND EFFECT]
(Ghost)
So, did you push me off the roof that day?
[EERIE SOUND EFFECT]
(Junghun)
Have they closed their eyes?
(Grim Reaper)
Stop with the riddles.
What is your name?
Don't waste your effort.
Even if you know my name,
you can't do anything to me.
So haven't I lived
for 900 years?
[TENSION-BUILDING SOUND EFFECT]
Don't mess around
State your name.
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
(Junghun)
Are you asking knowing what your name is?
Shall I tell you?
You are still grasping something insignificant.
[SUNNY SORTS WITH A CLATTER]
(Jungheon)
Seeing what you hold dear tightly
[A cracking sound is heard]
In this life, I will surely die
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
Do you
know me?
[SUNNY SORTS WITH A CLATTER]
[HEAVY MUSIC]
[A sizzling sound is heard]
[Heartbreaking music]
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
I knew you would laugh
(Grim Reaper)
[THE GRIM REAPER'S LAUGHTER]
I shouldn't laugh
[BUT WE LAUGH TOGETHER]
(Grim Reaper)
Ah, I shouldn't laugh
[THE CELLPHONE VIBRATES]
(Grim Reaper)
Hello
Deokhwa, it's me
Hello?
[EUNTAK QUICKLY SKETCHES WITH A PEN]
(Euntak)
It looks like this
(Grim Reaper)
This sword was given by the king, right?
You're not asking anything
You're siding with that goblin
I'm sorry but
Could you side with me just once?
What's that?
(Grim Reaper)
Please pass this on to Sunny.
I feel like there shouldn't even be such an excuse.
To me
I'll do that.
(Grim Reaper)
You won't remember me.
Just cover for me about the ring.
I'm going.
(Euntak)
It seems like you remember.
Are you still waiting, my lord?
I can't wait anymore.
Why?
Is it because I remember all my past lives?
The woman who loved you, my lord
is the sister of a great criminal.
[SOFT MUSIC]
So that person died in his hands.
I keep getting confused.
(Sunny)
I felt the pain of my heart being torn apart.
Was it me or was it my past life?
Was he sad too?
(Sunny)
I only saw his back turned away.
I was told to cherish only the happy moments,
but it seems I liked even that much.
If I remember all of this,
(Sunny)
What about that person?
Did you meet him?
It's in the past.
It's been a long time since then.
It’s something that transcends life.
You are from a past life, but...
I am still the current life.
I am living that life.
I have nowhere to retreat to.
I can only move forward.
That person killed you.
(Sunny)
They didn’t kill me; they killed Kim Sun-Il.
Not me.
I am Sunny.
My life is
this life.
[SIGH]
But if you, brother, move forward,
[HEAVY MUSIC]
Even crossing life, still,
my answer remains the same as it was then.
Go on, brother.
This time, if I move forward.
(Kim Shin)
What I want to do to her
It will not be forgiveness
[SIGH]
Don't worry about me
(Sunny)
In this life
I will truly
be happy, brother
(Death God)
Stabbing this sword in my heart
I have lived for 900 years
That person
[THE SCENERY WEEPS]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[DARK MUSIC]
(Audit Office 1)
This is the afterlife audit team
Sit down
(Audit Office 2)
You are performing the duties of a messenger
It has been confirmed that private abilities were used.
(Board of Audit and Inspection 1)
Aside from erasing human memories,
the list was disclosed.
[Tense music]
Not taking action even after being discovered.
Returning the previous life to humans, etc.
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECTS]
(Grim Reaper)
They fought each other.
You saw nothing.
(Grim Reaper)
Say, "I'll go first."
[Mysterious sound effects]
I'll go first.
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
[Mystical sound effect]
[Man's scream]
[THE MAN'S PAINFUL MOAN]
(Grim Reaper)
Could you take a moment to look into my eyes?
[In a strained voice]
I'm sorry, but could you please look into my eyes?
[MYSTICAL SOUND EFFECT]
(Grim Reaper)
The list of other missing persons has arrived
The list has arrived
Other missing person
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
(Grim Reaper)
There's something I haven't mentioned
It's about what you saw in your past life, Sunny
Isn't it a secret?
It seems to be your younger sister's reincarnation.
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
(Grim Reaper)
I am the Grim Reaper.
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
Does everyone acknowledge it?
I acknowledge it.
(Audit Office 2)
Since the individual has also acknowledged this, we will impose a heavy penalty.
Face the seriousness of the matter.
I will gladly
accept it.
(Audit Office 1)
It will never be sweet.
The Grim Reaper deals with those who have committed great sins in life,
going through hundreds of years of hell.
Those who have chosen to erase their own memories
[meaningful music]
Now face your sins again
That is the severe punishment for all these violations of discipline
[THE MUSIC BUILDS TENSION]
[meaningful sound effects]
[groaning in pain]
[A STRAINED GROAN]
[A LABORED BREATH]
(Interlude)
Having exterminated the traitors
You demonstrate strength
The previously restless slumber of the people
Is finally at peace
In the marketplace, the praises of Your Majesty resound.
I'm worried that you might be feeling unwell.
I urged to bring the pre-meal wine.
(Chorus)
The fragrance is beautiful
and the sweetness and sourness are harmonized,
making my mouth water...
[A TREMBLING BREATH]
(Chorus)
Your Majesty's mind and body are weak,
and all the people are worried.
From tomorrow, reduce the royal meals
and take the herbal medicine.
[A TENSE SOUND EFFECT]
You may consume it even if it tastes bitter,
and clear both your body and spirit
to restore your strength...
[Breath is exhaled]
[The bowl is tossed with a clatter]
If this level of strength is enough...
Will you be able to?
[A TREMBLING BREATH]
[A SIGH]
(Sang-gung)
I wonder if someday you'll come looking for me
[A TREMBLING BREATH OF SANG-GUNG]
[TENSE MUSIC]
[A TREMBLING BREATH]
[HEAVY MUSIC]
[SOBBING]
[WANG-YEO CONTINUES TO SOB]
[PEOPLE ARE NOISY]
[THE SURPRISED MURMURS OF THE PEOPLE]
[PEOPLE ARE WHISPERING]
(Wang-yeo)
This beautiful silk dress
Who will I put it on?
This beautiful jade ring
Whose hand will I place it on?
This beautiful silk dress
Who will I dress
This beautiful jade ring
Whose hand will it fit
[A SIGH]
(Samsin)
That beautiful jade ring
Give it to me
Surely it will be of use someday
Do you want it?
Yes
Then I shall give it
Take it
[A SIGH]
This fine clothing
Has no owner
Perhaps
Is it something you are looking for
Then
Take it
[THE CLOTHES ARE TOSSED ASIDE]
[THE KING'S SIGH]
(Concubine) Your Majesty,
the herbal medicine...
[WANGYE'S SIGH]
(Wangye)
My people
My subjects
My woman
Even I myself
No one
Ever loved me
In the end
I was never
Loved by anyone
[A SIGH]
Bring more herbal medicine
I know what is inside
What?
Let's end it in one go
The herbal medicine
Bring more.
[A TREMBLING BREATH]
[A SIGH]
[SIGNIFICANT MUSIC]
It is a royal command
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECTS]
[GASPING FOR BREATH]
(Audit Office 1)
You, who are now guilty in this world,
the greatest sinner among those sins,
the sin of having taken your own life,
have paid for 600 years of hell after death.
[GASPING MOANS]
Therefore,
the duty of the Grim Reaper is suspended,
and awaits further instructions.
[GASPING FOR BREATH]
I
was Wang-yeo.
[sobbing]
I
[WEEP]
I killed them all.
[I WEEP]
You killed me.
[THE GRIM REAPER CONTINUES TO SOB]
[THE GRIM REAPER SLAMS THE TABLE]
[THE TEACUPS CLATTER]
"Kim Sun, Wang Ye"
[AN ARROW FLIES SWIFTLY]
[Soldier 2 slashes with a sword]
(Kim Shin)
What do you think, gentlemen?
[SOLDIER 1 SLASHES WITH A SWORD]
What should I do
What should I do about him
[SHUDDERING BREATHS]
Never touch him again
You don't deserve to cry after looking at this painting
I
sheathed my sword
(The grim reaper)
To you
I killed him
I killed them all.
Memory
It happened.
I
was Wang Yeo
[WITH ANGRY BREATHS]
(Kim Shin)
Yeah
It's you
You did it, you killed them all
Killing, killing, you
Even you have been killed
You
Neither your woman nor your loyal subjects nor your Goryeo
Not even you
Could protect a single one
Seon-i
My little sister
was the one who protected you with her life
You should have lived
You should have survived until the end
And died by my sword
So the heavy crime of treason
that you laid upon me
[HEAVY MUSIC]
You should have
proven it with death.
[CRYING]
(Kim Shin)
Sister must have known
When Kim Shin came out of Park Joong-hun's mouth
That the next would be Kim Sun
That it would become a reason to trap you
So that foolish one
Died on the spot
As the sister of a traitor
To save you
The ring
I put that ring
[Crying]
So cruelly on
Her hand
(Grim Reaper)
That ring
Came back in this life too
Please
You
Just kill me
[SHAKING BREATH]
[KIM SHIN'S SIGH]
Is that so?
Am I going to abandon you again?
(Kim Shin)
The sin of killing you
Seems to be enough for the sin you committed
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
[THE DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
I thought a lot about it
(Eun Tak)
Is it right to deliver this?
So I kept it for a few days
I'm sorry
(Sunny)
Why are you sorry?
Aren't I the one who's sorry?
Aren't you going to ask more?
What should I ask? I know everything.
This.
I didn't expect to
receive it like this, but
Was someone else's
pain,罪, longing all mine?
[FAKE LAUGH]
That shaman is impressive.
But
What sin do you have?
What?
You said you're the
goblin brother's bride.
It's me and that person Let's say we are
entangled by the bond of our past lives.
Why are you involved
with your older brother?
It's because it's
such a destiny.
[EUNTAK SMILES SLIGHTLY]
Are you doing
something strange too?
(Sunny) Are you also
just like that? Like a bird?
[LAUGHTER]
I'm not like that.
(The Grim Reaper) A tool of destruction
to end the immortality of the goblin
That's the fate of
the Goblin's bride.
[SOBBING]
(The Grim Reaper) If you draw
your sword, that person will...
Dust as wind.
It will scatter.
[TREMBLING BREATH]
This world
Or to some other world forever.
[SAD MUSIC]
Part-time worker?
Ah, yes.
I can just make
it rain a little less.
So that citizens are
not inconvenienced.
The first snow might
come a little early.
People of the
world, let's have fun!
I'm doing the most
important thing.
But why did you
become a goblin, brother?
Because the world
needs miracles.
Strange and beautiful
(Sunny) Who says that?
Me
[EUN-TAK SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(Sunny) Yeah
Then what about the Grim Reaper?
Because everyone dies, right?
Because there is death
Because life is brilliant.
[SUNNY'S SURPRISED BREATH]
(Sunny) Look at
how well you speak.
As expected, a prestigious
university student [Tense music]
[PUZZLED MOAN]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
It's been a while.
(The middle) The
sister of a lowly deity
The empress of a
lowly martial family.
[EUNTAK'S URGENT BREATHING]
(Sunny) Why, is
there something there?
(Get lost) You should leave.
It's not your turn yet,
you're next after that bitch.
[EUNTAK'S ANXIOUS BREATHING]
Don't come closer.
(Boss) Could you please pass me
the lighter from my coat? Quickly!
Lighter?
Why the lighter?
(중헌) He was just like my son.
That bitch ruined everything.
I will kill you.
Boss, hurry up!
Got it.
Yes, two years!
[Tension-inducing sound effect]
[SUNNY'S STARTLED BREATH]
(Sunny) Part-timer,
what's wrong?
What is it, what is it?
Wake up, part-timer?
[EUNTAK'S AGONIZING MOAN]
[EUNTAK'S PAINFUL MOAN]
(Sunny) Are you
okay? Can you walk?
Yes, it's okay.
Were you surprised?
Well, I was surprised.
Who were you talking to earlier?
(Sunny) That blue thing, huh?
What is that light-like thing,
huh? You said you're a person.
Are you, by any chance, someone who seems like a
person but isn't quite a person? Someone like you?
[LAUGHTER]
This is a first for me too.
You go in first, boss.
I will meet with the
boss and then go in.
Did you promise to come?
If I call, you can't not come.
[SHE SMIRKS SLIGHTLY]
[BLOWING AIR THROUGH THE MOUTH]
How have you been?
[SOFT MUSIC]
[EUN-TAK IS SOBBING]
I missed you.
(Kim Shin) Me too
How have you been?
(Kim Shin) Yeah
I'm sorry, I'll be there soon.
[EUN-TAK SOBS]
The mark on your neck...
Why?
I can hardly see it.
(Eun-tak) Is that so?
Why?
(Kim Shin) The fact that it
has become this blurred means
That means I've put you
in danger to that extent.
From now on, it means that I
might not be able to feel you.
(Eun-tak) Don't worry.
I will be more careful
and more cautious.
Did you happen to run into
him again? Park Jung-heon?
That's true, but
I wasn't the goal.
The boss was the goal.
That's not something
you should worry about.
You just worry about yourself Because
someone else will take care of your sister.
Just two days.
(Fate) Destiny is the
question I have thrown.
The answer is
You all should find it.
I received a question and
He and I must find that answer.
[HEAVY MUSIC]
"Park Junghun"
[THE URGENT BREATHING OF LION 1]
(Lion 1) What is happening?
(Grim Reaper) It's the documents for the
other missing persons I mentioned before.
Are you talking about the deceased
person you said you missed 20 years ago?
(The Grim Reaper) Uh, but I'm in
standby mode, so I can't handle it.
You have to do it.
So from now on, listen
carefully to what I say.
Please speak.
It's a wandering spirit that
has been drifting for 900 years.
I've survived by parasitizing
the dark emotions of humans.
Even if we meet, it's
difficult with our own strength.
But if you put your
name on the list,
I think it will be possible
to control it for now.
Please process it
quickly, it's urgent.
By noon tomorrow...
(Lion 1) Before midnight today
Thank you.
I have something to say as well.
(I think you need to know this.)
I'm taking over the area under
your supervision and working on it.
Among the list, there's
someone named Ji-eun Tak.
Isn't this the goblin
priest from that time?
Looking at the date...
Don't spill it.
Get your hands off the list.
I saw it, you don't know it.
[THE GRIM REAPER'S SIGH]
"Jieun Tak, 20 years old"
A week later
[The bird chirps]
[Euntak's sigh]
It's not your turn yet,
you're next after that bitch.
In the end
Are you aiming for me?
"Yushinwoo"
[SIGH]
[THE BIRD CHIRPS]
Euntak-i
The list has arrived.
Somehow...
It must be related
to Park Joong-heon.
[A SIGH OF AGREEMENT]
In the year of the refined
oil, in the month of the cat...
Now that date has no meaning.
You must know.
I think it would be
good to know anyway.
Park Jung-heon
(Kim Shin) Circling
around my sister
Protect
[HEAVY MUSIC]
Just once, protect my sister.
As my sister protected you
(The Grim Reaper) That day
[Military 1 swiftly slashes with a knife] (Kim
Shin) The road to the emperor was too long, and
[HEAVY SOUND EFFECTS]
I ultimately couldn't reach it.
Knowing that I won't
be able to reach it
Even though I knew everything,
I could only move forward.
That day, you
What were you
moving forward for?
that seat
Knowing it will become a grave
To convey the
words I couldn't say.
Receiving a sword
I have asked to meet
you countless times, but
You, the emperor
and my brother-in-law,
All that has been conveyed is the
doctrine to leave for the outskirts.
(Kim Shin) It was only on the
day I was sure that I would die.
You showed your face.
So
What do you mean
by going that far...?
Your Majesty,
(Emperor) By not caring
I took care of it,
Your Highness.
By not taking care of
you, I took care of you.
(To Kim Shin) To your
half-brother, the former emperor.
To my sister, who was your ally.
To the me who kept
your consideration
You were loved.
So please say just one word.
I will strike down my sword
filled with anger and concern.
Kill Park Joong-heon
Just that one word.
That sword
I didn't know it would
pierce my heart.
[MEANINGFUL MUSIC]
How could this...
(Chungheon) You and I, it has
been 900 years [Kim Shin's sigh]
That mere sword of
water cannot cut me down.
Even if I come this far away
In the end, I get
to wield this sword.
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
(The Grim Reaper)
What's going on?
Are you hurt again, Gyeom?
The utility value of this sword
is ultimately [tense music]
That was it.
Killing Park Joong-heon
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
[TREMBLING BREATH]
(Is it a science major?)
The completion of a
phone number is the lip.
[I GIVE A KISS]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
[SOBBING]
[SHE SLAMS THE LIPSTICK DOWN]
[Crying] I'm going crazy, 정말
You need to look
pretty, stop crying.
(merchant) Please report back.
(Sunny) Why do you
keep following me?
It's already been a few
days, are you a stalker?
It's not that.
It seems like our paths
coincidentally overlapped.
(Sunny) Thanks to you,
I felt like I was on a date.
With Kim Woo-bin.
Why on earth?
How to remember...
Because you
hypnotized me poorly.
(The Grim Reaper) It's tough and
Forget all the sad moments.
Whether in a
past life or this life
And
I forget too.
I hope this can be a
happy ending for you.
You told me to only keep the happy moments,
yet you're telling me to forget you.
(Sunny) The order doesn't match.
Every moment that you are in
Even all the sad
and difficult things.
I even thought that was great.
So
By my dying, I protected you.
Did you have a happy ending?
Seeing you look
so young right now
You didn't live long, did you?
Every day
intensely
I miss you.
[HEAVY MUSIC]
[A SLIGHT SIGH]
Why would you do that?
Because I'm foolish.
(Sunny) Realize it quickly.
But how can I...
I fell for you even
in this life, didn't I?
[SNIFFLE]
Is it because the
inside is so bright?
Sleep.
We're really breaking up.
[I am about to cry] I
won't fall in love in this life.
The punishment I can give you.
This is the only thing.
Goodbye, Your Majesty.
[FOOTSTEPS ECHO]
[FADING FOOTSTEPS]
(Child1) Give it to me!
(Child 2) Where did you get the snacks
without any money? Did you steal them?
No! Grandma bought it for me!
Did you not get it by begging?
Don't insult our grandmother!
(Child1) Wind blast!
[The laughter of Child 3] (Child
2) Here we go again, seriously.
(Child3) Hey, that's
not how you do a fireball.
This is how it's
done, Wind Blast!
[THE MOANS OF CHILD 1 IN PAIN]
[THE CHILD GIGGLES]
(Child 1) Wind blast!
[THE CHILD 2 AND CHILD 3 GIGGLE]
[THE DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
Hey, these guys again!
(Child1) Wind blast!
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC]
- (Child 3) What is it?
- (Child 2) Was it really true?
(Is it okay?)
Sister, how did you know?
(I kid 1) I really thought you were
going to shoot a whirlwind, before to me.
I really shot, a magical wind.
When I was your
age, my sister too.
"I want to become a goblin
bride when I grow up," I said.
(Euntak) I really
became a goblin bride.
But it's a secret.
Things like air guns are really dangerous,
so you shouldn't just shoot them anywhere.
Got it?
I'll only tell grandma.
[EUN-TAK PUTS DOWN THE
TRASH WITH A RUSTLING SOUND]
Oh, that's pretty cool?
If it's cool, let's
go on a trip.
(Eun-tak) Whoaaa
Why?
I'm currently fluttering.
That's great, you're aiming
for heart-throbbing moments.
You look like you're
in a good mood.
Let's do that.
Let's just go
traveling and all that.
[SHE SMILES FAINTLY]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
[THE SOUND OF INSECTS CHIRPING]
[DOOR LOCK OPERATION SOUND]
(김신) Oh, you're pretty
good at this, aren't you?
uncle
[Camera operation sound]
[Camera shutter sound]
[EUN-TAK SMILES FAINTLY]
[WE LAUGH TOGETHER]
[Euntak smiles slightly]
[Kimsin's surprised moan]
[EUNTAK'S SMILE]
(Kim Shin) Ahem
Good.
[KIM SHIN SLIGHTLY SMILES]
I have a gift.
(Euntak) I'm enough.
It's already overflowing
with perfection even now.
(Kim Shin) I don't think so?
( Eun-tak ) Oh! Is this?
Now that you're an
adult, remember that.
This kind of thing is originally
meant to be shared one by one.
So I exactly forged it.
Ah, but I got
caught at that time.
But what is the original?
Is that it?
[DENYING MOANS]
Give me that.
(Ms. Kim) Hmm, I don't want to?
(Hee-tak) Ah, I
want to have that.
[Eun-tak's laughter]
[Kim-shin's surprised moan]
[Euntak gives a kiss]
[Euntak's moans of strain]
[WE LAUGH TOGETHER]
[POIGNANT MUSIC]
(Eun-tak) Eun-eun responds to the summoning of
Gap every year on the day of the first snow.
It's because Gap
will be waiting.
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
(Eun-tak) Awesome
[EUN-TAK'S STARTLED BREATH]
It's snowing.
It's the first snow, sir.
[I SOB]
What, should I be sad
for a thousand years?
What, am I always sick?
I humbly accept my fate and
live boldly as a brave goblin.
I am now humbly
accepting my destiny.
I’m a brave goblin
bride living boldly.
[KIM SHIN IS SOBBING]
(김신) Is there really any sorrow
that lasts a thousand years?
Where is the love that
lasts for a thousand years?
(Euntak) I vote for 'exist'.
Which side will you hang
it on? Is it sadness or love?
(Kim Shin) Such
excuses like permission
I hope it happens.
Using that excuse, I
I wish I could keep living.
[CRYING]
Like you
Sad love?
[SOBBING]
[KIM SHIN CONTINUES TO SOB]
(Employee) Mr. Andy Lau!
(Dukhwa) Ah, card, my card.
(Employee) Did you sleep well?
This is not a home,
it's a workplace.
Please let's stick to
it for at least a day!
(Duk-hwa) I'm sorry.
(Duk-hwa) Ah, welcome,
customer [Staff's sigh]
Oh, you came to see the bed.
Wow, you have a good eye again.
This bed, you know.
If you lie down like this then
sleep comes gently like this...
(Employee) Mr. Andy Lau?
Mr. Andy Lau! [Calm music]
(Duk-hwa) Oh, you startled
me [Employee's laughter]
Ah, this is something
I did unintentionally...
(Kim Shin) I will
miss you a lot.
(Dukhwa) The bed feels nice,
so sleep is coming again like that.
[DEOKHWA'S SMILE]
(Sunny) The drink is ready.
[THE DOOR OPENS AND
CLOSES WITH A BANG]
Welcome, please sit this way.
(Kim Shin) You look so peaceful.
You look healthy.
That would work.
As you in this life.
Live well.
[LAUGHTER]
(Euntaek) Oh, now just thinking about it makes
you feel like you're right in front of me.
I just thought of Mr. Kim Shin.
What brings you here?
I wanted to see you.
There are also requests.
Hello.
It's about Park Joong-heon.
(Ah...)
I was thinking about it
anyway and I was curious.
Why now, of all times?
I have wandered for 900 years.
I wonder why it
has appeared now.
Yeah, because of that.
You need to be brave
for just a moment.
Can you do it?
I'm a goblin bride.
[SMILES SLIGHTLY]
(Kim Shin) Listen carefully
I will call you in a moment Then
you summon me immediately.
It's gum.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
I'll be back.
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
[MYSTERIOUS BREATHING SOUND]
[TENSE MUSIC]
[TENSE SOUND EFFECT]
[A CRACKING SOUND IS HEARD]
(Didn't I) already tell you?
You can't cut me with a sword
made of water or anything like that.
(I know)
So shall we head to
our final battlefield now?
[TENSE SOUND EFFECT]
[THERE IS A CRACKLING SOUND]
(I know where I will go)
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
[CALM MUSIC]
[SIGH]
(Keun-tak) But
buckwheat flowers are
What does the flower
language mean?
Lover
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
[TENSE MUSIC]
[A SURPRISED BREATH]
As expected.
You can no longer see me now.
[MEANINGFUL SOUND EFFECT]
It's because of me.
[DARK MUSIC]
You were waiting for my mark to
fade away. [Significant sound effect]
You're quite something.
One is late.
Use me...
[TENSE SOUND EFFECTS]
Uncle, the sword.
You're thinking of drawing.
[EUNTAK'S TREMBLING BREATHS]
[MOBILE PHONE VIBRATION SOUND]
(Kim Shin) Now, summon me.
[URGENT MOAN]
[Nervous sound effect]
[Euntak's difficult groan]
[EUNTAK'S PAINFUL GROAN]
Don't resent.
This is your destiny.
[DIFFICULT MOAN]
[EUNTAK CLICKS THE LIGHTER]
[The lighter sparks to life]
[I blow air into my mouth]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
[EUNTAK'S LABORED BREATHING]
Are you okay?
[MUSIC THAT HEIGHTENS TENSION]
Ji Eun-tak!
[Sharp sound effect]
[Mysterious sound effect]
[EUNTAK'S ROUGH BREATHING]
I know everything.
I figured out the reason
why you appeared now.
I'm Beyo, I'm fast.
(Seung-tak) Once you
get inside my body, it's over.
I'm borrowing my hand
to draw the sword, uncle.
I'm anyway...
If it weren't for you, I
would have been doomed.
Hurry up, let me go, quickly!
[TENSION-INDUCING SOUND EFFECT]
(This child was right,
you should have cut it.)
Now it's you or me who will die.
You keep looking back.
[A SINISTER SOUND EFFECT]
(It's going to die in my hands.)
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECTS]
(The Grim Reaper)
Park Joong-heon
The deceased shall
answer the call of the lion.
- You...
- Park Joong-heon
Park Joong-heon!
[Tense sound effect]
[Tense music]
[Mysterious sound effect]
[SOLEMN MUSIC]
[HE SWIFTLY PULLS OUT THE KNIFE]
[SHARP SOUND EFFECT]
[SIGNIFICANT SOUND EFFECT]
You're going this way.
[DARK MUSIC]
One is not empty.
(I killed you again)
Look.
Eventually
It's a disaster.
[HEAVY MUSIC]
[SHARP SOUND EFFECT]
[KIM SHIN'S SIGH]
[TREMBLING BREATH]
Please forgive me.
[I WEEP]
Die gloriously.
I'm finally letting you know.
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
[EUNTAK'S HURRIED BREATH]
(Seung-tak) No way!
No way
[Sorrowful music]
[Euntak's trembling breaths]
[KIM SHIN'S FAINT BREATH]
[EUNTAK SOBS]
[Weeping] No, no
No way.
[EUNTAK KEEPS SOBBING]
[KIM SHIN'S FAINT BREATH]
[KIM SHIN'S LABORED BREATHING]
[EUN-TAK KEEPS SOBBING]
[EUNTAK'S TREMBLING BREATH]
[KIM SHIN'S LABORED BREATH]
(Kim Shin) Meeting
you is my life
It was an image.
I don't like it.
Please
[TREMBLING BREATH]
I told you I wouldn't
let go of your hand.
You promised.
I'll come when it rains.
I'll come with the first snow.
Please just let me do that.
I'll pray to God.
[Sniffling] Don't do that.
Don't go like that!
(Yeontak) I love you.
Uncle, I love you.
I love you.
me too
(Kim Shin) [In a
weak voice] I love you.
That much.
Already done
[EUNTAK'S TREMBLING BREATH]
[EUNTAK IS SOBBING]
[MYSTERIOUS SOUND EFFECT]
[EUNTAK IS ABOUT TO CRY]
[Eun-tak sobs]
[Touching music]
[EUNTAK CRIES OUT IN DESPAIR]
( Eun-tak ) [ sobbing ] No way.
In the end, I
You made that choice.
(Kim Shin) I understand now.
Subtitle: Choi Hye-ran